So far you have been creating places and that objects and injecting them back in real time job obligations.
We often create interfaces that is we always quarter to interfaces for abstraction.
For example here we have an order bill which is a class that holds all the business logic for the order
to place an order.
These are the be will is an interface and it will be implemented by a class card arder be Will.
I am it has it easy relationship with our beagle.
Similarly we have an order to be able which contains not the business logic but all that data access
called it could be JTB see hibernate etc. all that gold will go into the order.
It connects to the database and does that work.
Again this order is an interface and it will be implemented by arder will impact this order be will
depends on r r d r r r b will impel the relationship as a relationship with order to be able not to
inject arder Diego into our hobby will impel.
We do not or we cannot create an instance of this interface.
So we provide the implementation in our spring configuration will be providing this class of details
in the bin so that spudding can inject it into the RB will impact.
So the steps will remain the same.
We will be creating for porgies plane or the Jawa interfaces and play all the java objects create the
configuration and finally create the test class.
Do the first step in this lecture that is creating the interfaces and classes go to eclipse minimize
everything.
How one of them expanded so that we can copy the configuration and test reichlich new interface.
We should always code to interfaces back his name com dot dot dot Supreme Court advance a dot injecting
dot in Dunner face this and the interface name should be are to be will which will have the business
logic method the one and only matter this will have its place on the net returns nothing.
Wired plays are the mighty fall.
Its public abstract create a class for it right click new class.
So if you are right click on that interface will create the class you the name.
We will I am will be gone and search for arder we will select that hit.
OK.
Finish automatically.
Eclipse will override the place.
Our method for us simply sits out in the matter it sits out inside Arta be your
let's create the next interface which is the order to be able to write like create new interface or
to be able finish this already.
Well we all have one single method called create Varda.
This would create the Arta in the database.
Typically these methods will have parameters here I am not adding all the complexity because we just
want to see how interface injection works.
Right click new CLOS arder you.
I am the implementation.
Click on Add search for Arta be able select that it OK.
Finish and ready to delete that to do this out in side
order you will create order.
That the next lecture will copy or the test and the configuration and will make the necessary changes.
This should be in side order do you.