In the previous lecture hall created POJO classes and interfaces in this lecture he will add this dependency
and start injecting beans using this pudding configuration.
Let's get started by going to eclipse to Arabi will impel the art to be wimple should use the art to
be able to do that.
You're going to use arder be able and Carlat be able as I feed this in the same package we are using
that interface here.
You can make this private control will create getter and setter methods.
OK.
Black and blue shift after formatting.
And we can then use this D-Will inside the place are the matter the order art create order or simply
walking to create art or method which right now if you go to the implementation of it open implementation
by hitting control and this method it only prints this much.
So we have successfully added the link between the two classes.
Now let's configure.
By creating this being configuration we are going to create a bean and injected copy of the earlier
conflicts onto this new package open it.
Maximize delete everything.
We are not going to do annotations.
We'll start with the example being the first thing we are going to create always is the dependency.
In this case our Deewar is the dependency.
So let's start with that class is equality.
The Bakkies name
Bastet dot order will impel we how to provide the implementation.
Here are not the interface.
We cannot create objects of the interface and spring cannot do that either.
So you need to provide one of the implementation classes here.
But when we use it we use the interface so we can since this interface is implemented by order to be
able at runtime the spring container use is runtime polymorphism and it can inject any implementation
class in do this kind of object.
That is the power of spring.
Its very loosely coupled if you want to configure another class instead of this which implements the
same interface.
We can do that as well without changing the code.
We can just change the Exxon-Mobile configuration.
I will show you that later.
Class name is equal to that simply call this the ABL blows it right there.
We have the dependency the next bean bean class is required to base the package Daut are to be able
or R to be will impellor always the spring configuration will have implementation classes.
When we create the beans are the be all IMPO mean is equal to be able close it right.
The are we need to inject the dependency been let's use property injection
property name is equal to whatever name we have given in order to be Williams-Bolar that name is Diego
be able and you can use the ref bag here right here ref is equal to B will that name which we have used
here and you can close the property tag right there.
We are converging to format.
So in this letter you have successfully created the dependency we have.
First of all we have used order to be able by defining a field and we have used it inside the place
and then we have come up with the building configuration to create the dependency by using the implementation
of it and then injected it into the order b will be the next lecture will create the test and test it
and doing.