A last and final step is to create a best class and see the dependency injection through interfaces
can grab an earlier test.
I'm going to create one from scratch new class test with the main matter.
The first step in test it the to do and create application context which is our spring can be in that
context is equal to new class.
But example L-Space
application context within of course conflict Daut example semi-colon can go to one important application
context from Spring Framework that Abda package name operate very strict in the conflict or someone
and you know what to do add forward slashes instead of dots.
Replace the dots that follow slashes.
One more to go.
Once we have that allocation context the second step is to get the bean context Daut get being it didn't
double corresponds to the big name which we have used in the conflict or someone the BEEN we are or
we care for is the be Will.
You can also call it.
RB will have used shortcuts for everything.
Use b will and assign it to Arda B or we can assign it to an interface when you send it to the implementation
runtime polymorphism again or to be able to control one do the typecasting add cost to our to be or
B or dot in the motard third place.
The
right click on that.
And then I will explain the flow Java application so spring does that dependency injection for us.
First it goes to the place Armstead which is printing.
Inside are the be all inside the place order we are in walking.
If you go to the implementation we are working to create order.
So first it prints inside our B.
Then the deal gets injected and Darby when police creator springe injects this implementation into the
bill right here and in our will impel.
This is where it goes.
It does the property injection and then we can use but the key is it is injecting any implementation
of this particular interface and this interface can hold any of its implementation.
That is runtime polymorphism.
That is the reason we are seeing.
If you go to our Robbie Williams Palafox we see this then it goes to the order to create order that
is the implementation which is printing inside Aradia will create order and real time applications.
This is where really how all the hibernate and Julie B.C code which you will see in sections later on
how successfully learned how to inject interfaces or how to do dependency injection through interfaces
which is very powerful and used in all real time applications.