In this lecture you will learn how spring provides loose coupling in our application through runtime
polymorphism.
That is we can inject different implementations of the dependencies at runtime without touching our
core or without changing our dependent classes.
Let's see that we are going to create another implementation of this order.
Deewar impled right click on this package see new class arder you impel to add and they should implement
the audio interface the same interface which the earlier class has implemented
doing this out in the implementation inside to be imported bous create Arta.
So our first of all maybe we wanted to use putting DBC or plain-Jane Ribisi but in here in order D or
in Perl do we might want to use Hibernate or putting data in advanced API.
That is the reason we have to be.
Once we have to be able impellor we need not touch the are the be all because here it's the interface
so go to conflict Bartik someone create another bean.
Copy this for us when the order Deeble been Bastet instead of our idea or impulse it'll be orderly or
impolite to and here call this DA or two.
And when we inject it into the bee will impel use the the word to reference instead of the all the name
remains the same because that is the name inside Arda we will impale right here.
And we inject it we are injecting a different bean.
Let's run the test not just in the test because we are reading the bill and calling the place are the
matter.
And this time the output it still works inside are the be will.
But if you see it says inside order it will embellish to create order or not inside the deal that we
created earlier that is the power of spring.
Spring will look at the configuration file it creates this dependency here.
But but when it does the injection it will inject the will to.
This is the loose coupling without making any changes to our dependant classes.
We can't simply come up with Exxon-Mobile configuration and inject new implementations of the same interface.