So far you have done dependency injection while using interfaces through some old configuration in this
and the next lecture you will learn how to do it using annotations and Auto-ID.
Let's get started.
The very first step as you know is to mark our classes with the component annotation.
That's true that at component from Spring Framework.
On RB William Bell and also are to be you impel that component.
And we are that spring knows that it can create or create these objects to detect we need to go to the
conflict for example get rid of all these beings here.
We don't need them or we can create another configuration file if we want to back this up.
It's up to you can text Kallen components can close this element right here and we need to provide the
base package for putting to search for classes to auto wire up to create instances and hardware grab
this package up to interfaces or to configure the example Bastet do a control shift to format Springville
search this package as well as a package if it has any.
And that's it.
But we haven't marked our will impact right here at auto wide say it that's on the test and see if it
works.
I click to run as a job application.
We have an exception.
It says no such bean no be named B will available.
That's because we haven't by default if you remember it was the camel case of the class here but in
our test we are using B all and you know how to change it on that component.
You can give it to name call it Bial save it on that best.
Again let's see if it looks this time and it does so it injects the will yet by creating an instance
of order D or impellor because I have marked only the order D-Will impled with the competent annotation.
It worked successfully because putting scans through this package and it knows only off this order be
impact the only implementation.
It thinks that the Ardeo implementation is the only class that implement this interface.
So spring is dynamically finding on the class but at least one class which injects or which implements
this particular interface it creates an object of the type that these market with the component annotation
and is injecting it.
Now Lexmark the second one are to deal with it component annotation as well.
CBOT on that test again let's see if it works this time.
And we get that exception that see what that exception is and we'll fix it in the next lecture.
It says unsatisfied dependency exception error creating been with named buil unsatisfied dependency
expecta no unique bean definition exception we have seen this earlier.
It says No uneek being because there are multiple bins which implement this particular interface.
If you go to the order d r r r b y and pulp this interface is implemented by both are simple as well
as order D-Will.
I am here too and spring does not know which implementation it should use in the configuration area.
We were using the exact name of the bin or that operands of the bin.
But here we have an early spring which being in Ottawa for the next lecture.
I will show you how to do that.