The PBS lecture we have seen know no Inuk been an exception because our interface was implemented by
multiple classes and putting good and figured out which implementation could inject.
So to avoid that problem first of all we need to give our beans means to go to order deal with impulse
give it that name is the name of the object reference or call it the label.
The first big name will be the table or the second one R D will embellish to the component give it a
value card.
Be able to once we do that come back to the Art of War impulse and then we are doing the auto wiring
use the qualifier within brackets.
You have done this earlier but that was with classes.
Now we are doing it with interfaces through interfaces qualify or be a will that will inject offspring
will inject this bean because that is the name we have used on the component right here.
Later on the test and see if the exception goes away.
This time it injects be able impulse and that is the reason we are seeing inside Aradia will create
art to go to the bee will impel one more time change it to be able to insert and they will see the power
of putting past and it injects Attardi impulse to this time.
So we are wired unique been not found exception.
We use the qualifier and on the component we go to all the implementations and name and spitting uses
that name and it creates the object and we use it inside the qualifier and we inject the dependency.