Welcome to the "Spring Framework in easy steps" course.
In this short lecture I will explain you how this course is organised, so that you can use it effectively.
This course is divided into sections, and each section has short and to the point lectures.
There will be quizzes at the end of each section for you to evaluate what you have learnt from that section.
Consider 70% as a good score on these quizzes.
I will also be adding several assignments which I suggest you work right away
as soon as you finish a section or a topic. The softwares that are required for this course are Java,
Apache Tomcat server, Eclipse IDE or an other IDE of your choice and the MySql database and workbench.
The setup of all these softwares is covered in easy steps in the very second section,
which I suggest you work on right away so that you will be ready when you reach the hands-on sections pretty soon.
At any point if you have any questions, you can post a question on Udemy or you can send me a personal message.
And I will respond to them, usually pretty quickly.
You will learn all the fundamentals of Spring and also advanced topics and build applications end to end.
But for that to really happen, you need to practise and work hands-on along with me.
Spring is huge, and when we build enterprise applications, we use parts of Spring framework.
I will be adding several new modules to the course on a continuous basis and also
I will be upgrading the existing ones as required.
Now get started, enjoy the course and remember,
that I am always here to listen to your feedback and respond to your questions.