Two masters java based configuration you are going to work on a very simple use case where-in you will creative
DAO class which is a data access class
it will not really talk to a database
in this case and a Service class , service class uses the
services provided by the dao class you will define a Java based configuration so we'll create a
spring config dot file within which you will define all your beans and then it will create a test
class that will read the beans from the container which is
Annotation config application context.
It will pass this spring conflict to this container.
It will create the beans.
Then it will read it
from your test class first will do it in steps.
First create the Tao.
Wire it using spring config that is the Java config and then test it out and then we'll create
the service class which will use the dao will wire service as well and then test that piece as well.