In this lecture you will create the maven project so that we can start working on our case.
So go to eclipse File menu new go to other and type in Maven select Maven project click on next next.
Again select the default which is archetype QuickStart is a standalone project.
Next again give it a name call it
spring Java config spring Java config finish that will create the Maven project for us.
Go into it
Go to the source test Java right click on the package get rid of it.
We don't need that.
We're going to update the pom in a second.
Go to the source.
Main Java.
Delete the app as well.
Open the pom file which is the maven configuration file go to to pom dot xml tab go to the spring core
Project.
The very first project that you have created.
Open the pom dot xml once it opens up to the last tab double click to maximize.
Copy all the way from properties till the end up to the build end not to the project element from properties
all the way to build come back to the new project spring Java conflict pom start from properties
and copy all the way up to dependencies control shift F to format
So we have copied a property called Spring version and the dependencies we need are spring core and
spring context.
That's all we need to develop standalone projects using Java configuration and we have the maven
compiler plugin defined so that our Java version is one point eight starting the next lecture you will be
using spring Java configuration.
But before we do that right click on the project and always do a maven update.
right click go to Maven and do a update project every time we touch the pom file we should do this and no more
errors.