In this lecture he will create the deal class and also Configurate using the spring configuration
or spring Java based configuration and in the next lecture will create the test and retrieve our dao
from the spring container.
Go back eclipse go to our newly created Project right click on the package name say new class call it DAO
Now let's keep it simple.
This dao will have one single method called create public void create it will not have any database calls
simply add a sysout.
Then double coats create it.
It's lying.
It's not really creating it add it component annotation.
This will be a spring component.
The second step is to create the java configuration.
It's very easy.
Again right on the package say new class call it spring conflict
finish.
We need to mark this class with a annotation called at configuration that tells the spring container
that this is this class is spring configuration and to configure our bean inside this configuration
will create them at their public it should return a dao  instance and you can call it Dao since it
returns a dao inside that method you simply return and new dao.
This is similar to how you configure a bean inside the application context dot xml or the config
dot xml which is the configuration file for spring
But you should mark this method with at bean annotation from Spring.
Hit control 1.
Imported from org spring framework context annotation configuration org spring framework  context
annotation bean when you Mark a method with these spring container we know that that particular method will
return spring bean instance.
So you have successfully created a class called dao and we have also created your first Java configuration
for spring and marking a class with at configuration and a method that returns the instance of the
dao.
and you have marked that method with
at bean annotation.