The next step is to create a test class that will use an annotation config application context which
is a standalone spring container that can read off a Java configuration to do that go to eclipse right click
create a class call it test with the main method finish.
Control the application context.
Context is equal to a new annotation
config application context.
You can either pass it as a constructor argument or you can use a Method called register to register
that configuration.
So here we have the spring config which is the configuration you can pass that right here.
spring config dot class if you have additional configurations you can use the context dot register is
the method and you can register as many configurations as you want but the register method is not available
on the application context.
It is a method specific to the annotation config application context so on the left hand side you should
have the annotation configure application context then you will be able to context dot register if you
want to and you can register as many Java configurations as you want which can return beans for us.
Next step will get the bean out of the context context.
DOT get bean passin the class name which is dao dot class.
hit control one assign statement to a new local variable and that will return the DAO bean for us
Do a sysout dao dot create the method and we want to see what the output of that will be
So create will be a void method so we don't how to use the sysout simply invoke dao dot create do
a control shift O to get there up get rid of the unused imports.
Right click run as Java application and you have successfully void a spring
Bean using Java configuration.
So the container is loaded.
you see here and it reads the Java configuration creates a spring Bean because this method is invoked
which is marked by at bean.
It has the bean created and in our test class we are retrieving it from the container using the Get
bean method and invoking the method on it.