This lecture you will work on the next layer which is the service layer, we'll create a service class that will
use the Dao by Auto wiring the dao onto it.
And then we will use it in the Test class.
go back to the project.
Right click on the package new class call
it service finish
this service is going to use the services provided by Dao  at Auto wired.
We want to.
auto wire.
This dao onto the service and within service will again have a method called public void safe which will
invoke the Dao dot create
go back to the spring config and we need to add one more method that will return the new bean public
service.
Service is the method name return new service.
Again this is similar to bean element in spring configuration if you are doing a xml based configuration.
This is like a bean element when you mark it  with at bean annotation.
If you don't mark it then it doesn't have any value.
Spring will not invoke this method it will not create a bean.
So this is important here.
Go back to the test instead of Dao dot class.
This time we are going to retrieve service class and on the left hand side it'll be service bean.
And it not be create, it will be save instead on the service it is called Save on the dao
It's called create rerun the test
and it still says it is created.
That is the method on the servies is invoked which is say which in turn invokes creates the container
starts
It will go to the configuration file.
It will create these two beans it knows that the service bean needs the dao bean so it will first create
the dao bean then it would inject that in because we have auto void that on to the service part of
it.
Then when we get that bean in the test class and invoke the method at the appropriate save method is called.