In real time applications we often spread our configuration across files that is we don't want to put
all the spring configuration in one single java file like this here because we'll be having multiple files
in the services layer and multiple beans in the dao layer when the application is huge.
So we want to move this Dao let's say to a new file called Dao Config right click new class Dao
config go back to the application config or the spring config copy this piece or it out
of it.
go back to the dao config paste it here.
Now we need to mark this particular java class with at configuration as well because this is also a spring
configuration.
Once we do that go back to the spring configuration and we can import and reuse that configuration here.
So you can mark use the at import annotation and you can import whatever configurations you want.
In this case it is dao config dot class and everything else should work as it is.
So we import the doa config configuration here.
The beans inside that particular configuration can be used within the spring config so the Dao will
be instantiated and that will be injected into the service and the services created.
So rerun the test
and it will still work.
So in this letter you have successfully learned that you can spread your java configuration across beans
and you can import those beans or import those configurations into other configurations by using the
at import annotation at the class level.