Everything that we do with xml based configuration can also be done with java configuration.
In this lecture you will learn how to configure the lifecycle callback methods for a spring bean using
Java configuration. To do that,
Go to the service dot Java and the life cycle methods which are in it and destroy public void init
Sys out within double coats init brackets.
Open and Close save it copy it paste it call it destroy.
You can call it Clean-Up if you want to or whatever.
We have the init and destroy methods now go to the spring conference which is the configuration where
we define the service instance on the bean annotation.
We have several attributes that can be used.
Open and close the bracket.
Hit control space.
There are init method destroy method and more select init method is equal to within double chords
specified the name of the init method which is init  comma.
destroy method is equal to destroy.
So the method names themselves could be anything.
Here we are using init and destroy because that is what we have on the service method.
He change this test to destroy the test rerun it right click run as java application and you
will see only init being called and then of course the created message that comes from Dao or save.
But the Destroy is not getting called that is because our program is being terminated and we haven't
closed the context properly so context dot close that will cause the spring container to shut down
properly and that should invoke the destroy method rerun the test one more time.
And this time you see in it Created and then when the spring container is shutting down it calls
the destroy method on our object as well.