You've already learned that by default all the spring beans are singleton that is spring only creates
one instance of any particular bean by default and you can change it using scope already tried all
that when you do Java configuration.
You can do that if you go to Spring config.
There is an annotation which is called which you can define right here at the bean level and annotation
is at scope and you can provide it a value within double quotes which could be a singleton prototype
exectra I want you to explore it and in the Test class create two instances or invoke the Get bean method
twice and check out the hash codes on those instances.
If you say dao dot hash code see the values a new singleton which is the default both the values
should be same when you create create two Dao's
both their hash codes should match when you use Prototype S-Corp then the values should be different.
You have already played around with scopes but this time it's going to be on this method using the at scope
annotation.