In this lecture I will interviews you do what it will be is it will be stands for Aspect Oriented Programming.
It is the process of applying services or external services such as transaction management or logging
security etc. to our application process without modifying the cord or methods in those classes.
These external services are also called cross-cutting concerns because they can be applied across the
Java e web application.
They could be a padded down layer.
So it a clear and UI layer for example logging whatever is happening in our application logging it to
a log file can be applied across these layers.
Transaction management typically is applied at the Soviet Gisli.
So these external services can be just plug them without changing any cord.
That process is called the Aspect Oriented Programming for example.
Here I have a business class called arder Sobeys immobile with two methods in place order and ship ATA
and the services that could be used by this could be transaction management Doughtery shipped.
We might want to send out an e-mail.
And also we want to log what are what is happening in our services class in Deuel log file.
All of these services can be simply used true aspect oriented programming.
So without modifying these methods here and the code inside them all these services like transaction
management send email and logging could be used by this Services class.
They can be applied to the services class using Aspect Oriented Programming.
To summarize Aspect Oriented Programming is a process off a plane services typically external services
to the classes.
In our application without changing the core inside them.