This is a very important lecture that you are going to learn.
The key terms in Aspect Oriented Programming I'm going to repeat a few of them so that you are going
to get them for sure.
Let's take a look at it.
By going through an example of order so simple.
Here we have the business class which has two methods placing and order of a customer and then shipping
the order to him this class and these matters here needs external services such as transactions sending
email once the order is shipped and also logging if an error occurs to a log file the number of them
that is used in Aspect Oriented Programming is an aspect and aspect is the class that presents external.
So we see this all these services need not be a part of one aspect.
They could be spread across aspects.
But it's important that you understand that an aspect is it plus that are.
External services.
Next is advice advice is a method defined inside the aspect class.
We can also call it as an implementation of an aspect that is one way of looking at it.
Next point cut point cut provides an expression language or it is an expression that we use to tell
which all methods in our application need advisers.
So a point cut determines which all matters in our application need advisers.
But a point that does not tell which Ed always is required by the political rhetoric simply says that
yes this method requires an advice because not all of them are not obligacion need advisers.
That is that joint point.
The fourth term comes in and the joint point is a combination of an advice and a point cut.
It will tell which business met their needs which advice next is Target.
The target is an object of the business class which needs advisors.
So this is the object to which all the Edwy this will be applied to
next an important term called weaving.
We have two more to go.
Sixth is weaving.
So here we have the target object in our application it could be any classes object which the class
aspect aspect.
So leaving is a process of mixing the advisors to the target object based on the joint points.
So weaving is a process of applying the advisors to the target objects methods using the join points
we co-joined point us which advise should be applied to which matter on this object.
Last but not the least proxy.
It is a class that is generated as a result of the grieving process.
It contains the business logic method as well as the advisor logic.
So it is a combination off their advice and the business logic within the class to which that is need
to be applied and weaving is done by special component Carlat we were.
So in this lecture we have learned someone important terms in aspect oriented programming that you need
to understand.
Number one is aspect it is a class that represents the external services.
Number two is advise.
It is a method defined inside the aspect class that needs to be applied to the business method later
on.
Next comes point a point cut is an expression that tells which business methods in our application needs
advices.
They join point as the name itself says Joines and advice and point cuts so that that advice can be
applied to that particular method.
Next is Target.
Target is the object of a particular class to which we want them to be applied.
Once a plain object goes through the viewing process the result will be a proxy object.
So this process is done using a joined point which deals which advise should be applied to which business
method the proxy is a combination of our business logic as well as the advise which could beat transaction
management logging security etc..