Using point Kurt expressions we qualify as business method.
In this lecture we learn the syntax to create point to expression.
We start a point guard expression with Materne name followed by the class followed by our package name.
So this is a complete qualifier to their name with the class name as well as the package name.
We can then use a return type of that method file or our access specifier and even types of parameters
that matter accept.
So the syntax here will qualify a pretty clear business Mathare in our application.
Through that point that expression for example here I have a wind code expression which qualifies a
method called my reply which should be in say the class called my class.
It's in a package is called combat but it's the return type should be integer access.
This fire is public and it should take two parameters of pipe integer.
Only then that method will be qualified.
And we use this particular point for the expression.
We can also use wild cards or special symbols you know wind current expressions star and dot dot two
dots start then used we can use it for access specifier.
They don't type packages.
Class name and method name as valid and we use the statics of wild card.
It means anything any math or name any class name any access specifier and need it don't type DOT DOT
can be used at two levels.
We can use it at Bakkies level when we use a dot dot at Bakkies level.
It means the current package and the snapback just as well.
And if we use dot dot at Mathare parameters level then that means any type of parameters it's always
remember Stata means anything dot dot means current package and sub packages.
And then we use dot dot format.
Pedometers in the point for the expression that means any type of parameters on any number of parameters
for example here is the first point for the expression that we are using wild card or the star Aztec
symbol.
This means any method in any class any package but its name should end of it Id get stocked with anything
because we have used Aztec's here.
But it should end with ID it's straight downpipes should be wired access specifiers public and pedometers.
It does not pick any parameters only such method will be qualified by this particular point.
The expression the next the method name should have a Caddick that E in it.
It can't start with anything and with anything that type should be integer access specifiers public
dot dot means any number of parameters and any types of parameters.
One more example.
Method name is get.
It should be Sacchi get no wildcard characters there are no special symbols.
Return type is in Dejah access specified is public in any type or in any number of parameters.
Stop start meaning any type any method name access specifier is public but no parameters.
And we have empty brackets that means no parameters.
The next one public wide get the type is wide METAR name it should be exactly get but it can pick any
type of parameters any number of barometers.
Here the method name could be anything that type should be in Dejah access specifiers public any number
of parameters.
Let's take a look at two more examples.
Here is a little more tricky because the package is applied here and we use the dot dot.
So the Materne name should start with get it can end with anything.
It should fall into any class because we now use it to start here.
So this method can be a part of any class in our application.
The Bakkies nime com dot dot dot.
Meaning all the classes under doc app and some packages qualify for this particular point or the expression
that it doesn't type could be anything accessed fistfight is public and no parameters.
If a method has parameters but everything else is same it will not qualify.
Shouldn't have parameters last public star star or dot dot meaning any method name any return type access
very public any type of any number of parameters.
It's a little tricky but as you work on the next few lectures hand-sewn and peyot a few of these you
will understand it.
To summarize it point that expression qualify as a business matter and the syntax for it.
Always remember it starts with them and their names start from the right.
With a fully qualified class and package name the return type the access specifier as well as the type
of parameters we can use wildcard characters or symbols such as asterisks and dot dot dot dot.
And we applied both at that level as well as method parameter Lebel.