In this lecture you are going to learn the important aspects the annotations that you are going to use
in the next few lectures to create and apply aspects.
The very first annotation is the aspect annotation which will be mocking our class with to make it class
an aspect.
We use this annotation on the class once we have aspect inside an aspect we'll have multiple methods
which will be our advisors will mock those advisors with different types of annotations such as ET before
and after after returning at around and after throwing each of these will provide a special meaning
to our advice or the method in our aspect and before we use this to mock him and that all that mattered
in that aspect will be applied before a particular business mid-thirties invoked an Paraguay's.
Any method that is modeled with it after that will be applied after it will declare a business mid-thirties
in walked after returning as the name itself says if we mock advise with this particular annotation
then that particular method will be applied just before the matter returns of value.
But we can access that return value inside our advice at our own.
If you Mocket particular advice with at owned then that advice will be applied before our business matter
is invoked as well as after our business method is invoked.
It's right around our business method.
Finally after throwing as you can guess if our business met throws an exception then this particular
advise will be applied.
Remember these annotations are not applied on our business metrics.
We are playing these annotations on the aspect classis we create and the methods inside them which are
our advisors.