In the next few lectures will work on a use case where it will create and apply your own aspects and
advice.
This will start by creating a spring.
It will be project update them have dependencies.
It will then create pujo or a service class starting with the interface then you implement that interface
with one single method called Multiply.
This will return the product of two given numbers.
Once you code that the next step is to create logging aspect the job of this aspect is to log a message
onto the console when the multiply method is invoked.
We want to log the details onto the console and we'll be doing that without touching the logic inside
the multiply method.
That is true Aspect Oriented Programming.
Once you have that aspect you will configure our beans and the aspect in the sporting configuration.
And finally you will create a best class Ronak and C it will be in action.