The second step is to create or application classes and interfaces which are product service and product
service impled with one single method called Multiply go to eclipse or to the source main Java and the
package composite spring spring it will be doing this class Abdur Java.
We don't need it.
Right click on the package saying new interface product service is the interface name finish maximize
how one single method that returns an integer int multiply in number one and number two
create a class that will implement this interface right.
Like new class product service in.
Click on the Add button.
Are the services the interface we want to implement.
Ok finish that block.
And this should return the product of these two numbers here.
Number one stop number two.
That's it.
So you have created the.
Those are the application interfaces and classes in the next lecture.
We will start implementing that aspect's.