In this lecture he will come up with the point Curt expression that will apply this advise to a particular
business method which in our case is the multi play method inside the product so we empower waterlogging
aspect.
Let's start with the ET before advice.
Within the double court's exit fusion is what we should use within brackets to this execution we come
up with our point cut expression always start with the method which is multiplied is our business method.
Open and close the brackets within the brackets to darte stood up as and any parameters any types of
parameters and any number of parameters.
And before that multiplied dot the class name which is product service am.
Then the Bakkies name separated by our dot product.
So we simple dropped the package name corporate comeback pasted before the dot ideaspace.
Next is the return type of this multiply.
I'm going to use this type of wild card that represents any return back.
That's it.
So how come up at that point the expression for multiply so that this particular advise will be applied
to that particular method here.
So copy that and use it in.
After that we're going to use the same exact point Curt expression.