In this lecture you will create this configuration file and it will be elements to it or the it will
be namespace to it and use that aspect the auto proxy element go to the spring quarter or any other
project you want and grab one of the configuration files.
Copy the conflict or text someone close it come back to spring.
It will be rightly consulate's main Java.
Create a new package.
Com dot dot dot spring dot spring it will be dot test finish based conflict direct sample inside that
open the Banfi guard ask someone get it off the beans.
Delete any beans in there.
Maximize we need to add that it will be namespace and a prefix forward.
So copy any one of these here start with.
I'm starting with the C schema.
Bastet it will be.
Is the prefix I want to use and the namespace schema slash.
A or B.
That is the namespace that I need to at the end and grabbing the context.
And the schema file for it.
Enter Bastet changing from schema I-Slash context through schema I-Slash it or.
The same namespace we have used here and for that namespace the schema file will be instead of context.
It Off context.
It will be spring.
Hyphen it will be not exist.
The so all the elements will be using be only using one element as of now that is from the schema and
that element is a or b is the prefix colon aspect G or proxy that will enable the annotation based
aspects for us.
So in this lecture we have successfully created a spring configuration file added.
It will be spring it will be named spaces and also use the IT WILL BE aspect the Arto proxy element
which will enable all the annotation based aspects for us.