The next step is to configure our beans and aspects in the building configuration file that is as simple
as defining the beans in here.
Start with the bean name or ID whatever name is equal to product service is the name.
Class is what you do with the natural course because the Taghreed that go to product service impulse
grab the package name come back based it within that double course year dot product service in camel
case.
We have defined our POJO.
The next step is to define our aspects as well as a bean bean name is equal to logging aspect.
Class is equal to go to the logging aspect grab the package name come back to conflict Bastet dot logging
aspect.
Close it.
So we're defining all the beans here Springle create the objects of these bins and at runtime it will
use these aspects and apply that advises as we have already configured the wind cuts in here.