The last and final step is to create a test class access the bean and see it will be in action.
So let's create the best glass or Eclipse or with a new package called spring or it will be our best
new class best class.
But the main matter finish the first step is to create the application context.
Context is equal to new class but ex-model application context Bassett the
by copying this Bakkies name pasted inside double chords change their door stoop forward slashes
and at the end slash conflict got maximal save it can Daut Get been passed that class or the name in
the conflict or some other B mean is product service
and this can be assigned to AB product service interface runtime polymorphism product service is equal
to that it controls one to import the product service control one again to do the type casting because
get beyond it and set object the last and final step is product service not multiply and pass to numbers
let's say four and five semi-colon control shift to format and we'll see the end to end flow in action
in the next lecture.