You have created a service class with a business method called Multiply created aspect which is a class
mocked it with the ET aspect annotation and to advise us inside it then use it to point that expression
to express that particular advice or to match that particular advice to a business matter.
So this blog before will be invoked just before business method is executed.
Which is my play in this case.
And this law after really being walked right after the matter is invoked it a lot of worry about the
method execution.
As soon as the multiply method is called log Okkervil be invoked.
So you can change it from after the method of execution to offer them at their invocation because it
will not wait for them at that execution to complete go to Best Before you run it and to sort this out
display the result.
Otherwise would not see the result on the council and close the bracketed and formatted on that based
on that explain the flow right click run as Java application and the output days before calling them
a third.
That is the first advice after them.
Third invocation.
That is the second log after advice which we have marked using it after annotation.
And finally there is Albee's displayed.
So the flow here the spring container.
Which is the classpath application context is loaded down and that is created it will use this configuration
file conflict direct someone within which we have the IT WILL BE aspect Jarkko proxy which tells spring
that we are doing the aspect Jey annotation based it will be hard to defined our Beanz the product service
as well as the logging aspect.
So spending will create instances of these beans in our test we are retrieving the bean and then we
are in walking the multiply method as soon as we do that the advisors will be applied by spring.
Using aspect J because we have used the point Curt expressions that will qualify the multiply motard
for these two advisors we have defined here.
That is why we have seen before calling them at their first then after them at their invocation.
And finally the result that comes back is being displayed.