In this lecture I'm going to very briefly introduce you to a.
I'm going to explain just that piece which is required for this course.
Remember that this is not a Jew equity course.
So J.A.G. is a javascript framework which makes the life offer quite easy to use javascript.
It isn't laya or javascript and everything in equity starts with a dollar symbol it hides a lot of things
that we could do in Javascript.
And it does the work for us automatically we simply use the dollar symbol and perform a lot of operations
for example.
To access a field called user id in HDMI within javascript core we might have to write this much but
using J.A.G. it becomes very simple dollar within Doublecross within braces use that poem and use that
ID and will be able to access the user id field.
This is a very small example there are many other things which we can do using J.A.G. in very simple
manner and to perform an AJAX call using J.A.G. again it simplifies a lot of things for us.
We need not use the javascript code and function calls.
We simply use the daughter symbol dot.
Ajax is the function and within which we give it you are l.
So what we will do for that particular request at a particular function for a particular task.
Basically what we want to do we have a model and then we provide the data that needs to be sent as a
part of that AJAX call.
This data is sent as key value pairs within braces.
This is also called Jason javascript object notation.
And finally the third and last parameter is success colon function which is right.
It is a callback function and the response comes back for this call and response comes back at some
point from the server.
This function will be called on whatever code you write inside it will be executed.
To summarize equity is an abstraction but what step it makes our life as it don't appear very easy to
use as easy syntax to use instead of better using the javascript syntax.
You can implement it using javascript and to make it Ajax call we need to pass in three parameters to
the Ajax caught in J.A.G. API.
You want to hit that data or to send that callback function which will be invoked when the response
comes back.