In the next few lectures you are going to use and make an object's call to the controller to do a validation
of this ID field.
Every time a user enters their ID and he moves to another next field.
Here we are going to validate to make sure that ID doesn't exist in the database already.
Are going to do that using two simple steps.
The first step is to create the backend cord.
There is the down layer which will check if there a card exists in the database with the given ID then
the Soviets layer then the controller.
This controller will be used or called Indu from the UI through an AJAX call.
We'll use the J.A.G. in our days page will include that library then we will handle the onchange event
in our days javascript core will make the AJAX call to the controller.
And finally will handle the response if the ID exists in the database then we will display the error
message.
If not we will not display any message to the end user.
That is the validation is successful.