In this lecture We'll work on the first step.
That is partially we'll implement that Dow method.
And so it's a Slayer method to fetch a user with a given ID.
So when a user enters ID here we are going to make a call to the server side.
So we need a method in the Dow that will dig that ID and check if our database record exists with that
given ID here.
So go to that Dow Plus in our application stop the server before you do that because it's going to reload
it every time we change and save something or do the user be able the new method will return a user
back.
It's called Find user on single user with that given ID integer ID or to use a Dow impel and implement
that he'd control one or the unimplemented amateurs.
They need that to do.
And you know how to load one single user if you remember from the Autumn section we use the hibernate
template.
Dot Net is the matter and you pass it the entity class and the ID
entity class is user got class and ID is what comes in as that parameter.
And our third has been implemented in the area.
Now go to the services layer use the service or do the interface user it returns a user back get user
is the method.
And it takes the picture ID.
The user service impulse control one of the unimplemented amateur's the lead the Tulu and return whatever
that doubt returns.
Dow d'arte find use it and pass in the ID.
Thats it.
So in this letter we have successfully implemented the dollar as well as the so we just need to find
Ifat use that exists in that database with a given ID in the next lecture we will implement the controller
method.