This lecture We'll wrap up our back end development by implementing the control of matter.
So we typically call this portion as the Bakken development and whatever we do on the white pages or
the page is just using javascript is called Frente in court.
We'll get to it once we wrap up the controller or go to eclipse user controller add a new method right
after get users start typing in public string miscall it up
public string.
Validate email is the matter on the controller map it at request mapping.
Is that iteration within brackets.
Map it to validate e-mail.
This is there you are.
Are you all right that we are going to use in our AJAX call later on.
Validate e-mail.
The logic here is going to be simple.
But first we need a request parameter that should come in which is the I.B..
So integer into the use their request Param annotation which you learned from spring NBC and we lose
the name as ID and here return we'll get some response for now return NULL.
Which means that in a second so we got the incoming parameters and we have also mapped the method to
where you are right.
The next step is to use the service
service Daut get user when we pass in the ID that comes in the request if that returns Eyrecourt control
one Assane statement to our new local variable user.
So hibernate if it finds a card with the given ID it will return that entity back.
If not it will return the null object or NULL.
So we are going to use user is not equal to null then we will send back one response.
Otherwise we are going to send the response so if the user is not equal to null that means the validation
has failed.
A user with the given ID already exists in the database so it should be displaying an error message
to the user create a message string a message that is equal to blank.
Nothing to start with do not have anything.
If the user is not equal to null message is equal to ID plus whatever came in the request plus error
message already exists.
And returned the message.
This is something new here.
Get rid of it.
You have been returning a view Buhl name back so far from the controller.
But here we are returning a message back.
It's not a view Meem So we need to do any additional step if we don't do that Springville think that
whatever we are running from here IIS view me and it will try to resolve it.
Well-spring that is not a new name and this is a response to the AJAX call we simply use another annotation
here wherever we specify that it downpipe just before that Al-Odah annotation called response Wardy.
I'm spitting hate control one imported from Spring Framework that HealthSpring that whatever we are
returning from this method should be used in response Wardy and no need to resolve Foret view name that
set we have successfully implemented the method in the controller will call this or will use this try
in the next call automatically This method will be invoked.
The ID will be passed in and this calls into the service to check if the user exists.
If they use that exists with that ID it returns this error message.
If not it will return a blank message and this response Bardy HealthSpring that whatever we are returning
is not a view but that the response that should go back in the response Bartie.