In this lecture we will implement the front end for our use case by following these simple steps.
First we'll go to our Facebook page and include the J.A.G. library so that we can use the equity in
our application to do that.
Go to clips go to the user rage darte dispute is under webapp.
Was the rage not be open that open up your Chrome web browser and Google for J.A.G. example J.A.G. example.
Click on any of the links I'm going to click on this very first link.
I'm W3 schools.
Scroll down click on any of these examples here.
We are not going to use the example code.
All we need is this clip block here.
What you see here.
Copy that and typescript.
BLOCK This is to include the J.A.G. library which is available at this help in our page.
Go back to Eclipse and it should be included inside the header block added after this matter.
Or you can also added after that title that you want but it should be within the header block.
So we have successfully included the Equity Library.
Next if you see here we create one more script block and start writing all over the J record inside
it.
So go back to eclipse create script block and within that script block it just query function or record.
Always starts with dollar symbol within brackets.
Document Daut ready Dotty's outside the brackets dot ready within brackets function.
So this is an anonymous function that we are creating when the document is loaded completely into the
web browser.
We want to execute the following anonymous function and within that function
Let's close this right here with the semi-colon and within that function we are going to check on Change
event or handle the onchange event for this particular field.
Here so everything in J.A.G. and nowadays even in normal Dallas script we don't deal with names of these
fields.
We should be able to hit Steimle field will have an ID ID is equal to ID.
In this case you can call it user ID as well but I'm going to use it as ID and will use this ID inside
the J equerry function dollar.
Is the syntax within the brackets within double chords hash ID.
That is how we can access a hasty field by using dollar for a query and within double quotes hash or
the poncey month and then followed by the hits DML fields ID Daut change.
I want to handle the onchange you in d'arte change within brackets.
Again function.
So everything in Javascript is a function.
And here we are providing anonymous functions and the document is loaded.
This is the function that should be executed within that function when on Change happens on a field
called ID.
We are creating another anonymous function starts there and ends right there with the Florida race and
a semicolon at the end.
So in this letter we have successfully used the J.A.G. library.
You have also handle the ready event when the document is loaded in the browser.
You said this is the function that should be executed and within that function we also handle the onchange
event for this ID field in the next lecture will start making the AJAX call by using dollar got Ajax
from Chiqui.