In this lecture you will make the AJAX call.
So we didn't function on change and the user moves from the here from when he changes to another field.
We want to handle that event that is exactly what we did here and within the Bartie use dollar d'arte
Ajax is the function name within J.A.G. that we can use to make it Zak's called open bracket.
And for Ajax as I said earlier we need to pass in three parameters within flower racquets this AJAX
call ends right here and a semi-colon and the ex-colonies you waddle
in you or at least if you remember from the controller validate email is that you will go back to use
a controller and the new method that you ought to have used that you or I use validate email that is
exactly what we should use in the user rage.
Daughter JCP That's number one second is data data and we need to provide the data that Windflower brackets.
Eat ID or you can call it id that is what we have mapped it to on the server side in the controller
using a request from the colon to get the value of this particular field here dynamically within javascript.
We need not to document target element and all that we can use the J.A.G. syntax dollar but then flower
brackets hash ID within double courts.
And outside of the of racket outside the dollar within brackets it's not allowed rackets dollar within
brackets use hash ID dot value.
So anytime you want X or Y to get Steimle field using the use daughter and it id using the pollen symbol
within double court and then you can either handle the events or get the value of it.
In this case we are getting the value and passing it to the server side using the AJAX call and this
value here is a function blows it right there karma.
Each of these should we be limited with a comma you all call our data comma.
The last one is success.
If it is successful call then we need to write a callback function for Jacques's this callback function
will be called when the response comes back from the server.
So a function always there will be a response.
We know that this function will return a response text so that should be included here and within the
body of that function we are going to court our logic will do that in the next lecture.
So so far you have handled the index events are how to handle the Dallas trip events for the ID field
and how made the AJAX call the next lecture will call this function which will display the error response
arm nothing to the end user.