In this lecture We'll wrap up our courting by displaying the message whatever comes back from the AJAX
call.
So go to the Ajax function and we need to display an error message right next to this ID field so we
can add s pan here Hatcham else pan and give it a unique ID IDs equal to within double chords.
E r r MSEE for error message.
We'll use that here will accept using J.A.G. dollar that in brackets double courts palm symbol passing
the 80 which is error message.
E r r capital M S G dot next we the same text.
It is the text function and pass in whatever response text comes back from the validation.
Initially it would be blank.
The span doesn't have anything.
We are dynamically assigning Whatever comes back in the response to it.
And also not just sending the text.
We also want to do a little more work on the UI if response text is not equal to blank.
Then I want the focus to be back on this particular field here.
So the user enters something.
He tab's over to name and the validation happens.
And if the validation feels I want the focus back to this particular field so that he can change it
to do that we can use the equity again dollar within brackets within double course hash.
The name of the field is ID
dot focus is the function and that will put the focus back on the ID field.
So we have successfully completed our courting of the front end as well.
We have done three things you know handle the document don't really change and made the ADX call and
we have provided a callback function within which you are taking the error message and displaying it
on to the UI by creating a hasty XML span.