This lecture with action and I will explain the flow and doing before we do that once more people here
here should be viral or not value the equity function to get the value of a particular field.
The following syntax Daut a valid function not value so get rid of the extra characters.
That and it should be fine.
Once you do that go to servers right click or restart because we have been making quite a few changes.
That's really what everything we're back to the browser.
That is how the registration page open.
If not launch a local host AUP spring NBC autumn registration page camel case is that the aren't that
friendship so that the new GSB gets lauded Let's take a look at the database to see what ideas we have
here or how.
1 2 and 7 8 9.
Let's create a new one.
Get it for our street name.
That's a Sherratt which is my brother's name.
Sharratt at gmail dot com.
Please go ahead and use your own sibling names here.
Submit and that creates a new record.
But that's not what we want.
Let's try using whatever is already there.
Let me use two or and immediately look at how fast it is that goes to the server it makes an AJAX call
goes to the controller controller calls the services layer services layer caused the Tao.
Tao uses hibernate makes a database called checks that there at a card already with ID too and it comes
back with the error message 2 already exists.
Let's change that and the focus if you saw the focus goes back to this field so we can edit it change
it to 5 Babbo work and that error message goes out.
Because the validation happens again.
This time it comes back with a blank message and we are displaying that blank here but you don't see
it on the UI because there is nothing to be displayed so we have successfully used Ajax with J.A.G.
and spring NBC which is used quite a bit in realtime applications.