These attacks and the equity section you have learned that Ajax stands for synchronous javascript and
XML.
It allows us to build responsive web sites by the end user to send in multiple requests instead of him
sending one single request and waiting for the response to come back.
It's engro less communication.
Second we have also learned that Jay queery is a javascript library that uses Javascript internally
but it provides abstraction and makes it easy for you I don't oppose to use javascript.
It provides easy to use syntax.
You have performed at Ajax call you it Ajax call into spring and we see the publication from the browser
using J.A.G. syntax $ Ajax.
It required three parameters are data namely you order of that.
So what are the application data that has to be sent to the.
So what.
And finally a callback function and the response comes back we need to provide a callback function that
will be invoked.
So how successfully performed FDX call using J.A.G. and spring NBC.