So far we have been using the ModelAndView object as a return type to the methods in our Controller.
This ModelAndView design is tightly coupled.
That is, in our Controller methods, even though we don't use the model or data
in some scenarios, we still have to create the ModelAndView object. That is why in later versions of
Spring they have introduced ModelMap and ViewName as a simple string.
So if you don't want to deal with data in a particular Controller method, then we need not create
the ModelAndView. We simply create the view name as a String, java string object and return it from the
method.
And if we have to deal with the model or data in the Controller method, then we will use the ModelMap
The ModelMap is like a map with key and value pairs.
The key is a string and the value is an object and it provides a method called addAttribute using which
we can add data to the ModelMap. A good scenario where we can consider this whole usecase is if we
go back to the user registration usecase, open the UserController and in the very first method, here
showRegistrationPage,
we do not have a model here.
All we are doing is taking the request from the user and sending him a view back.
Even then we are creating a ModelAndView and returning it. In the next lecture, we'll migrate, we'll
use the ModelMap and string in these two methods instead of using ModelAndView.