In this lecture, you are going to set up the employee table in the database that is required to work
on the spring JDBC usecase. To do that,
download the springjdbc.txt by going to the resources section of this lecture.
Open it up in your favorite text editor,
Notepad, Notepad++, Sublime text. Copy
these three lines and launch the MySQLWorkbench. Open a new query window or query tab by going to file menu,
new query tab. Paste the three commands. The first command in my case, my database name is mydb.
So change that to your database name,
your mySQL database name or if you are using Oracle then you would use a different client altogether or
command prompt.
Select that.
Execute it and it will go to my database mydb. Select the second command.
Here I am creating an employee table with three fields, id which is an integer, firstname which is
varchar and lastname which is varchar again. Select that whole thing execute it and that creates an
Employee table. Execute
the select query, select * from this table which I have just created.
Right now, it does not have any records. So you have successfully set up the employee table and in the next
few sections when you work on Spring ORM, Spring MVC ORM, you'll be doing something similar but
you'll be creating different tables like product, user, etc.