In this lecture, you will create a JDBC Maven project and update the pom.xml with the required dependencies.
The required dependencies are spring-core, spring-context to do dependency injection, spring-jdbc to
do database operations.
Finally the mysql-connector jar which is the driver, JDBC driver to connect and work with mysql
database.
Let's get started by going to Eclipse IDE. File menu,
New -> Maven project. If you don't see this option go to other and you will find it. Click on maven project,
next, leave the default as it is. You should choose maven-archetype-quickstart. Next.
The Group Id is fine. Enter an artifact id which is our project name.
springjdbc is the name, springjdbc, all lowecase.
Finish and we have our project. Open the pom.xml which is the maven configuration. Click on
pom tab, which is the last tab here.
Open up any of the earlier poms. Go to springadvanced, springcoreadvanced, open the pom.xml, maximize.
Copy all the way from properties to the end except for the project closing tag, copy up to build closing.
Control+c, come to the new product's pom.xml. Start from properties, go all the way till
end of dependencies.
Delete it and paste whatever you
have copied. Do a control+shift+f to format. We have defined property for the version of Spring.
We have the two core dependencies, spring-core and spring-context to do dependency injection and
we also have the maven-compiler-plugin and we are telling maven to use 1.8 version of Java.
All that is left is spring-jdbc dependency and the mysql-connector driver.
So let's get them from the internet.
Open up your web browser, search for spring
jdbc maven dependency. spring jdbc maven dependency, click on the very first link which says
maven repository. And if you go back and check we have been using 4.3.6.
Go to your pom.xml. 4.3.6.RELEASE is the version.
So let's grab that version by clicking on this here.
Scroll down. As soon as you click here
this will be copied to the clipboard. So go back to Eclipse, paste that new dependency inside the dependency
section.
Do a control+shift+f.
Delete this link by hitting control+d.
Copy this version from here, $. We don't want to hardcode that. So paste the dollar,
the property, this property is
defined right here.
And the last dependency is the sql connector,
mysql-connector. So go to Google one more time, search for mysql connector maven dependency.
Mysql connector maven dependency, click on the very first link,
and 5.1.6 is the latest.
Click on the text area here, that gets copied.
Go back to Eclipse.
Add it at the end of the dependences. Control+shift+f to format.
Delete that link.
Delete any spaces. Control+shift+f to format.
This we'll leave it as it is because you will be using this version only here. 5.1.6 is only
for this connector. Since we have deleted the JUnit,
let's get rid of this package here.
We don't need any tests.
Delete, hit OK.
And also delete this app.java or you can do it as a part of the next lecture.
It's up to you.
Anytime we change the pom.xml, we need to right click on the project, go to run as, sorry, go to
Maven and do a update project.
Click OK. Maven will pull all the dependencies and build our project or atleast make sure that our project
has everything.
So we have successfully created the springJDBC project, added
the dependencies we need. In the next lecture,
you can start using the JDBCTemplate to execute database operations.