In the next few lectures he will learn how easy it is to perform database operations using spring JTB
CPP template.
He will do it in two simple steps.
The first step is to configure the driver manager data source and The Daily Beast template.
In this configuration there man is a data source will be used by JTB template.
So you'll first inject this being or you will first create this being or configured.
This being in the Phoring can pick the example by setting for properties.
The class name you want to connect to the database the user name to the database and finally the password.
In my case I'm using the Skrill driver so it would be my column brought my escarole dart the DBC Daut
driver and this is that you are a that we need to connect to the my Escorial DBI running on my machine.
My DB is the name of the database local host windes to my machine.
And here we have the protocol SoBo protocol.
The user name is routine in my case and the password is best.
Once we can figure out the driver manager data source the next bin is the GBC template will configure
that bin by injecting the data source that recreate in the previous to these two and going to this same
spring configuration file as two different beings.
There really is a template depends on our manager data that is step number one.
And the second step of course is create the best class and use the GBC template to perform it insert
operation or any other update operation on the database.