In this lecture you will walk on the very first step which is to create the configuration file and create
the driver manager data source and Daily Beast template beings go to eclipse grab the configuration
file from Springwater advanced or two source mean Java.
Pick it from any of the packages those that come back pasted on this package.
Get rid of this app Dardar we don't need it.
We're going to create a test class later on.
OK open the configured example.
Maximize it.
Delete everything inside it.
All the bins.
All we need is the root bean tag.
It has the required namespace just like the schema except to get started with the B in the very first
bin we want to create is the driver manager data source.
We don't have the package name of it so we can either google for it or another way is to do it control
shift be eclipse and search for driver manager data source.
So Eclipse can search for it on the classpath and if you click that double click it to open it opens
a decompilers that dark place file and opens it.
In your case if it doesn't decompile at least open up as you read it can see the class name the package
name etc..
So scroll up all the way up and you can grab the Bakkies name from the control see come back to the
configured Sammul bean CLOS is equal to within the courts bath the package back scroll down and get
that last name which is driver manager data source.
This way we can ensure that we are using the right package in place name we can't remember the entire
package so we know how to google for it or use Control shift B and then search for de-worm manager datasource
in Eclipse.
Give it a name you can give it water what name you want.
That's called Data capital source to inject the form properties.
Let's use the schema.
That is the easiest way to do it.
Driver class name is the first one so the colon Raber class name is equal to within the court.
For my Escuela it is com Daut might as well start JTB see Dorte braver.
That is the name of the driver last name of the driver.
Next is be call.
You are all small by the class name has case sees capital and in its capital you Oreille all small is
equal to.
But then of course the Ribisi call an
my you is this a protocol call in to forward slashes local host slash.
My database name is my baby.
You have control f to format so that it goes to the next line.
Next property call in user name.
All small is equal to root is the user and the last property peacoat and password all small again is
required to within double courts.
Best we can close that been Dagget idea can't you if you have to format and we have the data source
bin.
Next we can create the dependent which depends on this data source that is the database the template
being class is equal to.
We know the class name it is the BBC template but we don't know the package.
So the best thing to do.
Control shift be.
Search for JTB see template open that up scroll up all the way up grab the Bakkies name it's our Spring
Framework.
Julie B.C dark gone come back.
Bastet dot JEDEC template.
So JS capital B B C small template.
So it is a common case that name is equal to the Ribisi B Gabbidon template.
And the only property we need to inject into Edgerly we see a template is this data source.
Let's use the schema again.
The colon you know how to do that to do as reference will get the name of it.
So the name of the datasource property inside the government as a data source.
If you go here or inside Ribisi template go to a very basic template search for a control f data source.
Keep searching for the property and the property name is datasource.
If you see it here.
So we got to use the same exact property name we open that declaration it is sitting it right here so
go back to the configuration Piccola data source hyphen ref because it is a reference type you the name
which is datasource.
Copy that pasted right here and you can close the bean bag right here.
You don't need the ending element to a control shift to format.
So we have successfully completed the first step that is configuring their data source being the driver
manager data source and also the database template.