In this lecture you will create the test class and we insert a card into our database table that is
the Employee table which doesn't have any records.
Currently if we exclude the SAT ACT right now it doesn't break down any ID cards.
So let's insert a card by using the basic template in our best plus create a new test last night on
the package new class based with the main Mathare finish by now you know each and every step to create
a test class application context.
Context is equal to a new class but some model application context has in the configuration conflict
darte example the package from here based the package slash If you want to I wired this package thing
you can copy the config file directly under the SLC folder.
In that case we need not you the entire package you know that from spring core use forward slash.
But since we are creating so many config files we better keep them under package just under one.
Add the import for application context.
You can also call this DBI context or beby conflict dot.
If you want to do context Daut get B in the B name.
If you remember is JTB template.
The capital Ribisi template semi-colon.
Control one assign statement be a local variable that will make it the object change to JTB see it control
space for template from Spring Framework.
Select that one again add cost to get EBC template been.
Call it Ribisi template.
Now we have the Daily Beast template we can use the update operation that are overloaded wash and software
update and we are going to use one that big sequel and variable arguments pass in the sequel.
You can create a string sequel spritely string Escurial is equal to insert within double court insert
into the table name which is employee values.
If you go to the table its employees small and we have three fields Id first name and last name employee.
All small values within brackets question mark comma question mark comma question mark.
Close the double quotes so I am not providing the values here.
If you know the Daily Beast prepared statement.
This question marks are placeholders and will provide the values here so pass in the Escuela to the
update method as the first parameter and the next three arguments are the values which will be replacing
the question marks.
So the first value is the ID.
Let's say the here in argument one is diety.
Or you can create a new bigger one diety.
That's the first argument.
Comma part is the first name you can use your first name and sort of part and last name is period.
I'm passing in three parameters which will be used by spring to replace these three question marks when
it prepares the prepared statement and it's and this update.
It returns the integer value back which tells us the number of cards that got inserted or updated or
deleted.
End result is equal to that 6 out
number of records inserted our colon space plus the result and that's it.
And third shift to format right click on and see job allocation and the inserted number of girds inserted.
Are 1 go to the database
the select one more time and you see that data 1 but not in the period.
I will explain the flow in that next lecture.