In this lecture explain the flaw of what exactly happened and we ran our best and successfully inserted
a card into the database when we ran our test the configuration file is lorded by the spinning container.
It reads our on for example in which we have two bins.
The first one is the datasource been.
So the second one is The Daily Beast template.
Been putting notes that the Daily Beast template needs the datasource being so it will create that dependency
and well creating it.
It provides the form properties the driver class name the user name and password the datasource Bean
is the one which creates the connection internally.
The Daily Beast template will use the data source to create a connection create a statement and it is
responsible for executing that insert statement as well.
So internally spring Daily Beast template will take care of collection creation creating the statement
and executing it.
And at the end it uses the integer result and we can do whatever we want to do with that result.
That is the beauty of using the basic template.
Without writing all the Breillat plate calling it which we do enjoy Ribisi we can simply execute sequel's
statement.