The previous lectures you have used the J.D. template and inserted the card into that database in simple
steps in this and the next few lectures we are going to make our application look more real time more
like a real time application.
By following simple steps first will create the Employee class which will have three fields.
These are simple being which represents our database table employee database table with the first name
and last name.
We call it D.
It carries the data.
We can also call it an entity.
Once we have that entity we'll create a diesel interface which is implemented by the class in real time
obligations be able as a pattern be able stands for data access object.
We put all the database code inside the class.
This class will use the Daily Beast template to perform the database operations and we are going to
wire this very basic template with employee door impellor that is we are going to inject it into the
employee Dow impulse and you already know that the template uses that data source.
We have already wired these stupe.
Now we are going to wire the database a template into the employee document and will test the employee
Dow impellor then start off that actually using the Ribisi template in our test.
That could be more real time.
So lets get started by creating this deal and this does and will do the injection in the next lecture.
Go to eclipse right click on the source package we are going to create it in a new Bakkies new class.
DD always the first one employee and we'll put it inside a package called Spring duty got employed dot
D D.
You can either call a deal or you can call again NDP.
Typically we use entities that term into the other package entity and we are working with autem tools
like Hibernate finish and the data that carries its weight in ID.
But I weighed in first name by weight in our sorry strength
last name.
Also this is also staring back at the end gender getters and setters right click go to source gendered
getters and setters to select all hate ok and don't shift effort to format these fills up until X..
Move them up there.
That is where they belong.
Gendered that boosting matter by going to source generate to string it ok.
Shift to format we have the Deeble this will carry that data for us.
Next create Berdahl interface be able interface new interface employee be a fool and they should go
in to employee dot Deeble package finish.
Let's start with one single mother to insert a card into the database and create
and this will the employee object.
So whatever data we provide to it through the employee control one import employee will retrieve that
data inside the Create implementation and will send it in the insert or update operation create an implementation
class for this.
I click Create new class Employee B.
I am all for implementation.
The package will be com dot dot dot employee Dot be able dot 8 MP for implementation we put the implementation
classes in a different package finish and they should implement
employee d all developments the employee idea or head control one and an implementation methods and
how one single mother will implement this method in the next lecture.
So in this lecture you have started making our application look like a more realtime application by
creating employee DDR which holds the data then the employee interface and finally the employee will
class the or impellor Plus.