In this lecture will vie The Daily Beast template into them play the away and use it in the create method
to insert the card into the database that gets started by creating a new field called wait Judy we see
it control space template Spring Framework oller GBC template
create a room set amateurs it control one create getter and setter it OK to a control shift to format
and we can use it inside the create matter.
Now you already know that Korti how written it in the Test class.
But in this case we are not going to use their application context in their Dalrymple's we simply use
the Daily Beast template radically.
And then in the next lecture we will configure it.
We are doing it the other way around said go to imply dhal impulse.
Use the JTB see template dark update the access string and object parameters.
You know that sequel grab the sequel from best class copy this statement come back to the Dalrymple
inside the third string.
Scale is equal to insert into employee and the values with three placeholders.
We'll use that as well.
And the argument this time instead of hard coding them we lose it from the employee don't get AB is
the first one employee darte get first name is the second parameter employee don't get the last name
is the last and third parameter.
And this returns an integer result get control 1 signed statement to a new local variable call it result
and return that result instead of the zero delete any blank lines of to format in this lecture you have
successfully implemented the create method by using the BBC template.
Well why are they still the basic template.
In the next lecture in the conflict got eczema.
And also will create the best class.