The previous lecture we have either a field called Julie B template which the employee of the wimple
used in the create method we have underwired that though using spring.
So we need to do that in this lecture will create a configuration file and also copy or the test and
we'll work on the test in the next lecture.
Right click on the door package see new package.
The mother doll and another employee will create a package card.
Best finish is where we'll put our configuration and the test.
So grab the best and the config from our earlier work based on the test package open the conflict and
we'll work on the best in the next lecture configured example.
We already have the JD b c template or the data source and The Daily Beast the template being defined
here.
Now if you remember our use case we know how to configure the employee will simple which uses the very
basic template.
So let's create a new bean class is equal to grab the class name.
We need to inject the employee or impled not the interface.
We learned it earlier and it worked with injection of interfaces copy the package name come back to
configure based or class dot or the package go back grab the class name which is the employee the impulse
come back Bastet space name is equal to give it a name call it employee be able to close the bean tag
and within the being that we'll use property injection.
So a property name is equal to DBC template.
That is the field which we have defined in the doll symbol right here.
That is the field name laws it use ref element and being is equal to the name of the bean which is EBC
template which is defined right here.
So copy that and based on Baulch f format and we are all set in the next lecture we'll create a test
class and test this employee in.