This lecture We'll update our test class Open the best darned Java under-employed test package.
Let's fix the package names etc..
Befre spinning JEDEC dot employee or forward slash employees less desk to copy that forward slash or
dot add a forward slash that will do and this time we are not going to read J.D. B.S. template.
We are reading the employee be able.
That is the name of the bean which we have configured in the conflict for example will read that Dow
type cast it into employee be able we can use the interface because that interface is implemented by
them Pleydell impelled.
Get rid of these two lines here.
End result is equal to call this the Will not that there really is a template.
Be able darte create.
We need to pass in a new employee.
So create that here New Employee object semi-colon control.
One important employee set up this new employee control one extract to local variable.
Eclipse will do it for us.
We know we need to add some data into this object employed dart set.
ID is the first one ID is to send in Digest or get it off double quotes you have value of do we already
have a field in the database with ID of one.
So lets start with two and Dot set.
First name is equal to John employee got lost or said last name is equal to for gusano.
One of my colleagues John Ferguson capital save it use whatever names you want.
You need not use sophisticated names if you feel that this sets up a stick and the control shift or
to organize or import.
So in this lecture you have successfully created the test class with the right package names for the
configured example.
Then when you read the bean which is employed from the spring container and how in walked the create
method by passing it the Employee object instead of simply passing values.
We are getting the result and we are displaying the result.
Let's run it right click run as Java application and everything is wired and access number of records
inserted are one.
Go to the database on my siecle workbench on the set.
One more time and we see two records.
Now the next lecture will explain the flow and trend.