In this lecture I will explain the flow end to end and summarize what you have achieved in the last
few lectures and we ran best.
The spring has always it's the configuration file and in the configuration file you can find three bins.
The first being is the employee be able implementation.
This Been needs the daily the template being to work so the container will then tried to create the
DBC template bin and The Daily Beast template depends on datasource.
So this being container will look for the data source bin.
It will find it here.
It will create an instance of it by using the information we have already provided here.
Then it indexed that datasource into the database template and it uses the database a template object
to inject it into the employee or Imbolc while creating an object off the employee impellor and then
we are creating employee BP or setting the data in to it and we are invoking the create method on the
Dow being which we are reading from spring and in the create matter.
We are using this very basic template which we have injected in the configuration.
Exclude the update method which makes the sequel and the 3 values for which we have placeholders here.
The question marks.
So spring will replace them.
Here is the update and we saw the result already.
So this is a pattern which we typically follow in real time applications instead of a test.
Plus we would inject this Deewar in our business object plus the next layer class in Java the application.