This lecture he will implement the update method in our employee.
He will be using a query like this update employee set the first name to a placeholder.
We are going to provide that value.
Last name Zeke will the question mark where given the burglar Id say you're going to update the first
name and last name given Id do that go to eclipse.
Open up the employee walk first the interface create a new method int update give an employee object.
We are going to update it
to the implementation and by da Imphal hit Control 1.
Add and implemented amateur's.
Now that we have everything in place it's going to be very easy cut it pasted right next to create that
shift after format.
The only piece that will change here is instead of insert We are going to use an update and we pass
the parameters differently get rid of everything in the double quotes Abbate employee is the table set
first name all lowercase is equal to a question mark comma last name is equal to.
Question mark.
There IAB is equal to question mark.
So we have use of placeholders for the values will set those values when we invoke the update matter.
JTB see template d'arte update.
We lose the same one which we have used for insert string sequel and the second is variable arguments
passing arguments the first placeholder is the employee got get first name come up for the second placeholder
employee not get the last name and for the last placeholder the ID that ID is equal to a question mark.
Employee Daut get ID ones that executes it will return the integer result get control one end statement
to a new local variable.
Call it result and return that result.
Until you do format and we have successfully implemented the subject matter.
Now go to the test.
Plus comment out this create fortune where we are invoking create and use int.
The result is equal to be able dot update and pass in the employee.
Let's change the jaunt to that say Bob Ferguson in the database if you exclude the sequel right now
if we exclude the select query we have two records.
The second one is John Ferguson.
Once we run our test it should be updated to Bob Ferguson the first name should change to Bob here.
Let's see if that happens by running our test
and access number of cards inserted.
So let's change that.
It should be number of cards updated.
Let's go check the database to see the result.
Run the query and it got changed.
Bob.