In this lecture you implement the delete method by using the following query.
We want to delete a card from the Employee table give an.
Let's do that
go to the interface first employee.
Now in Dejah delete in this case we only need the ID we don't need the complete Employee object or employed.
Embattled head control one are unimplemented amateurs to caught up in Eclipse you can select the core
all the art button on your keyboard and press the up arrow and that will move the complete code up and
control shift to format control be to delete the truth.
And in here you can grab these three lines from here paste it in delete.
Change the query can we delete delete from employee.
That is equal to a question mark and we pass in the ID here.
Sequel is fine and we only need one parameter in this case which is ID.
That's is pretty simple.
We got the query and we are using the ID and we will update metheglin variable arguments and we are
returning the result to test comment or the update portion.
And end result is equal to Dow d'arte delete.
Passing the ID one.
Let's delete my data card which is buried in the database.
Go to sequela bench execute the query.
Regards Bharathi probably has an eighty one that's come back from the test and here before we do that
number of the cards there should be there next run the best and it stays number off the guards delete
it off of one.
Let's make sure it is good to select and we have only one record which is Bob Fogelson.