So far you have learned how to execute the non-selling statements using the GBC template that is they
insert a update and delete in this and the next few lectures you use the Daily Beast template and execute
the Select queries using two methods it provides one query for object which returns a single record
and query method which returns multiple records from the database table.
The query for object X the sequel as string.
The second parameter is a new type called Roll mapper which you will learn in a second and then the
variable arguments.
The second method is the method which takes only two arguments string sequel.
Their school statement the select statement and then the road map and it returns a list of objects not
just a single object like for object.
That brings us to a new type called Rule mapper.
Romancer is an interface in the Spring Framework which we need to implement it maps a daily B.C resultset
that comes back in do an object of a class that we create in our application.
Here is the room Appert architecture from our application we execute a select query using the very basic
template against a database.
We get all our rows back as a result set.
Then we use the road map or we create a roadmap or by implementing this rule mapper interface and our
class will or write a method within which will map the result set in object.
So all that will do in the map roll method that we implement the map room at is from the roadmap an
interface we or I that we implement it and all that matter does is it gets the result out of the resultset
and we set it into our object in here I am reading the result from the results and setting it into the
object Karg employ.
To summarize the exiguous select statements we use the query for object.
If it is a single record that we want our query if we want multiple records both these matters take
a roadmap for the job of the roadmap or it's an interface in the Spring Framework will create a class
that implements this interface within which we all read the map room or for that matter we simply map
from resultset to the object of our own in our application.