In this lecture you will implement a method that will lead a single employee from the database table
to do that go to the employee interface and the matter will return.
Employee object and you can call it read pass it single value called integer ID.
So give an employee ID.
It should read the employee record one single record from the database go to the employee now impled
it control one and implemented amateur's the end on Thursday and start implementing them.
Third we need to use the GBC template d'arte exit qued are not ready for object.
There are several or loaded versions and the version we are going to use will take that string as a
roadmap.
And also we can pass variable arguments.
Let me call it up.
And also more this method.
Up next to delete Jerry B.C template doc query for object is the matter.
Create the sequel string.
A school is equal to select star from employee.
Their ID is equal to question mark you can have multiple conditions here is equal the question mark
and x are you going to have a complicated select query and you can pass variable arguments here.
But in this case we have only one argument one placeholder and that is coming in as the parameter so
passing that ID the next key step is to add a semicolon here and the next step is to implement the roadmap
or interface.
We don't have a roadmap for it so let's create a road map for class right click on this employee door
package see new class give it a name employee role map up and the package is changed to dot dot roll
map or add a new package.
Karl Rove mapper we can put all our own mappers here.
Click on.
I hired this room apper needs to implement the all mapa interface from not Jow I start swinging.
Please don't sell like this.
You should select it from ARG dot Spring Framework.
Ok finish
and it didn't implement all that mattered because we need to select that generic type here.
If you remove the generic type by default a role mapper will use object as the type selects provider
type.
We know that type with this employee we want this room roadmap to return the employee now hit Control
one.
Let's import this employee control one on the road map or add unimplemented amateur's and the only method
on the employee row mapper are the interface is the map row that gets the result set as well as the
row number it tells us which row is being currently processed.
We don't need it as of now.
We only need the result set.
It will do the remapping in the next lecture.