This lecture Cherryville implement the Map Room mattered the days you are going to read from the resultset
in Walk the letters on the resultset and I will set the values by creating an employee object.
So let's get started by creating it Employee object employee.
MP is it called the new employee
MP Daut set.
Let's start with the IB r s dot.
Get in.
The ID is of type integer Bhasin the column index it starts with one.
We know that the first column in the database is the ID that is the reason we are using one and setting
it into MP Daut set the next ENP darte set.
First name ORUs d'arte get to column 2.
It should be get screened get x x x Smethurst based on the paper we pass and string in double.
Except for bits of type string.
Finally employed Daut set last name to start get screened again for the last name and the index's 3
and return that employ.
That's it.
It's that simple to implement the map roll mattered.
Spring will give us the resultset at runtime.
We are getting the results out of the results that creating an object of our own type and returning
it in the next lecture.
You will create the test and see it in action.