The last step is to use the employee roadmap or in our dollar impel.
Update our test and test it to use the roadmap or you can create an instance of it right here employee
role map to correlate road map is equal to new employee roadmap to big that object and pass it here.
Control shift to format and that should return employees so you can take the results that are coming
from here.
It control one and sign statement to any local variable.
And that will return Employee object because we are passing aerial map of pipe which should have done
and applied.
So we are returning it back at the return statement return.
Employee
So here once again the reason we see an employee coming back from for object is because the road map
or type that we have implemented is for the employee genetic backup.
Let's upgrade the test go to test comment board the delete portion
Dow dart read and pass in and let's pass.
Let's check the database to see what it has right now.
All it has is one row with ID 2.
Let's use that to is the ID.
It controls one to and the statement to a new local variable.
Call that employee.
That's the result we are getting back.
Display the results change this text to employee record Seybert.
We already have an employee created up here for updates and leads you can comment out that portion.
We don't need the Employee object in this case or comment out portion as well.
Right click on that test as job application and we see the employee at a car coming back and the details
are being printed.
So the flow is the container creates all the beans.
Then when we invoke this reed matter in the employee of Ambuhl The Daily Beast it complex query for
object will be invoked.
The sequel will be passed in along with the roadmap that will be passed so the statement will be executed
against the database result set comes back JTB said as an asset is what comes back to spring.
Spring Springville use the roadmap that we have provided by invoking the map third it passes in that
is all set.
It gets Employee object back because that is what we are doing inside that matter and it will return
it back to the employee Dol impellor.