The previous lecture you have learned how to read a single record from that database and this lecture
will create a method that will read all the employer cards before we do that let's insert record manually
because we all have to come in discord if you want to exclude the insert You are welcome to do that
but I'm going to set the record manually from my skill work bench insert into employee values within
brackets 1 within single quotes that you can use your first name and last name.
You need not use.
Witnessing And of course the period the
execute and that the traditions are dead a card in the database do a select and we have to record snow
parrot and Bob go back to eclipse or to imply Dao create a new method that will return a list of employees
read.
That's it.
That's the name of the matter.
You can also call it find if you want to.
Until one imported from Java I doubt it or be employed.
Simple go all the way up until one the unimplemented matters that really are the read method.
At the end that wrap that matter come back up Bastet here do a control shift F. mix it up so that you
can see it.
Delete the.
String skill is equal to select star from employee you have to write a query that will get as multiple
records from the database you can have a WHERE clause.
But typically that Burtless should return multiple records
JT B.C template Daut query.
That said we are going to use the query which will take the school and the road map or school comma
row mapper which we need to create.
So grab this roadmap or from up here.
Pastrycook pass that road map are to this method.
Can control one at the start of the line sign statement to a new local variable.
Select that and that will return a list of employees.
Since we are passing aero mapper which returns employee requirement that automatically returns a list
of employees.
We can return that list call it result and return that list go to test instead of invoking the read
method comment that line out and invoke the word dot.
Read an old one and sign statement to a new local variable.
Call it result
display the result.
We can also use a foreach loop.
Let's run this first reichlich run as Java application and that will display all the employees like
this.
You can also use it for each.
I read through the list and display each record as you want.
Let me maximize this or that you can see it clearly we have Beauregard's Bob Ferguson.
And at the period the rate works when we run this test you know what happens it goes to the Dow in the
Dow.
Daily Beast the template directory will fetch at resultset with multiple cards and Springville call
this employee roadmap.
This map room a third for each card in the reserve set.
And this matter Rattansi and play object for every red card in that database or every card in that is
an asset.
And finally we get results liftoff results back Springville the list of employees and we are returning
it which we are displaying in the desk plus.