Know that you know how to use the GBC template to perform cad operations against a database in this
lecture you will learn how to auto wire this very basic template.
If we go to the employee we're impelled we haven't wired it but instead we have used the configuration
to inject the database the template into the employee.
So let's get rid of this we not defined the been here the lead the Dow impled been from the configuration
go to the employee down in pulp the very first step to start using annotations is to mark our Been with
that component annotation from Spring.
Do that.
This tells spring that this class an object of this class can be created the next annotation is at Arto
wired and spring will automatically inject it provided we enable annotations as well as contex type
1 component scan in the conflict Daut example where they're added right at the beginning you can add
it in context.
I found a colon component hyphen can provide the base package which is the Dow impels package.
We should provide the implementation package not the interfaces package.
They are different now.
It's a border configured based package you can PLO's this element right here we control shift to format
a rerun that best.
That is an exception.
Let's see what the problem is no such being employed now available.
That's because in the past we are trying to read the bean as employee doll.
But if you remember by default spring will create the class using the class name or create the object
using the class name.
So let's provide the name here within brackets.
Employee.
Now that is what we are using in our best employee be able.
So once you give it you will create the being with that name and it should be available.
And this time it works successfully.
So in this letter you have successfully Ottaway or the daily busy template or by mocking our POJO with
that component annotation use of that word annotation on the BBC template.
And in the config you have provided the base package for the container to scan by using the context
colon components can.