In this lecture I will summarize what you have learned from the spring.
Julie B.C section the spring JEDEC takes care of all the repetitive chord that we typically write when
we directly use the jelly B.C API in our applications.
It also takes care of the checked exceptions that we need to handle when we use the daily API.
We simply use their daily B.S. template by defining it in the spring configuration.
And it depends on the data source which takes care of the connection creation the data source requires
a driver class name in order to connect to the data source a user name for the data source or the database.
And finally the password to connect to the database so the data source object is created by the spring
and then it inject it into the database template.
Once we have a template in our application process we can perform the DML operations that is insert
update delete using the update method on the very busy template and pass it as well.
And we can perform the Select queries if we are cutting for one single row one single object we can
use the query for object.
And if we are retrieving multiple rows from the database we use the query method.