Do work on the spring duty B.S. assignment will how to create a table called passenger in the database
which will how three fields IAB first name and last name will use the database a template and perform
the following four operations.
Create the read update and delete all the crowd operations while performing greed.
You will be using the rule mapper and you will be converting the data that comes back into air passenger
Jaba object.
So you will need to create a class car passenger with these three fields and a road map or inside of
a road mapper.
It will be reading these three fields and displaying them and you write their test class.
So once you create the table the steps will be configuring the Julie B.C.E. template and datasource
in the spring configuration and then you will write a test class in which it will read the Daily Beast
template bean and perform the correct operations.
As I said you will how to create a passenger class so that the data can be read back in Java object
when you do the read operation.
You will provide a real mapper so that the data can be converted.