In this lecture, you will learn what constructor injection is and start using it.
Spring supports creating objects using parameterized constructs. To specify one argument to a constructor,
to create an object using a constructor with parameters,
we use the constructor-arg XML element. Within that, we can either pass primitive types as value, we can pass collections
using list, set, etc; which you have already used when you worked with setter injection.
And also you can pass reference types using the ref element. Both these elements value and ref can
be used as elements, as attributes and also you can use something called C schema or C namespace. This is very
similar to P schema or namespace which you have used in property injection.
So let's get started and use constructor injection. By going to eclipse, right click, create a new package.
com.bharath.spring.springcore.constructorinjection. Instead of dependency check,
this will be a new package called constructorinjection, finish.
And grab a couple of beans.
Go to the inner beans package,
grab this employee and address.
We are going to reuse these two. We'll write the configuration and test from scratch. Come back to the
new package,
paste them.
We are going to inject employee or create the employee bean using constructor injection. And the address,
we can inject it using property injection. So we can mix and match as well. You can use both property injection
as well as constructor injection within the same XML. Copy over the config.xml, paste it.
Delete the bean.
Start off with the bean.
The first bean is the dependency, which is the address.
So let's get started with the address.
Employee uses address or it depends on address. Start with address, class is equal to, go
grab the package name,
up to constructorinjection, come back to confif, paste it, dot, close the bean element right there. And
use P schema to inject elements required for our address, which in this case is house number, street
and city. Let's use P schema. We are still doing property injection here.
p:hno="123", space, p: the second field is city, or street and then
city. p:street="mira mesa" p:city="san diego".
The second bean is the employee bean.
class="employee", paste
the package, dot, give it a name. We haven't given a name to the address
bean. Give it a name, name="employee",
we'll use this name later in our test.
Close the bean bag right there. And within the body of the bean, we are going to use constructor.
So before we do that, go to the employee, get rid of all the setter methods or you can leave them there.
But we are not going to do setter injection.
Define a constructor, Employee()
the default constructor.
But now we are going to add parameters to it.
Employee(int id,Address address) two parameters.
this.id = id; this.address = address;
Go back to the config.xml. Start using the constructor injection.
constructor-arg is the element. Within that,
the first parameter that we want to pass in to the constructor is id field.
So use,  pass in 123 for id.
The second argument, another constructor-arg, use an other constructor-arg.
This will be ref, because we want to pass in an object or inject an object.
close it there. The name of the bean will be address. We've already created the dependency
Control+shift+f to format. And you have successfully configured constructor injection. In the next lecture, we'll write
the test case and I'll explain it end to end.