In this lecture, we'll create the test class and see the constructor injection in action.
So get started by right clicking on the new package, Class, Test with s main method, finish.
You can copy over the prior tests if you want to, but I'm going to type.
ApplicationContext context = new ClassPathXmlApplicationContext("");
Pass in the config.xml.
Grab the package name so that it will find the conflig.xml under the appropriate folders
on the classpath. Forward slash, change all the dots to forward slashes.
Two more. Hit control+1 on ApplicationContext. Spell it correctly, ApplicationContext. Control+1, import it
from Spring.
context.getBean(); read the bean.
That's the second step, so that we can use it.
The bean is employee in the config.xml, that is the name of our main bean, Employee.
Employee e is equal to, typecast it because it is an object
sysout, e. Do a control+shift+f to format. Run the test, right
click, Run as -> Java Application. That runs and prints the employee details for us along with the address
that we have configured.
House number is 123,
Street is mira mesa and city is san diego.
So we have successfully used constructor injection.
And if you see, we have mixed both property as well as constructor injection here. The address itself
we have used P schema. That is, using setter injection we have injected the values into address. And then, when we created
the employee, the spring container, we configured it to create the employee using the constructor injection.