As I have said in the constructor injection introduction, everything that we do in property injection
can also be done in constructor injection.
That is, we can use this value as an element which we have already done or we can use it as an attribute.
On the constructor-arg element, value is equal to, within double quotes, 123.
And then, we can get rid of all this xml and close the constructor-arg right there. Save it.
Similarly, the reference can also be used as an element or as an attribute on the constructor-arg element.
ref="address".
Get rid of the constructor-arg, closing and the ref tag. And close the constructor-arg right there.
So our xml becomes simpler. Save it, re-run the test.
And we should still see the same output coming back.
The third one is using C-reference or C schema.
You already used P reference on P schema or P namespace. With constructor injection,
we can use the C schema or C namespace which will make our xml even more compact.
So start using it.
Copy this P namespace here and the prefix. Enter, paste it and change p to c.
We need the c schema namespace from Spring because the attributes that we use will be from this namespace.
And here, where we are doing constructor injection,
we can say c:, use the field name which is id="123".
c:, for passing reference or for injecting reference,
very similar to how we used it in p:,
we need to specify the name of the field which is address.
address:ref="address". Then we can close that bean bag right there.
So the c schema makes our xml very compact just like the p schema and p namespace.
Save it, re-run the test, and it should still work as expected,
and as how it was working earlier.
So in this lecture, you have learnt three things using value as tag and attribute with constructor injection
using reference as tag and reference and also using C schema or C namespace to make it compact.