In this lecture, you will learn the ambiguity problem with constructor injection.
You will do that by creating a class called addition and constructors with different types of parameters
and see how the spring container invokes those constructors. Right click, new -> class. Call it Addition. We'll
not be performing any operations, we'll simply create constructors with some system.out.println
statements.
com.bharath.springcore.constructorinjection.ambiguity. Finish.
Create the first constructor, Addition(int a,int b) two integer values.
System.out.println("Inside constructor INT")
Just to differentiate it from other constructs that we create,
we are saying "Inside constructor INT". Create another constructor, copy and paste this, double.
And change this to double as well in the sysout. Save it, create the config file, you can grab it from earlier
lectures.
Copy that.
Paste it on the package. Expand it, close everything else. Open the config.xml. Lets delete everything,
all the beans and create the beans from scratch.
bean class="Addition" name="addition"
Its class, copy the package name.
Paste it, dot, close it there. Inside the bean tag
we are going to use constructor injection. constructor and pass in a value to it.
We can use the value as an attribute as well. So use it right here.
value="10" and close the constructor-arg right there. Get rid of this. Copy it.
The second argument is 20.
And that's it.
Let's use the integer constructor. These two values here are integers. Grab the test class from any of
your earlier packages. Paste it, open the test class. We are not going to rewrite it. Simply change,
make changes to it. Addition is our class and the name of the bean,
is also addition. springcore, copy the package, constructorinjection.ambiguity. After springcore,
it's not dependencycheck.
Change the dot to forward slash. ambiguity/config.xml and change the name of it,
name of the variable to addition.
Go to Addition.
We don't have any,
what we want to see,
is these getting printed and not
any variables. So simply reading the bean will do, because it's going to invoke the constructor and one
of these should be printed.
So run the test. Right click, run as -> Java application. And it says Inside constructor INT,
which is okay.
That's expected.
That's what we wanted.
We passed in two integer values.
So spring should invoke the constructor that takes integer values.
Now let's switch the order of these constructors.
Double comes first and then the int constructor. Save it. Rerun the test and you will see that it invokes
the double constructor.
Let's see how the problem becomes even more complex.
Copy paste the constructor one more time. At the end of it,
String, String.
I'm adding a method that string and inside constructor string type.
Save it.
Run it again. And this time, instead of invoking the double constructor or the int constructor, it
invokes the string constructor. It says Inside constructor String.
So this is the ambiguity problem.
I'll explain why it is happening,
why spring container is behaving this way and how to fix it in the next lecture.