In the previous lecture, you have seen the ambiguity problem. That is, we have defined three constructors and
spring was invoking these constructors in a random fashion.
Although we have defined integers as constructor arguments, it was invoking the string constructor.
And if there was no string constructor, it was invoking the double constructor.
It's not random behavior.
It is expected behavior.
Let me explain what is happening. In the config.xml, by default spring considers these values
we provide as strings. And then, based on the method arguments
here or the constructor arguments it will convert them into the appropriate type using the parseInt,
parseDouble methods. But the container behavior is like this.
The reason the ambiguity problem is happening is because the container will try to match the given parameters
and see if there is a constructor which takes the string arguments to start with.
If there is one, it will use it and it will not invoke any other constructors.
That is the reason why we saw that Spring container was invoking the constructor that takes string arguments
when there is one.
If there is no constructor with string arguments, then it will match any other methods in the order in
which we define those methods.
Here in our case we have two methods. One that takes double arguments and the other one that takes integer
arguments. So the values we provided, 10 and 20 are also accepted as double values.
That is the reason Spring goes and searches.
If I get rid of this string method, the Spring container, if you run the test again,
it will search in the class for methods that can accept those values and the first method it finds is the one
with double arguments.
That is the reason it invokes this method, which is exactly what happened. That is the reason it never
invokes the method that takes integer values.
This problem, this ambiguity problem can be fixed
by using three different attributes that are available on the constructor-arg, starting with type, index
and name.
Let's look at type in this lecture.
Go to eclipse, go to config.xml.
These are attributes on the constructor-arg.
Type can be used to specify what type of arguments we want to match.
type="int", type="int".
The second parameter is also int. Run the test this time. And this time it invokes the Inside the constructor int.
Let's put the string method back as well. Save it.
Now we have three methods, although the order, first double comes then
the string. Let's run the test again and see the output.
It doesn't invoke
the string method or the string constructor anymore because we have used the type attribute and we are
telling the spring container that it should match a method which takes two arguments of type int and
int. So we can avoid ambiguity problem to a level using the type attribute.