In the previous two lectures, we've seen what the constructor injection ambiguity problem is and fixed it. In this lecture, you
will see an other variation of this problem and learn how to address it. Go to the Addition.java,
get rid of these two methods here and change the constructor to accept one integer type as parameter
and one double type.
And here we can simply say, Inside the Constructor.
There is only one constructor. Go to config.xml and invoke that constructor. The first type is
integer, 10 is fine.
The second type here is 20.
But let's reverse that and see what happens.
10.23 or first
let's see the valid case, 10 and 20.3.
Save it, change this type to double.
Run the test.
And it works as expected,
no issues there.
Now go back to the config.xml and switch these two. Move it up.
Control+x, move it to the top.
So we have reversed the order.
Double comes first and then the integer.
But in Addition.java, its
integer first and then double. Rerun the test, and it still works without any issues.
This is an other variation of the issue because we might not want, although it would have injected if
you do sysouts in here.
sysout, let's print the values of a and b. Run the test again to see the values.
So it has injected 10 into a, which is correct, and 20.3 into b, which is also correct.
But we do not want this behavior in our application, because we want the order to be correct.
We don't want to accidentally change the order. If we don't want to do it,
then you can use an other attribute called index. The index starts from zero and it goes all the way
up to how many number of parameters we have minus one.
The index of integer is zero, and the index of double is one.
Now run the program, and it runs and it injects 10 into
a and
20.3 into b. If I try to switch this index, lets try switching it, 1 and 0.
Run the test,
and we'll see an exception.
Let's maximize it and it says error creating addition bean, Ambiguous argument, constructor
argument 0, values for parameter of type int.
So for type int, we are trying to pass in type double.
That is the reason it has failed.
So using the index, we can avoid such problems.
Change it back to 1 and 0 to ensure that the order is correct, re-run the test. So in this lecture, you have learnt
how to use the index on the constructor argument to make sure that we are passing the arguments in the
right order.