To quickly recap what you have learnt from the constructor injection section, the Spring container uses a parameterized
constructor instead of using the setter methods, when we ask it to use the constructor injection.
And we do that using the constructor-arg element inside the bean element.
We use multiple constructor arguments depending on the number of parameters we have on our class' constructor.
We can inject primitive types, collections as well as objects using the constructor-arg and the Spring
container will invoke the appropriate constructor based on the number of arguments we provide here, in the
bean tag.
You have also learnt about the ambiguity problem that can happen because of the types of constructor arguments
we pass in.
And to avoid that ambiguity problem,
we can use the type attribute, index attribute as well as the name attribute on this constructor-arg
element. Using the type, we can specify the exact datatype of the parameter on the construct parameter
we define in that class. Using index, we can specify the order in which the constructor argument should be
mapped to the constructor method in a class.
And finally, using the name we can specify which parameter name a particular constructor argument, that
we define in the xml should be mapped when a object is created.
This name, is the name of the parameter of the constructor method that we define inside a class.