Spring provides two life cycle methods to every bean it creates.
They are the init method and the destroy method.
The names need not be the same but the signature should be exactly the same it should be public void
and no parameters.
Any initialization code such as loading some configuration file from the file system or connecting to
the database or connecting to a web service or a server can go into the  init method
We put that code inside the init method and all the cleanup code that is closing the connections or cleaning
up all the objects should go into the destroy method.
The lifecycle looks as follows given a spring bean and xml configuration to the spring container the
spring container will first instantiate an object of the bean.
It will then set all the values onto that object.
Then it will invoke the init method whatever code we put into the init method will be executed at that
point.
After the data is set into the object.
Then we read the bean make use of that bean in our application and once we are done and before the container
is destroyed or object is destroyed the destroy method  will be invoked before the destruction of the object
the destroy method will be invoked and we put all the cleanup code inside the destroy method and then
spring will destroy that object if we are aware of servlets  then you know the init and destroy method in
servlet,
these are very similar but what you need to remember is that the init method is called after the object
is instantiated and all the properties are set on to the object that is all the dependencies are injected.
After that the init method is invoked and just before the object is destroyed the destroy method is
invoked.
You can configure the lifecycle methods in three ways using xml configuration using or implementing
some sring interfaces.
our bean classes will implement these interfaces and override some methods
And finally a simple way by using annotations.
You are going to explore all these three handson in the next few lectures.