In this and the next lecture you will learn how to configure the spring life cycle methods that is the init
and destroy methods using xml configuration.
We'll do that in three simple steps which you already know will create a spring bean called patient.
will use the xml configuration to configure the init and destroy methods and finally
will write a test.
Let's get started.
go do eclipse
New Class call it patient package com dot bharath dot under spring core
Let's create a package called LC for life cycle dot xml config
They're going to implement lifecycle using xml config finish.
double click to maximize this patient will have only one field.
Int ID patient ID make it private control one create getters and setters methods
next is to create the configuration so you can grab the configuration from ref types config dot xml
come back paste it open it clean up all the beans and start using the bean tag to instantiate
or create an object of type bean class is equal to patient.
Grab the package name in a second go to patient copy the package name come back paste it dot give it a name
name is equal to the patient.
Lets call it patient use the P schema P colon the name of the field is ID ID is equal to assign a number
lets say 1 2 3 close the element right there.
So so far we have instantiated the bean and done the injection of one and only one field we haven't
used the init and destroy methods yet to use the init and destroy
We need to go back to patient create a init method should start with public the return type should
be void
the name of the method need not be init.
It can be anything.
Let's say high.
No parameters within the body.
add a sysout
inside hi method.
So this is our init method it's going to act as our init method also code the destroy method
public.
void no return type instead of destroy.
I'm going to call it bye the name can be anything.
No parameters sys out
inside bye method.
save it so we have two methods which will act as init and destroy.
Now we need to configure them in the config dot xml will go back to the bean element to configure
the init method.
We use an attribute called init.
Hypen method is equal to.
within double coats we need to provide the name of the method  just the name which is hi and for destroy
as you can guess destroy hyphen method is equal to within double quotes bye save it and that's it
you can create our test class can grab the test class from the ref types.
Copy that.
Paste it here open it.
We need to change the packages.
The class names etc. instead of student it will be patient.
That's the bean that's going to come out of spring container change this name to patient as well.
Instead of ref types it's springcore core colon or forward slash RC slash xml config that is
the package name.
And then the config dot xml changed this name to patient the variable name should be patient.
We haven't implemented  tostring method on patient.
We can do that.
Go to patient go to source generate tostring go back to source.
I just need the tostring method.
hit OK.
control shift F to format lets run our test so successfully you have configured the init and destroy methods
which are hi and bye let's run that test and see the output
run as java application.
There is an exception.
Let's see what it is
it could not find the Config dot xml com bharath spring spring core RC xml config
Let's check the package if it's correct.
It's LC not RC So go back to the test and change it from RC to LC for lifecycle.
Run the test again.
This time we will see that it says inside hi and then it prints the patient object.
So before the object itself is injected as soon as the object is created and once the setter methods
are invoked the init method is invoked. So to prove that this hi method is being invoked after the setter methods are called
go to patient and inside the setter method for ID right here add a sysout
sysout inside the setter method save it come back run the test again.
So spring creates the object called the setter methods and then invokes the init method
And then it creates the rest of the object.
But one thing you notice is that our destroy method is not invoked yet this here inside bye method
is not being printed.
There is a reason for it.
We need to enable something in spring.
We need to enable a hook in spring for the destroy method to be invoked.
We will see that in the next lecture.
So to summarize we have done a lot in this lecture we have created a patient object you have created a
couple of methods which will act as init and then destroy and in the config dot xml when you create that bean
using the bean element we have also configured the init and destroy methods using init method and destroy
method attributes have successfully created a test and seen it all in action except for the destroy
not being called that which you will fix in the next lecture.