The previous lecture you have successfully configured and seen the init method in action the result
object was instantiated the setter methods were invoked and then our init method which is the high method was invoked
then we have used the object
but at the end the destroy method or the bye method on the patient wasn't invoked.
So in this lecture you will see why that is the reason that the bye method was not invoked all though we
configured it and the config dot xml
is that the spring container before it shuts down.
We need to tell it that it needs to invoke the destroy method
we need to configure or register a pre destruction hook or pre shutdown hook.
We do that programmatically in our test dot java
on the context we need to tell the container or we need to enable a pre destruction hook
before the container gets destroyed.
We should it should also invoke the destroy methods
That is exactly what we are going to tell the container.
We do that using the context but the application context class does not have the registration method to configure
the pre shutdown hook we need to do it on the abstract application context is a parent class of application
context abstract.
So you need to abstract at the beginning.
hit control one to import that from Spring Framework do a control shift O to organize the imports.
Now context dot register.
Shut down.
Hook.
So this is a method that we need to invoke on the abstract application context which tells the spring
container that it needs to invoke the destroy methods
we are enabling that feature
Run the test again.
And this time we will see that it goes inside the by method as well.
So the setters get invoked after the object creation it goes into the init method
We use the object in our program as we need it.
In this case we are simply displaying the details.
Then it also invokes the destroy method
And from that bye method we are getting this text which sits inside the bye method.