This lecture you will learn how to configure the spring life cycle methods using spring interfaces.
So far you have done it using spring configuration.
Now you're going to do it using spring interfaces you're going to reuse these three classes from this
package by creating a new package.
So right click on this folder or package say new package instead of xml config
Change it to interfaces.
We are going to use the spring interfaces to implement the lifecycle methods copy these three from
xml config package paste it expand open those three patient
dot java or pojo the test dot java will remain the same no matter whether it is xml config or
using interfaces we are not going to change anything here.
Goto patient dot Java and we are going to implement implements initializing bean control one import
initializing bean from spring or dot string framework dot beans dot factory that is the package for it
control one had control one and implemented amateur's the very first method is after property set
is amateur's in this interface we need.
All right.
This is the init method public void
No parameters
the method name is after properties or set.
This method will be invoked sysout within double coats.
Inside after properties set save it the next interface for the destruction or the destroy method is
comma after initializing bean we need to implement  disposable
bean disposable bean from Spring Framework import that it's from the same package control one
control one again to implement the methods
go to the end just scroll it down and you see the destroy method. The destroy method
the name is also destroy
do a sysout double coats inside destroy and in the config dot xml we don't need these
two the init method
And destroy method
Because we are already implementing those interfaces.
We only configure the bean in the config dot xml spring will automatically see that this bean is implementing
these two interfaces from spring and it will invoke the after property set and destroy methods. In the
test
We still need this register shutdown hook.
This tells the container that before the container is shut down it needs to use this hook which will
invoke the destroy methods lets run  the test right click change the configuration instead of xml
config
The conflict is now under spring core LC hype forward slash interfaces.
That is the package name we have used LC dot interfaces that becomes LC forward slash interfaces
right click run as Java application inside the setter method there is a class cast exception.
We should go back to the test
We need to change this
patient here
should be patient from patient dot java but in the config dot xml we need to change the package name this
here should not be xml config
This should be interface's as well.
So we are trying to cast one type of patient to another type or class type that is the reason we are
seeing that exceptions are changed to interface's rerun the test.
Now we will see that it creates the object invokes the setter methods then it invokes the after property
set method which is the init method
then we use the object and then the destroy gets called.
So in this lecture you  we have successfully learned how to configure it and estimators by implementing initialising
being disposable bean and by operating the after property set then that's try methods.