In this lecture you will learn the last and final way to configure the spring life cycle methods.
That is using annotations to do that.
Let's create a new package.
Right click on interface's package say new package.
Change it from interfaces to annotations.
We're going to use the spring annotation support copy all the patient dot java test  dot java and Config
dot xml
paste it on annotations package close everything in Eclipse.
to avoid confusion and open everything from under the annotations package patient dot  Java test dot Java and
config dot xml go to patient Java patient will not implement the spring interfaces any more.
Do a control shift O to organize the imports delete after property set and destroy methods  do a control
shift F
we are going to use the hi and bye methods but this time instead of configuring it in the config
dot xml using init and destroy attributes.
Here we use annotations right above the hi methods we use a forced construct from javaX dot annotation.
This will mark the hi method as the init method.
So this method should be public void hi without any parameters.
The name of the method could be anything.
Similarly the destroy method should be marked with predestroy before the object is destroyed this bye
method should be invoked.
This annotation is also from javax dot annotation. Go to test
and you know what changes you need to do.
Change the package from interfaces to annotations
save it go to config  dot xml even in here.
We need to change it from interfaces to annotations.
The package name for patient.
Otherwise we'll see a class cast exception, run the test
Right click run as a java application.
And in the output you don't see the init and destroy methods being called you only see that it goes
inside the setters and then we use the object and display it.
The reason is by default in spring all the annotation support is disabled.
We need to enable it using the configuration.
There are a couple of ways to do it.
we will learn one of the ways in this lecture.
The first way is to enable just these two annotations.
The predestroy and post construct support in spring.
The second way is to enable support for all the annotations.
So first you are going to learn how to enable the support for just the post construction predestroy annotations
for the life cycle methods, we do that by defining a bean element.
Class is equal to common annotation bean post processor.
So to get it go to your test class and start typing in common annotation control space.
It's common annotation bean post-procesor select that and Spring will import the whole class for you
copy that from the import including the package.
Go to the config dot xml and define a bean with that class bean class is equal to within double
quotes.
paste that entire thing.
No need to give it a name.
Close the bean tag and that's it.
Once you create an instance of it automatically spring will enable the support for life cycle annotations
the post construct and pre-destroy again
The name of that bean is common annotation bean post-processor come back to test get  rid of this,
You don't need it do  a control shift O to remove the  unwanted imports rerun the test again,
And this time you will see that it goes inside the hi method as well as inside the bye method.
In this lecture you have learned that you can use the post construct and predestroy annotations to
configure in it and destroy methods and to enable annotation support these for just these two annotations
you need to create
a spring bean called common annotation bean post processor for the spring framework.