In the previous lecture you have enabled support for these two antotations the life cycle annotations by configuring
a bean called common annotation been post-process in the configuration file.
There is also a way to configure all the annotations support in spring.
We do that using the context namespace or an element from the context namespace in spring which is defined
here.
Here is the namespace prefix called context.
And this is the schema for it and the name of the element is this the recommended way and the most
used way and most of the realtime applications context colon annotation config.
Thats it you can close that element right here and we don't need this bean anymore because we are asking
springe to enable annotation support for all the annotations although we only use two annotations right
now post construct and pre-destroy run the test again.
And the output inside the setter method
Inside the hi method we use the object
And finally inside the Bye method.
So in this lecture you have successfully learnt how to enable annotation support in spring for all the annotations
using context namespace and an element called annotation hyphen config.