The spring  container provides two life cycle methods for every object that it creates.
And we can implement these lifecycle methods in our classes.
And then the spring container will invoke them the init  method just after the object creation
And the destroy method just before the object is cleaned up or destroyed. There are three different
ways in which we can configure and use these methods using xml configuration where in on the bean element
when we define a bean using the bean element.
We use the init method attribute and specify which method in our class needs to be the init method.
Similarly destroy-method attribute can be used on the bean element to specify a clean up method.
So usually we put all the initialization could be database connections could be connecting to a web
service.
All that will go into the init method.
And the destroy method will have the cleanup code will be closing the connections cleaning up the files
etc. so using xml configuration we can use init hyphen method and destroy hypen method
The method names can be anything they need not be init and destroy second method is to use annotations.
We can use the at postconstruct and predestroy
We use these annotations on our classes init and destroy methods
again the names need not be the same.
The last and final ways to use the spring interfaces namely initialising bean and disposable bean
our class will implement these interfaces and override the methods in those interfaces and those
methods will become our init and destroy.
We have also learned that when we use annotations by default in spring annotations support is disabled
to enable it.
We use context colon annotation config
First configure the context namespace  in your XML configuration and use this one single line which will enable
the annotations.