In this lecture, you will see how simpler the code will become
once we start using the ModelMap and string to return a ViewName instead of ModelAndView. To do that, go
to the UserController,
the usecase that we have worked on earlier, that is the user registration usecase. Open up the UserController,
the very first method, all it does is return a view back but it is creating a ModelAndView object to
do that.
Let's change that to string. Get rid of the first two lines and simply return, within double quotes, userReg,
r capital, that's that. We need not create a ModelAndView object at all.
So that's simple.
Now the code is much better and cleaner.
The second method takes a model attribute, that is whatever comes from the HTML form. Again it creates
a ModelAndView.
So get rid of ModelAndView. Instead return the view first. Within double quotes,
regResult is the view. Change the return type to string.
So we are done with the view portion.
Now for the model portion, we need to use the ModelMap. We need to define the ModelMap as a parameter.
ModelMap from spring, call it model.
model.addAttribute, use that method.
Whatever you are adding here to the ModelAndView, do that on the ModelMap.
User comma user.
Format it.
Get rid of the ModelAndView, we don't need it anymore.
Now the code is much simpler and cleaner because we don't use ModelMap. Do a control+shift+o to organize
the imports, control+shift+o. Let's rerun the application and see if everything works as expected.
Right click, run as -> run on server, finish.
My Tomcat is not running, so it will start it.
If you have it up on running it will restart it.
The very first page is the registration page.
So copy that URL, come to spring MVC, paste it, Enter. So it goes to the first page, the first method
has worked.
You have simply returned a string as a view and the Spring container has sent it to that particular
view.
Go back, give it an id 123, Bharath, bharath@gmail.com. Submit and the second method
works as well,
just like how it was working before but the code is now much simpler and cleaner.