Spring MVC is one of the most used web frameworks in the Java EE space.
It uses three different patterns namely the FrontController, HandlerMapper and ViewResolver to implement
the MVC framework.
When a request comes in from the end client, it first reaches the FrontController which is a dispatcher
servlet that we'll configure in the web.xml of our application.
This dispatcher-servlet will then forward this request to a HandlerMapper. The HandlerMapper is responsible
for mapping the incoming request to a Controller class that we create.
We mark these classes with @Controller annotations. The HandlerMapper uses the URL in the
request and it maps it to the appropriate Controller. When we define a Controller,
we also do the RequestMapping on the methods inside that Controller.
The Controller handles the request, takes the appropriate action
and finally at the end it returns a ModelAndView. Model represents the data and view represents the
next UI to which the response should be sent.
The Controller returns ModelAndView back to the FrontController which is our dispatcher-servlet.
The dispatcher-servlet will then invoke the ViewResolver which is the component which is responsible
for adding a location and the extension for the view that the Controller returns. Once the FrontController
has the complete view,
it will generate that view and send the response back to the end client.
And to exchange data from the Controller to the UI we use the ModelAndView object and to get the
data from the UI to the Controller
we use @ModelAttribute. Whatever form data comes in, automatically that will be mapped to a
Java object when we use the @ModelAttribute annotation. The Spring container will take care of the mapping
for us, provided the names in the HTML form should be same as the names on our Java class. You've
also learnt that in the recent versions of Spring this ModelAndView has been split into model and
view separated out.
We use the ModelMap to send the data back and we use a String type for the ViewName.
So instead of using ModelAndView, we use the ModelMap for data and a string that represents the ViewName.
Everything else remains the same.
The ViewResolver will take the String ViewName, it will append or prefix it with the location and suffix
it with a extension.