In this lecture, you'll see how easy it is to create a Spring Boot Web MVC project using STS. Go to the file menu,
say New -> Spring Starter Project. Give your project a name, call it springbootweb.
Change the group to
com.bharath.spring.web instead.
Same with package, the package should be com.bharath.spring.web or let's follow the convention spring.boot.web.
Next.
Here, search for web and select the very first one under web which is web. We need the web dependency.
That is the only dependency required as of now. Finish and that will create a Spring Boot Web project.
Expand it and open the pom.xml which is the important Maven configuration file. Click on the last
tab, double click to maximize. We have the maven coordinates with the project information.
The parent project as always is this the spring-boot-starter-parent. We have some properties which
specify the Java version. And the important section is the dependency section, wherein you see the
spring-boot-starter-web is the starter project for the web MVC projects while using Spring Boot. And the test dependency
as always and also the plugin that will create a jar file of our project and we'll be able to run the
jar file because, it will have the embedded Tomcat inside it and automatically it will launch our application
on localhost:8080 as you will see in the next few lectures.