A simple hello controller that will greet the user if he sends his name from the web browser. To do that,
go to the springbootweb project, source and right click on the package. Say New -> Class, call it HelloController.
Put it in a package called web.controllers. Finish. To make this a controller, you need to mark it
with @Controller annotation as you have learnt from the Spring MVC section.
Now that's a controller. Next, create a method that will send a greeting back to the client.
public String hello()
and it will get a user name. Given a name, it should simply greet hello and the name. return, within double
quotes, hello, space, +name. Control+Shift+f to format.
Do the RequestMapping for this method. You know how to do it.
You have learnt it from the Spring Web MVC Section. @RequestMapping is the annotation we should be using.
Within double quotes, in the brackets provide a RequestMapping. /hello is what the user should be using
from the web browser to access this particular endpoint or this particular method.
And since we are returning a string, we need to use
@ResponseBody. You want to send the response back in the HTTP body.
And this needs to be marked with @RequestParam.
This will be passed in as a URL param from the web browser later on.
So in this lecture, you have successfully created a controller class and implemented a method called
hello, which when given a name, it will simply return hello
and that particular name.