In this lecture, we'll launch our web application and see Spring Boot magic on our web application.
To do that, right click, do a Run As -> Spring Boot App. We need not run it on the server, we need not create a war file.
That's the beauty of Spring Boot. Simply run it as a
Spring Boot App. At this point,
our application is built, a jar file is created and that jar is run.
This particular class runs and automatically it will launch a embedded Tomcat. For every Spring Boot
web application, automatically a
Tomcat is embedded into it.
And as you can see, it is launched and
our application is running on that Tomcat and we can access it at localhost:8080.
That is the power of Spring Boot Web.
Launch your web browser, hit control+t, localhost:8080/hello?name=bharath.
So localhost:8080, there is no web application name given here.
I will tell you why that is and how to configure one.
localhost:8080/hello?
the parameter we need to pass in, which is name is equal to, whatever name you want. Enter.
And the result is hello bharath.
So our Spring Boot web application has worked as expected. When we type this in and hit Enter.
The request goes to the Tomcat running, and we have mapped the URL in such a way that if it sees
hello, it will come to this controller method which will take the name from the query parameter and returns
hello.
To understand the flow, when the Spring Boot application is launched,
and this main method is run internally,
Spring will scan through all the base packages within which this class is located which is market with
@SpringBootApplication and its subpackages. And it will automatically find the controllers.
So it knows about the controllers, the Dispatcher Servlet, the Internal View Resolver,
they are all configured for us automatically. And you can customize them using the properties.
So within this property file, you can mention whatever custom configuration you want.
You can also write Java configuration, but most of the times we can configure everything in application.properties.
I will show you a couple of properties in the next few lectures.