In the previous lecture, we have seen a Spring Boot Web MVC application
in action. In this lecture, I will show you how to customize a few properties
by using the application.properties.
We had to access our application without the context last time, because by default the Spring Boot Web
applications are configured to run at localhost:8080 on a Tomcat instead of having a
root context. When you deploy a war file, it will automatically have
a root context, but in this case we are deploying our application as a jar file instead.
So to configure a root context, go back to application.properties and type server dot, and you will see
all the properties you can configure for a server. server.context-path,
context-path=/springbootweb. You can use whatever name you want.
You can simply call springweb as well if you want to.
There are several other properties, server.port, etc; So you can even configure port if you want to.
By default it runs on 8080. Save, stop the application, re-run it or relaunch it.
This time we should be able to access it using springbootweb as the context from the web browser.
So before hello, use springbootweb/hello and we still get the same result back.
So that is how we can customize, without writing any xml or even Java configuration,
you can configure your application or you can customize the application.