The difference between the earlier Spring projects and the Spring Boot web application is that, we were
able to run this application without deploying it to a server or without creating a
war file. So Spring Boot allows us to do that. When we run our application, Spring Boot will look for a
class that is marked with Spring Boot main and it will run its main method. And when that happens,
Spring Boot since we have Spring MVC and all that on our path, or as dependencies, it will pull a Tomcat
dependency as well.
If you go to the maven dependencies, it adds spring-boot-starter-tomcat which has the entire Tomcat
in it.
So it will launch that Tomcat and it will run our classes on that server.
And that is the reason we were able to access our application on localhost:8080.
We can even apply it like this onto production. Instead of deploying it as a war file,
we can simply deploy the jar file of this application onto a production server. So to see that in action,
right click on this, do a
Maven install or Run As -> Maven install. That will create the jar file of our application and I will show you
how that jar file will look like.
Once that is created, go to your workspace. Build is success, go to wherever your workspace is. For me its under
documents. Go to your particular project, called springbootweb.
Go to the target directory and you will find a jar file that it creates by default.
Right click on it, open it with any zip utility. For me I will use the Archive Utility. That will unzip
the contents.
If you look at it, it has a BOOT-INF. Inside it, it has a lib.
So our jar file inturn has a bunch of jars which our project depends on.
These are all that Maven dependencies which you see here, which got pulled because we
have spring-boot-starter-web in our pom.xml. Just because of one single dependency,
all these jars came in and it has embedded Tomcat in it. So we can deploy our jar file. And if we depend
on any other libraries, it could be within our company or outside our organization,
all those will go into this particular lib inside the jar and we can simply run this jar on production.
We can use a Java command or we can simply launch it by double clicking on it
if you have Java on your environment variables.
So it's that powerful. When we use Spring Boot,
we can run our projects as jars instead of wars.