In this lecture he will mandate the dependency injection and do a dependency check by using the at
required annotation from spring.
the usecase that wIll be working on is a patient prescription use case you will create a prescription
class a spring bean which will have an ID patient name and the list of medicines and will see how
to mandate some of these fields and you can mandate some of them.
So let's get started by going to our favorite eclipse IDE I click Create a new class start with prescription
patients prescription package com dot bharath dot springcore dot dependency
Check your going to request the spring container to do some dependency check finish
the first field is an ID that is our requirement then patient name then list off medicines int id
the prescription ID private string patient name.
Finally private list of medicines list of strings.
call them medicines
control one import the list from Java util select them all right click go to source generate getters
and setters.
Select all ok do a ctrl shift F to format.
Let's take these two fields.
Put them right up top control shift F to format and we can copy over the first step is to create the spring
bean and you know the next two steps.
The next two steps are to grab the test and the config dot xml grab them from LC annotations.
Our last use case that we have worked on paste them will change them and will come back.
And in the next lecture you will mandate all the fields go to test
the spring bean configuration file will be spring core slash dependency check.
That is our package config dot xml is fine we don't need the abstract application context here
because it's not about the spring life cycle so get rid of the context dot register shutdown hook
and we can change this back to application context.
do a control shift O change this from patient will come back to that hit control one on application context
import that from Spring.
Save it.
This will be prescription on the left hand side as well.
Prescription and the bean name also will change to prescription.
Say it do a control shift O to organize the imports.
call this prescription instead of patient
so you remember the steps the first step is to create the application context.
pass it the configuration file.
The second step is to get the bean and then use it from the spring.
And here we are simply displaying the details of the bean go to config dot xml
Clean it up and you're going to configure it in the next lecture.
Go to prescription generate the tostring method for our prescription.
We'll do that by going to source and generator to string hit.
OK control shift F to format, so in this lecture you have successfully created the POJO And you also copied
over the test modified it made it uptodate to what we need.
Also we have the config  dot xml which you will configure and wrap it up in the next lecture.