The previous lecture you started working on the prescription use case for dependency check.
But you have skipped the config file step and moved on to test.
And we wrapped it up.
Let's go to conflict and configure our bean.
And then this lecture will also configure dependency check for our bean class is equal to prescription.
Grab the package name
all the way to dependency check come back paste it dot give it a name name is equal to prescription
And let's not inject any values.
But go to prescription and make this I.D. mandatory by using at required annotation from spring.
hit control one import
you cannot mark the fields as required.
That is the reason I have put it here.
I wanted to show you that you should use the required annotation only on the setter methods,
So cut it take it to the set id methods right here and it's good to go.
So you should always apply them on the setter methods.
We are making the ID field mandatory.
Let's see if it works.
go to test right click
run as java application.
It still doesn't throw any exception although the ID is 0 which is the default values spring simply
accepted all the default values for patient name  its null and for medicines it's null so it didn't
apply the required attribute.
Can you guess what the reason could be.
Yes you are right by default.
in spring the annotation support is disabled one way to enable it as you have seen earlier is to enable
it only for that particular annotation in case of dot required go to the spring config dot xml.
And we need to use a bean class is equal to
required.
We need to grab a class so the best way to do it close the Bean tag right here.
Go back to test at the end.
Type in required control space grab this required annotation bean post-processor and you will get the entire
package and the class copy the whole thing from the import come back to config dot xml paste the
class.
So once we configure this class as a bean spring will instantiate this bean and this bean
knows how to process the at required annotation come back to test get rid off that line do a control shift o
to remove unwanted imports now lets run the test and see what happens
run as java application this time we will see the exception so that dependency check kicks in.
And if you scroll it to the right it says error creating bean with name prescription defined in the
classpath resources.
Keep going to the right bean initialization exception from spring property.
ID is required for bean prescription.
So it clearly says that ID is required but only the default value was found and its value was not set
So go to config dot XML use P schema .
P colon ID is equal to one to three save it rerun the test and this time there are no issues because
we have set the value for the id field.
Similarly you can mandate the patient name and medicines by using the @ required annotation on the
setter method for appropriate field.
Please go ahead and give it a try.