In this lecture you will learn how to configure and use inner beans.
You will work on a usecase where a employee class has a has a relationship with a address class.
Every employee will have an address along with ID and the address will have a house number street and
city.
We are going to keep it simple.
You will create these two classes
and then in the spring configuration will configure the address as a inner bean for the employee go to eclipse
right click
create a new class called employee and the package will be com dot bharath dot springcore dot inner beans
finish
employee will have private int ID and private address which doesn't exist yet.
A d d r e s s
address will create it hit control one get eclipse help create class address in the same package
Finish
address will have a house number private int H  number private string street and private string
city.
just three fields select them all source
Generate getters and setters.
Select all OK control shift F to format.
Go back to employee do the same generate the getters and  setters right click.
You can either go to source here or up at the menu level.
Generate getters and setters select all OK and that generates the getters and setters do a control shift F to format save
it.
The second step is to come up with the configuration file.
Copy over the configuration file from any of the earlier lectures.
Dependency check.
Come back to inner  beans.
paste it
clean up all the beans and will start with the employee bean.
Typically we start with that dependency bean.
That is address but in this case we want to use addresses as inner bean for employee.
So let's get started with that.
Class is equal to employee and it's in the long package.
Com dot bharath dot spring core dot inner beans
Copy that package paste it
Give it a name.
Name is equal to within double quotes.
Employee and set the properties using P schema p colon the only field we have is ID and then the address
id is equal to 1 2 3 its not mandatory to give it a value but let's give it a value.
Next comes property the property name is address and we are going to set that property not by using
ref tag but as a in inner bean simply inside the property we use the bean tag one more time
class is equal to address and copy the package name from here.
paste it right before I address at the class level.
And the name for inner bean is optional because we cannot use an inner bean outside anyways so the
name is optional we need not provide the name to set the properties.
We can use properties.
Inside this bean use the property element or simply use P schema at this level P colon the very
first field or address is H number house number then the street and the city H number is equal
to 700 next P colon Street is equal to Mira Mesa blvd
P colon city is equal to my city San Diego.
One of my favorite cities and we can close this bean right here and get rid of this ending tag and we
have successfully used a Nested bean.
That is a bean as a property for an other bean in the next lecture will create the test will run
it end to end and I'll explain further.