In this lecture you will finish the last step which is creating a test and see the inner  beans in action.
We have started by right clicking on the package say new class let's do it from scratch.
It has been a while since we wrote a test
Select the main method finish the very first step is to create the spring container or get access to the
spring container we do that using application context.
Context is equal to new class path xml application context that takes a configuration file which
is the config Dot xml with the entire package.
So copy that package name and paste it right before config add a forward slash and change all the dots to
forward slashes
the spring container and the classpath xml application context will search for this file on the
classpath
at this path control one import the application context from Spring.
Second step is to retrieve the bean from the container.
We use the get bean method and pass in the B name which is employee.
We haven't added the two string methods,
So let's go to employee along with ID and address we need along with the setter and getter methods lets add a
two string method.
Source generate two string hit.
OK.
That will do it.
Same for address.
Source generate 2 string.
OK.
save It come back to test retrieve the employee and hit control 1 assign statement to a new local variable
it returns an object change to employee and change the name to employee as well.
control one add down casting two employee from object sysout employee do a control  shift F to format right
click run our test.
It is an exception.
Let's scroll up and see what the error is, error creating bean with employee defined on the classpath
error setting property values.
That's not rightable property invalid property address.
So we have used the wrong name instead of ADD.
We have used AD somewhere.
So let's get let's go and see the config file.
go to config dot xml.
And here the property name should be address and not our adress run the test
again and this time it passes and we get the employee object along with the address inside it.
So you have successfully configured the inner bean address for the employee.
And spring has instantiated the inner bean and it has set it in to the address of the employee.
And we got it back.
So now you know that there are four ways to inject an object using the reference as element reference
as attribute using P schema and also using inner bean.
The inner bean can be used only in case of reference types and also only when the bean above or the  dependent bean
has a has a relationship with the dependent bean or depende
So in this case the employee has a has a relationship with the address only in that case we can use
the inner beans.