In this lecture you will learn about the spring beans scopes.
The scope is availability of the object in the container in simple words,
it is the number of objects created in the container of a particular bean type.
There are five possible values Singleton prototype request session and finally global session. Singleton
is the default value when we configure a bean in the spring configuration,
and we do not provide any scope,
by default it is singleton.The spring container if the market a singleton or if we don't specify anything
on the bean will create only one object no matter how many times that bean is read and used in our application.
The second scope is the prototype scope.
If we mark bean as prototype then the container will create different objects of that type.
Every time that object is read and used in our application and next is request as the name itself says the
request scope is only relevant for spring MVC webapplications, when the request comes in from the end user
or from the browser to our web application which is developed using spring spring container will create
an object per request per user request next session again.
Session is also relevant only for spring MVCweb applications.
A session is everything that happens between a user logon and Logout or everything that happens from the
time the user first access our website till the time he leaves our website if we mark a bean as
session scope scope then the spring container will create only one object for the entire session.
If a new user session is created then another object will be instantiated by spring.
Last but not the least the global session,
this will create if we mark bean as Global's session scoped spring container will create an object
per global context.
This is used only in spring.
MVC Portlet applications.
In Portlet applications there can be multiple Portlets across these portlets
there will be a global session.
global context and Spring container will create only one object for the entire global session
across these portlets we will see the first two.
That is the singleton and prototype in-action in the next lecture and request and session will be covered.
When you create a spring MVC webapplications in sections later on a global session will not be
covered as a part of this course because will not creating Portlet applications in this course.