In this lecture you will see the springs scope in action.
You're going to reuse the beans from the inner beans usecase we use address employee etc. and the test
and config
So go to the config dot xml and right now we haven't configured any scope for our beans by default
spring.
Beans are singleton scoped that is the spring container will create only one instance of any bean no matter
how many times we use it in our application.
If you go to test dot Java we use the employee only once.
As of now.
Copy these two lines.
Let's use the employee.
One more time.
Change it to employee two
And also in the sysout change it to employee two now we are using it twice run the program again run the
test as java application.
It prints the same values but that doesn't prove that they are the same objects in memory.
To prove that they are use employee dot hash code, hash code is a method that every object in Java gets from
the parent class which is java dot lan dot object and it points to the if the both the hash codes are
same that means both the objects are pointing to the same memory location.
So run the test one more time and compare the hash
codes they are exactly the same.
So the spring container has created only one object although we have used employee twice here and we
have retrieved it twice.
Now lets change the scope go to config dot xml to set the scope to prototype on the bean tag for the employee.
Scope is an attribute is equal to within double quotes use prototype.
Now that will change the scope from singleton to prototype rerun the test and observe the output.
The hash codes are no longer the same spring.
Now creates two different objects every time we use the object in our best.
If you go back to the test
for the first time here when it prints it , its a different hash code in the result and the second time
and we retrieve the object it once again instantiates the object and uses a different object.
We can also use Singleton here instead of prototype but that's default anyway.
But you are welcome to use this as well singleton.
Spring won't complain run the test.
And both the hash codes are same.
Change it back to prototype and we get different hash codes.
I didn't mean to run them.
I keep doing it once in a while go back run the test and know the hash codes and object to different.