In this lecture I will summarize what you have learned from that dependency check inner beans and
scope's section. Using the spring dependency check feature we can ensure that a particular object for
sure gets what it requires,
that is the dependencies that it requires in order to function.
We do that using the @ required annotation on a particular dependency.
If that particular dependency is not provided at runtime Spring will throw a bean initialization exception
by default spring will assign the default values.
But if you use the at required annotation then that dependency has to be provided otherwise you will see
this exception in your application.
Second we have learned how to configure beans inside beans.
That is dependencies.
We use Bean then the property tag and then inside it we can define another bean.
So the first bean depends on the second bean inner beans allow us to define dependencies within another
bean.
We have learnt how to do that and seen it in action as well.
Last and very important you have learnt the five different scopes namely Singleton prototype request
session and global session that apply to spring beans.
Spring container by default uses the singleton scope that is no matter how many times we retrieve and
use an object from the spring container in our application it will create only one instance of it to
change it.
We specify a scope in xml configuration.
The second scope that we can provide is prototype which tells the spring container that it should create
a different bean everytime we request for an object in our application. The request transition scopes are
for the web application context when you work with spring MVC.
You can see these two in action and the global session is for portlet context when you develop portlet applications
which is  very rare which you use for global session.