To start working on the Spring auto-wire use case, let's first create a new maven project, because we have
put quite a few classes under this Spring core and also packages.
It's getting overloaded or cluttered.
So create a new project by going to the File menu.
New -> Maven project, click Next. Leave the default option which is maven architect, click start, click Next.
The group Id is com.bharath.spring which is fine, and the artifact Id should be springcoreadvanced.
Finish, that will create the maven project for us.
Open the pom.xml and close everything else. If you have other files open close them all. Click on the last tab
which says pom.xml. By default it will have the junit dependency.
Let's add the spring dependencies by going to the pom.xml of the previous project. Open it, go to the
last tab, maximize.
Copy all the way from properties till the closing of build element. Come back to our new project's pom.
Start from properties, go all the way till dependencies, paste it, save it. We got the spring version as a property,
we have the two spring dependencies, the spring-core and spring-context, the jars that we need, and Maven
will pull all the other transitive dependencies. And in the plugin management, we have configured the maven
plugin compiler or maven-compiler-plugin.
And we are asking it to use Java version 1.8. By default, maven will use 1.5.
So we're asking it to use 1.8. Go to src/test/java.
We don't need junit, we are not using junit. So delete that package, OK.
Right click on the project. Since we have changed the maven pom.xml,
you have to right click, go to Maven, say Update Project, hit OK.
That will update the project and all the errors will go away.
Now let's copy over the propertyplaceholder which we have here.
Copy over that package, Control+c, paste it under the source folder here, because propertyplaceholder
is also an advanced topic and let's delete it from the previous project. We'll have it only in one place.
That's it. Starting next lecture, you'll be working on Spring autowiring.