In this lecture, you will learn how to implement Spring autowiring. To do that,
all we need is two object types because autowiring works on reference types. Go to the previous project, go
to the constructorinjection package, we are going to grab these four files from here. Before we do that,
right click on this package on the new project, create a new sub-package called autowiring, finish.
And you can delete
this folder here.
We don't need that package.
Get rid of it.
All we need is the auto wiring package. Copy address all the way to config from constructorinjection.
Paste them here.
Expand, open all of them, address, employee, test.java and config.xml.
On the address,
we have house number and we have street and city. And the Employee object is the one which depends on
address.
Get rid of this constructor and let's keep it simple.
We don't even need the Id field.
So delete the getters and setters for Id.
getId and setId, delete both of them.
All we need is two objects to demonstrate autowiring. Source, generate the toString method one more time.
Enter, control + shift + f to format.
So we have an employee that uses address and we are going to autowire this address into Employee.
To do that, go to the config.xml.
First create the address bean using the setter injection.
We are going to leave it as it is.
We are using p-schema here. But when we create the Employee object we are not going to use the c schema.
Delete the usage of c schema.
Instead we use autowiring. We tell the container, you go ahead and inject the dependencies. To do that,
we use the auto, control + space,
autowire is the attribute, is equal to the values,
as I said there can be different values. Let's use byType. I'll explain the flow end to end once
we finish everything.
So using Autowire attribute on the bean, we are telling Spring container to inject the dependencies for
this bean automatically, automatically wire the beans. Go to test,
we need to make some package changes in the config as well because this package is not correct.
So go to test, grab the package, the new package with spring advanced in it. Come back, change the package
for address and also change the package for employee as well. Save it, go to test. And this here, should
also change.
So paste the package, change the dots to forward slashes,
and that's it.
Let's run the test, right click,
Run as Java Application.
And if you see everything still works as expected, although we haven't used constructor injection
or Setter injection on the employee, Spring automatically injects
by type. byType,
if you go back to the slides from earlier, it uses setter injection, by Type and by Name, the container
is going to use Setter injection. By constructor is constructor injection and Auto detect is outdated.
We are not going to use it.
So what exactly happened here is that Spring, when we run our test, the spring container loads this configuration
and it will create this bean, the address bean.
And when it comes to the employee bean,
since we have configured it by type it will go to the employee class,
it will search what all reference dependencies or what all object dependencies does employ have. It will
find address and it will look at what it's type is or what class type it is. It is address.
It will then take this address, goes to the config file and searches which bean tag has a class as address.
It keeps on searching,
and as soon as it finds it, it's going to use that particular bean. It will instantiate that bean if
it is not already instantiated and then it will inject that bean into the employee using setter injection.
That is how it has worked.
So always remember that the Spring container
will look at all the object references that are dependencies.
It will then take the type because we are, we have configured autowiring by type. So it will use the object
type.
It searches the configuration file for that type, a bean tag which has a class with that type.
It will instantiate it and it will inject it into the bean.