In this lecture you will learn three important things that you should always remember when you do
autowiring by type. The number one thing which you already know is that the Spring container will try to find
a match by type and if the bean is there, it will inject it.
You have seen it in the output in the last lecture. If it's there, it will inject it.
If it can't find the match,
for example let's delete this bean from here.
Save it, run the test. No exceptions but simply the container will inject a null value for the address
dependency of Employee.
So if no bean is found, no bean match is found for autowiring the dependency, it will inject a
null value. Do a control+z, bring the address bean back.
Copy the entire address bean, paste it,
and changed the name to address1.
So we are duplicating the same type. The name itself is different, but the type is same.
Let's see what happens, run the test and you will see an exception. Maximize the console by double clicking.
No qualifying bean of type autowiring address is available: expected single matching bean but found 2.
So the spring container is confused because it was expecting only one bean of type address, but we have
accidentally configured two.
So get rid of the second one.
Run the test and everything is back to normal. So always remember that if a Spring container finds a
matching type, it will inject it. If there is no matching at all then it will inject a null value.
And if there are duplicates, then it will throw an exception.