In this lecture, you will learn how to do Autowiring by name.
So far, you have learnt how to do it by type. Simply change this attribute value from byType to byName,
n capital and that's it.
If you go back to the employee, byName works by the name of the object or name of the reference variable
that we have defined here.
In this case it is address. And in the config file the name of the bean should be address for it to work.
Let's run our test and see what happens.
And everything works as expected.
This time the Spring container, the way it searches is, it comes to this configuration file, it uses this configuration
file.
As soon as it sees autowiring here, byName, it goes to the Employee which is the bean it is trying
to create,
searches for all the dependencies which are objects. In this case it is only the address.
It will take the name of that variable because we have configured it byName.
And it will go back to the configuration file and search for beans with name as the same name as the
reference variable.
It will not search for the type, for the class this time.
Simply it will search for the matching name of the variable inside that object.
Let's get rid of this, let's delete this dependency. Do a control+x, save it. Run it and it'll be null.
Similar to byType, in case of byName as well, the Spring container will inject a null if it can't find
the bean.
Let's try to duplicate it.
Copy the same bean twice with the same exact name.
The type doesn't matter now, what it looks for is the name.
So save it. We have two beans with the same name. Run it and we see an exception very similar to byType.
It says Configuration problem: Bean name 'address' is already used in this  element. So we get a
duplicate bean definition parsing exception.
We can't have two beans with the same name. Let's change one of their names.
Let's make one of them address1.
Save it, rerun the test and this time it works.
So the spring container will start searching for the bean named address.
It will come here.
This is not the one. Although the type is same the Spring container doesn't care about the type this time. It's
byName. It comes to the next bean, it finds this address and it will immediately instantiate that object
and it'll inject it into Employee.
So you have learnt both byName as well as byType. byName,
we can have the same bean defined multiple times but we have to give different names.
And when we do injection the Spring container will use the name of the reference variable and
searches for that bean with that name.