The last option in XML based autowiring is to use the constructor.
When we did it by using byType and byName, the Spring container uses the setter injection or
the property based injection.
Let's use the constructor injection
in this lecture. Go to Eclipse.
To use the constructor injection, we need to provide a parameterized constructor. Go to Employee class.
Employee should take an object which is the dependency.
this.address = address; Go to the configuration, delete the duplicate bean that
we have created in the last lecture, the address1, save it.
And here, where we say autowire, instead of byName,
use constructor and that tells the Spring container that it should do a constructor based injection.
Go to test, right click, Run as Java application and automatically the spring container
does the constructor based injection for us.
So the way it works, it goes to the configuration file,
reads this employee bean and it sees that it has to do a constructor based injection.
So it'll look at what this constructor takes, what type of argument and it will look for this type of bean
in the configuration, it will instantiate it and then it will invoke the constructor to create the Employee.