In this lecture, let's learn Autowiring using annotations. Get started by right clicking on this autowiring package. We are going
to use the same beans. Right click, new -> package. At the end of it, autowiring.annotations. Finish, copy over
the configuration file, the beans and the test to the new package dot annotations. This is the new package.
Paste them on it.
Close everything in the editor, so that we don't have any confusion.
Address, Employee, test and config.xml. In the config.xml, we don't need this autowire attribute
anymore, because we are going to use annotations. Go to Employee and to inject this dependency on the
setter method of setAddress, use @Auto, hit control+space, Autowired
is the annotation from org.springframework.
We don't need the constructor here, get rid of the constructor, because we are using setter injection.
Or leave the constructor there so that we can use it later. Do a control+z.
Right now we are using setter injection, go to test. Update the test to use the right package, autowiring
slash annotations slash config.
Everything else remains the same. By default, if you remember annotations in spring are disabled. To enable
them, you know how to do that. Go to config.xml, right here, context colon, hit control+
space, annotation-config. You can close that right there.
And that is all we need. context
colon annotation-config. That tells Spring that all the annotations should be enabled and used. Run
the test.
Right click, run as Java application.
There is a classcast exception ofcourse. Go to config.xml,
we need to change the package here as well.
autowiring.annotations.Address, autowiring.annotations.Employee.
We see a class cast exception because Spring was creating the wrong classes because we asked it
to do so.
But in our test, we were using classes from different package.
This employee here is from the current package which is annotations. But here in config.xml, we
didn't have annotations in the package.
That's rerun the test.
Right click, Run as Java application and we see the proper output. This time you have configured autowiring at a
setter level using @Autowired annotation from Spring and in the XML, we need not do anything except
for enabling the annotations.