The autowired annotation can be used at the property level as well or the field level.
Instead of doing it at a setter level, you can grab this autowired from here, cut it and paste it on
the field level and Spring will automatically inject the dependency into this field.
You can get rid of the setter method if you want to and still it works. Go to test, rerun the test.
And we still see the same output.
So the second way of using autowiring is to use it on the field level.
You can also use it at the setter level which you have already seen.
The third combination is to use it at the constructor level.
So get rid of it.
Cut it from here.
Go to the constructor, paste it right above the constructor.
Now the autowire is going to do or the Spring container is going to use the constructor based injection.
Nothing else changes.
Rerun the test and everything still works as expected.
So autowiring using annotations is quite easy.
You configure the annotation support in the Spring configuration, then you come to the beans and use
the Autowire annotation at the constructor level,
if you want to mandate the contract or at the field level, if you want the dependencies to be optional.