In this lecture, you will learn and use the Qualifier annotation along with the Autowired annotation.
The Qualifier annotation tells the container that it should find a bean with the given name and then
inject that bean.
If the container find a bean with that name in the configuration, it will throw a NoSuchBeanException. Go
to Eclipse. To use the qualifier, we need two beans here which we already have. Instead of having address
and address2, let's change this address to address123
and the value to 5 or let's leave it as 123 and change the value of the second bean to 567 so that
we can differentiate them.
Now if we run this test,
run it and we see an exception because it can't find a matching bean for this address. We have multiple
beans,
that's the reason we are seeing an exception.
Now go back to the config.xml.
We have address123 and address2, multiple beans but no match is found. Use the qualifier annotation
on the Employee class. @Qualifier,
control+space import it from org.springframework. And within brackets give it a value. In the config.xml
you can use either of these beans.
Use address123, copy it, paste it. Rerun the test and this time the container will be able to find the bean
and it injects it with the house number 123.
So it is this bean here. The container, the qualifier tells the container that it should find
a bean with the given name instead of the field name.
It goes here and searches for a bean with that name.
Let's use address2. Go back to Employee. Change this to address2, save it. Rerun and this time it injects
the second bean, the house number is 567 and not 123.
So it creates this bean, it matches this bean here.
Now if it can't find it, for example if I say 789, this bean doesn't even exist, a bean
with this name doesn't even exist.
And if I remove this required=false, that is,
this has to be injected, then if we run the test, we should see an exception because it's not finding a match,
it says No qualifying bean of type address is found.
And we are seeing a NoSuchBeanDefinitionException. If you want to avoid that, you can put the attribute called
required=false.
Rerun the test and it will inject a null value.
So in this lecture, you have learnt about the @Qualifier annotation using which we can tell the Spring
container that it should use the name we are providing it instead of the field name, using the field name.
Let's change this back to address123, something that works. Run the test and it injects the bean.