In this lecture, I will quickly recap and summarize what you have learnt from the Autowiring section.
Autowiring
is the process of the spring container automatically injecting the object types. Autowiring can
be done in two ways, using XML configuration and annotations. In XML configuration,
we can do it byType, by the object type or the class type, byName,
that is the name of the object or bean in the XML configuration.
And byConstructor. As the name itself says, byConstructor uses constructor dependency injection methodology
whereas byType and byName, when we use these two the spring container will use the setter injection.
And the second and the most used way is using annotations.
We can autowire by simply marking a particular dependency or a field on a class using @Autowired
annotation.
And if there are multiple beans of the same type and if there is a confusion for the spring container,
we can use the @Qualifier annotation and tell the spring container which bean we exactly want to inject.
@Qualifier is always used along with @Autowired annotation.