In this lecture, you will see the power of Spring Data. Without writing any queries, you will implement two
finder methods to find the product. To do that,
go to STS, go to the ProductRepository class or interface. To add a finder method, start typing in
findBy, hit control+space.
And STS will automatically show you all the finder methods you can create. By scanning through
the product, and for each of these fields here, it automatically shows you the content or the code assistance
to generate the finder methods.
We want to do a findByName. Select that and automatically the type is String name and the return type is
a list of products. Its not a single product, because there could be multiple products with the same name.
If it was an id, then it is unique but not the name. That's it.
That is all we need to do to get a list of products,
given a name. We need not write any SQL.
Now go back to the SpringdatajpaApplicationTests.
Let's comment out this entire code here so that we can just see the custom finder methods in
action. Start commenting out with save and comment out all the way till the end. You can use shortcuts if you're familiar
with them. Control+shift+f to format. Add a sysout, control+space, system.out.println(repository.findByName) now it
lists out, along with the inbuilt methods like findAll and findOne,
we also see findByName, because we have just added it to the repository.
Pass in the name. Name is Mac.
Saved.
Run the test.
And we should see one product coming back
in the results, and here you go.
So I got a product back successfully.
So it's that easy to implement custom finder methods. Now to implement a findByPrice, you know how to
do it.
Go back to the repository. Again, start typing in findBy, Control+Space, price. Automatically it picks up
what datatype it is,
and also it returns a list of products. Control+shift+f to format. Come back to the test, instead
of findByName or let it be. Copy it, go to the next line.
Paste, findByPrice. Instead of Mac you need to pass in a double.
Remember, we have updated the price.
Don't use 1200. Use 1500d.
Save it.
Run the program again. This time we should see the same output, twice, because we are doing two finders.
Let's see the results.
There we go. So we have two products coming back, or there is only one product but we are executing
two finder methods,
and we are displaying the results.
So in this lecture, you have successfully learnt how to implement a custom finder methods on our repositories
without writing any SQL.