In this lecture, you will learn how to implement a findBy method that takes multiple fields and returns
a list of products.
It's very simple again. findBy,
I want to search for a product based of its name and price. And this time it takes two parameters,
(String name, Double price) and it should return a list of products. Save it. At the end add
a semi-colon. Do the control+shift+f to format.	That's it.
So you have successfully used a keyword called And.
And you have come up with a finder method that takes two parameters. You can always refer to the Spring
documentation, Spring data JPA documentation and it has different keywords that you can use for different
sql syntax that you want to generate.
The key words are similar, named similar as the SQL.
When we come up with our SQL statements, we typically use the same keywords. Go back. To test it, go back
to your test, add one more.
sysout,
repository.findByNameAndPrice. So I need to pass in Mac, which is the name and the price
is, its a double 1500d.
Save it, run the program. We should get a total of three products as a result from these three finder
methods and we see three products coming back.
Now if I change this to 1501 instead of 1500, re-run the test, I should
not be getting any results for the third finder. I should only be getting two results.
The third list should be empty.
So we see two products and the third one is empty because the prize didn't match although the name matched.
Now go ahead and play around with the different keywords that are available in this table.