In this lecture we'll migrate the Spring MVC web application that you've developed earlier to use Java based configuration instead
of xml configuration. You will create a Spring configuration by extending the WebApplicationInitializer
You will create a class that will replace the web.xml and that class will extend the
WebApplicationInitializer from Spring.
Similarly you will create a configuration file,
where we'll configure the internal view resolver etc; and that will extend a WebMvcConfigurerAdapter.
And you'll mark this with annotations such as @EnableWebMvc which is equivalent to .
When you used the xml, the dispatcherservlet.xml,
this is what we used there.
But here you simply annotate this class with @EnableWebMvc. The next one @ComponentScan, instead
of defining
in the xml, you'll use this annotation and tell Spring which all packages it need to scan for our controllers.
Finally, you know what
this is. The configuration which tells Spring that this particular been here, SpringConfig encloses
spring beans or
it acts as a container of Spring beans.
This is equivalent to defining beans element in your spring configuration file. So you will do all this
in simple steps in the next few lectures.