In this lecture, you'll learn how to migrate the spring MVC web application to use Java configuration instead of xml based configuration.
If you expand this project in your Eclipse IDE, go to src/main/webapp/WEB-INF
and you will find two configuration files. One ofcourse is the web.xml which is the deployment
descriptor for our web application where we have defined the Spring dispatcher servlet which is our front
controller.
The second configuration file here is the dispatcher-servlet.xml.
This is the spring configuration file which we intend to replace.
You're also going to get rid of the web.xml and use Java configuration there as well. In the
dispatcher-servlet.xml, we have define the context:component-scan telling Spring which packages should
be scanned for our controller classes.
If you go to src/main/java all our controllers are under this particular package.
If we see, atleast one of these controllers working after our migration, then we are good.
The second bean here is the InternalViewResolver or InternalResourceViewResolver which resolves our
JSP pages. Build this project and run it on the server. Run As -> Maven Clean just to make sure it's still
working and we are all set. Right click, Run As -> Maven install.
Once that completes, you can run it on the server.
Right click, Run As -> Run on Server. Finish.
That will launch the default page which is the index.jsp which says Hello World!
Type in hello
at the end because our hello controller is configured to use that URI pattern. hello, Enter.
And that takes us to the HelloController which redirects it, after setting some information it will
redirect it to the hello.jsp which is under WEB-INF/views/hello.jsp,
and it displays all that information.
That is what we are seeing here.
So this should exactly work the same once we get rid of the web.xml and dispatcher-servlet.xml
and replace it with Java configuration.