The very first step is to update the pom.xml with a new dependency which is the servlet jar dependency
and also add the war plugin to the pom.xml. To do that, go to Eclipse, go to the Spring MVC project,
open the pom.xml which is the Maven configuration file.
Click on the last tab which says pom.xml. DoubleClick to maximize. Go to the dependencies section and
at the end of it we are going to add a new dependency for the servlet jars. We don't need this servlet
dependency at runtime because Tomcat already has it.
But to build our project using Maven, we will need it because we are going to add or use some classes
from the servlet API when we replace the web.xml and dynamically register the servlets. Launch
your web browser and search for, or Google for
Servlet maven dependency and the very first link that shows up. Click on 3.1.0, the sublink
here. That will take you to the maven dependency page.
Scroll down,
copy the contents. Go back to Eclipse, paste it. Do a control+shift+f to format. Delete any unwanted spaces.
Delete this line.
Hit control+d and you will see that by default the scope is provided. Meaning, that at runtime we don't need
it and it is provided by the application container which in our case is Tomcat. Stop the server for
now. So we have added the Maven dependency.
The last step in the Maven pom.xml is to add another plugin which is the war plugin.
So far, we have been using the default settings for the war plugin that comes with maven. We have to
override them because when we delete the web.xml later on, the Maven plugin will fail to build
our project, because it always expects the web.xml by default in a web application project for Maven
to build.
So we are going to tell Maven by adding a new war plugin configuration that our project will not
have a web.xml although it is a web project. So you can start by copying this compiler plugin.
Paste the contents right next to it.
We are going to update it. The groupId is same for both the compiler as well as the war plugin, so leave
it. The artifact name is maven-war-plugin. The version, you can go for whatever version.
If there is later than 2.4, you can use it.
But I have been using 2.4.
So I am going to continue with that. Within configuration,
get rid of the source and target directories.
The configuration will look different for a war file, warSourceDirectory.
If you hit control+space, Eclipse will help you out with the elements that are available.
warSourceDirectory is what we need.
src/main/webapp. That is the source directory for our war file. In our project
that is how it is structured.
Give it a name, warName. Do a control+shift+f to format.
The war name will be springmvc. That is our project name as well.
And the last and the important piece, failOn, hit control+space, failOnMissingWebXml.
Let me scroll it up by adding some spaces so that you can see it clearly. failOnMissingWebXml,
and this by default is true.
So turn it off by changing it to false.
So this tells Maven, there is a missing angular bracket,
let me add that. Do a control+shift+f to format. Save it and all the errors go away.
So this failOnMissingWebXml tells maven that it should not fail the build if there is no web.xml
in our war project. This is the purpose that we are adding the entire plugin for war. Otherwise we
would have not needed it.
We would have used the default settings that comes with maven.
So in this lecture, you have successfully configured the servlet dependency as well as the Maven war plugin
and turned off the failOnMissingWebXml
so that maven will build our application although there is no web.xml.