The second step is to replace the dispatcher-servlet.xml with a Java based configuration.
Go to Eclipse. Before you create the configuration,
right click on our project. Any time we change the pom.xml,
if you see any errors or even if you don't see any errors, right click on it, say Maven, do a Update Project.
Hit OK.
And if you have any errors they should go away.
Maven will update according to the new pom.xml.
Now let's create the Java configuration for our Spring MVC project by
right clicking on the new package. Say New -> Class.
Call it SpringConfig, Finish.
We are going to replace the dispatcher-servlet.xml which has two elements, context:component-scan
and a bean which is the InternalResourceViewResolver.
We'll replace these two with the Java configuration. To do that, our config class should extend a class
from Spring which is MVC or WebMvcConfigurerAdapter.
Its WebMvcConfigurerAdapter.
Very first step is to annotate this class with three annotations.
Number one you already know, @Configuration, which tells Spring that this is a configuration class.
Second annotation here is enable
MVC support, that is @EnableWebMvc. Last and the most important one, ComponentScan.
So this is exactly the same as the component-scan element here in the xml. And using this we can specify
which packages should be scanned within double quotes, you can provide a value.
You can simply grab the package name from here. You can have this configuration in a different package
and use a different package here for scanning.
It's up to you. But I have everything in the same package.
So in this lecture, you have successfully created the Spring Configuration file and added three annotations
to it. You have enabled the MVC support from Spring. You have marked this class as a configuration file and also you have used
the ComponentScan element and you have told Spring which all packages
it should scan for all the controller packages
or the spring beans.