In this lecture, you will configure the InternalResourceViewResolver as a bean in the Java configuration.
To do that, by now you know how to do it.
Public, it should return the view resolver from Spring.
viewResolver is the method that returns it. Inside
this we'll create a ViewResolver
or InternalViewResolver. InternalResourceViewResolver resolver = new InternalResourceViewResolver();
Create an instance of it, then we have two things to set on it. Before we do that add a written
statement so that we will not see all those errors and we successfully return the resolver.
If you go back to the dispatcher-servlet we set up a prefix and suffix.
So grab the prefix, copy that WEB-INF/views, come back to the configuration. resolver.setPrefix();
Come back, within double quotes set the prefix. resolver.setSuffix(). Within double quotes you know what it is.
It is ".jsp".
The extension of our views, within double quotes provide that information. And you have to mark this method with
an annotation.
If you remember, it is the bean annotation that tells Spring that this method will return a Spring bean.
In the next step,
we have one last thing to configure in this configuration file or one method that you should override and
we will be done and we can delete the dispatcher-servlet after that.