In this lecture, you'll configure one last thing in the Spring configuration which is the default
Servlet handler. Although it's not required in this particular usecase you should know about it.
I'm going to explain each of these again at the end of all the lectures.
First, Configure it and I'll explain what it is.
Type in configure, hit control+space and we have several methods which you can override from the
WebMvcConfigurerAdapter.
Select ConfigureDefaultServletHandling. That's the method we want to override.
It gets a DefaultServletHandlerConfigurer as a parameter. Delete these two lines here and simply use
the configurer.enable. You are overriding this method to tell spring that the default handler
in the web container whereever our application is being deployed, in this case Tomcat, should handle all the other
requests.
That is, once we configure the dispatcher-servlet, the dispatcher-servlet is going to handle certain kind
of requests. Do a forward slash because we are going to map. If we open the web.xml right now
a dispatcher servlet is configured for forward slash.
It can serve everything that is there in our application.
But if there are any HTMLs that we want the web container to handle, the dispatcher need not
handle the HTMLs or any static content.
So that is where this comes very handy.
We are telling spring that it should delegate the responsibility to the default servlet handler that
comes with our container, which in this case is Apache Tomcat.
So we are done configuring the Spring configuration and we can delete the dispatcher-servlet
at this point. Right click, do a Delete.
And we got rid of one xml, we have one more left.
We'll get rid of that one in the next few lectures.