In this lecture, you will create a Java configuration file that will replace the web.xml.
We'll split it into two lectures as always. We'll do few things at a time.
So right click on the package, create a new class. Call it WebConfiguration or WebServletConfiguration.
WebServletConfiguration and this should implement an interface from Spring.
Click on add and search for WebApplicationInitialiser. Select that interface, WebApplicationInitialiser.
Click Ok, Finish. And there is only one method that we need to override, it is the onStartup method, which gets
a servletContext. Delete the todo. Hit control+d and create a
AnnotationWeb or AnnotationConfigWebApplicationContext. Not the AnnotationConfigApplicationContext
application context which you have used when you worked with the standalone Java applications for configuring
standalone job applications.
This is AnnotationConfigWebApplicationContext, call it webContext is equal to, create a new instance
of it.
And register our configuration, webContext.register().
The class is SpringConfig.class.
That is our configuration file. Control+space, SpringConfig.class, and we have successfully told
the web configuration about the Spring configuration class. In the next lecture,
you will configure the dispatcher-servlet dynamically within this WebServletConfiguration.