In this lecture, we'll dynamically configure the dispatcher-servlet,this piece here. With the web.xml we are
going to dynamically do it in our Java configuration. Starting 3.0,
we are allowed to do this.
Start by using ServletRegistration, it's an interface.
ServletRegistration.Dynamic servlet, is equal to context or the servletContext which was passed to
this method, dot addServlet(arg0, arg1). We are dynamically adding
a servlet with a URL mapping. Go back to web.xml or the name of the servlet which is dispatcher.
Comeback,
paste the name and create a new instance of the servlet which is DispatcherServlet from Spring. So you've dynamically
created a dispatcher-servlet instance and you've registered it with the container.
Next step, we can tell the container that we want to load this servlet. servlet.setLoadOnStartup(1);
That means this servlet should be loaded as soon as the servlet container starts up.
And also we can dynamically register it for a particular URI, addMapping("/").
That is what we mapped. Everything that comes to our application should go to the dispatcher-servlet.
That is how we have it in the web.xml as well.
So you've successfully registered by creating a
Dispatcher-servlet. Now you can get rid of the web.xml as well. Right click, delete and it's gone.