Before we see if the Java configuration works for our Spring web application, there is one minor step
which I missed, which is to pass this webContext to the DispatcherServlet. That is how the DispatcherServlet will
know about our Spring configuration.
So right when you create the DispatcherServlet, to the constructor of the DispatcherServlet, you can pass in
the WebContext which you have created here.
And we have registered the Spring configuration with it which is our configuration file. And we are all set.
Right click, do a Run As -> Maven Clean, which will clean our project. Right click, Run As -> Maven install.
And once that finishes we can run our application on the server. Success. Right click, Run As ->
Run on Server. Finish. If your Tomcat is running it will restart it and it will launch our application in
the browser. And at the end of it,
append hello.
That's the URI for the controller. Enter and we still get the very same output which you have
seen at the very beginning of this usecase.
So we have got our spring MVC web application to work without web.xml without dispatcher-servlet.xml,
all with simple java configuration.