In this lecture, you will install Java 8 on your machine, to do that
You can download this development tool setup dot txt file from the content of this lecture on udemy
or you can simply google for the appropriate software.
So the first link here is for Java 8.
You can also get there using Google.
Copy that link.
Launch the web browser paste the link that will take us to the java 8 downloads page
scroll it down.
And here we have the Java SE development kit,
that is what we want we don't need their demos and sample downloads accept the license agreement and
for different operating systems.
We have the appropiate JDK.
So depending on the operating system you are working on if you are in Windows you will click on this
here for 64 bit and 32 bit and then for Mac you will click on the DMG and for Linux you will download
the tar.gz. Once you have the exe downloaded on windows double click on it and just follow
the prompts choose an appropriate folder on you c-drive or D-drive,
but do remember which folder you were installing Java as we needed later to configure the JDK in Eclipse
for Mac.
It's pretty simple you double click on the DMG once you downloaded it and you will push it into
your applications.