Eclipse is one of the most popular and most used ides that provides code assistance compiles our code
and even allows us to apply that code on a web-container and run it. By the end of this lecture it
will have the eclipse IDE installed on your machine to do that you can grab this URL from here or simply google
for Eclipse download launch your web browser,
paste it here enter this
will take us to the eclipse downloads page has different releases
Mars is the latest
and then it supports multiple operating systems.
Click on Mars packages,
We need to install Eclipse ID for Java
EE developers not
and not the java developers click on that
and now you can select the package for your appropriate operating system for windows it will be
a zip file for Mac also it will be a tar.gz
file you need to unzip the contents of it and you have the eclipse there for windows you can
simply download unzip the contents of the zip file and eclipse will be installed on your machine once
installed,
let's click on Windows 64 bit here as you can see there will be a download link,
you click on it and you will get the zip file once you downloaded and unzipped
please create a shortcut like this on your desktop on Mac it will automatically appear if not you can
drag this shortcut.
I'll show you how to launch eclipse and configure eclipse to use the java we have installed earlier in
the next lecture.