In this lecture you will learn how to launch that Eclipse ID and configure a JDK in it, so click on Eclipse
icon
once you install it your version might be different.
That's OK as long as it's one of the latest.
You need to select a workspace, workspace is where all the projects you are going to create will be saved
into eclipse.
We'll put all the projects into this folder, browser and you can select whatever folder you want on my Mac,
I have it under documents workspace.
You can create any folder on your cdrive or d drive and make it your workspace.
hit OK.
And that will launch eclipse if you are launching it for the first time you will see a different view.
Once you are on Eclipse you can close all those windows and we'll get here.
Eclipse has different perspectives java
EE Java exectra when you're developing a certain kind of project automatically those perspectives
will be switched.
If not you can click click on them and switch as well to configure the JDK you need to tell eclipse
where the JDK is so that it can use it compile your classes and do the rest of it.
So Windows preferences on a Windows machine you will see preferences under Windows preferences on Mac
will have go to the eclipse menu preferences once you are here
either its windows or Mac,
its all the same.
So JRE type-in JRE
Click on installed JRE's by default.
Eclipse picks up the JRE installed on your machine.
If you have one so Windows usually comes with a JRE under program files.
It would pick that up.
If not if it has picked that up delete it by selecting it remove and add click on add select standard
V.M. next browse to wherever you have installed JDK on your machine and select that folder.
So in my case if I did this this is my JDK in your case if you are on Windows it will be C-Drive program
files Java or JDK 1.8 like this.
So just select that folder.
You don't need all this content slash home that is on Mac on Windows you can stop here right here are
JDK.
So you shouldn't select a JRE or JDK bin.
It should be the JDK folder.
So in this lecture you have lunched the eclipse ID selected workspace and also would have configured a JDK
that you how installed in the previous lectures for Eclipse to use.