In this lecture, I'll show you how easy it is to download and setup tomcat on your machine.
Launch the Web browser and Google for Tomcat 8 download enter click on the very first link that says
Apache Tomcat 8 software download
Once you are on the page scroll down and you will see the binary distributions for different operating
systems.
Download the version for Windows if you are on Windows 32 bit 64 bit exectra its a zip file and if
you are on Mac or Linux download the tar.gz once downloaded unzip the contents of these folders
or the zip files I have unzipped them directly under my desktop just to showcase we can install it anywhere.
Open that folder and you will see the following subfolder.
You need not care or worry about these folders because we are going to configure tomcat in Eclipse and
we are going to use it from within
the eclipse IDE.