The database that you are going to use throughout this course is mysql which is a popular open source
data source database and also you will be installing mysql workbench and install mysql.
Mysql workbench is a client which is GUI based tool which which we can launch connect to the mysql and execute our sql
statements. You are going to do it in three simple steps you will download the installer you will install
the mysql as well as mysql workbench and you will configure mysql although it sounds like a
lot of work it isn't.
Once you download the installer you just keep clicking on the next button and there are a couple of
things you need to do.
You need to choose that you also need the workbench when you are installing.
And when you are in the configuration step you need to make sure that you enter a password it will
prompt you for entering a root password so that you can log in later on.
Make sure that you give a simple password which you will remember.
I will also give you a link which has very good instructions on how to install mysql search for my
sql install.
And scroll down.
There are many links but I found one of these very useful
which says Corley solutions dot com how to install mysql server 5.6 on Windows 7 development machine.
This works for different versions of Windows and Mac.
Click on that link and list out all the important steps to download.
to install and to configure.
Again all these instructions are nothing but clicking on the next button.
Only if you have any issues you can come back here and refer to it in the very first step.
you can click on the link here control click it and you will go to the mysql downloads page.
Scroll down and select your operating system.
If you are on Windows select Microsoft Windows.
I don't want you to download the zip files which are here click on this go to download page that will take
you to the MSI installer's and download one of these depending on your operating system once downloaded
double click on them and just keep clicking the next button.
Once the installation completes it will ask you if you want to configure the mysql server click on that
and that is where it will prompt you for a root password and make sure while installing you check the
workbench option as well so that you will have the bench installed as well and at the end of it, it will
be running as a Windows service automatically for you every time your machine restarts.
Mysql server will be up and running,
you can manage that by going to your Windows services.
Same on Mac on Mac as well.
It will boot up as soon as you mac starts and it will be up and running on a
port 3 3 0 6 by default.
Please do not forget the password that you are entering during installation for me I use a password
called test So that will be easy to remember.