Hoping that your mysql installation has completed successfully you should have mysql up and running
and the mysql workbench installed on your machine to connect to connect to the my sql server
from mysql workbench launch the mysql workbench by clicking on a shortcut like this here
and that will launch the mysql workbench.
You start by creating a new connection to the database click on this plus button will open up a pop up
By default the host name is my local machine.
The default port for mysql server is 3306 and the user name is root.
Give it a name.
I'm going to call it local.
That's my connection name.
Click on test connection and it will prompt you for password.
This is the password which you would have entered when you configure the mysql server So in my case it is test.
Click OK and it says successfully made the mysql connection.
OK.
Again and it will be created.
You can now connect to the database by simply double clicking on this, it will open up the query window.
Since I have been using it I see all this but you can always create a new query window by going here.
New query tap.
And let's start by creating a database called my db to create a database create database.
My db
So is the name of the database select click on the lightning button here and that will create a database
called my db which will be using on in like just later on.