In this lecture I will show you how to download the completed maven projects that you will be developing
throughout this course.
You can always compare your code and configuration with the code and configuration in these projects
if you are having any issues.
Go to the resources section of this particular lecture on udemy that would be on the top left
corner.
It will be prompting you saying there are available resources for this lecture.
If you click on it you can download this spring projects dot zip file unzip the contents of it and
you will see all these projects.
I'll be updating these contents as I add more sections in the future.
For example if you go to Spring core you will find the source folder and the pom dot xml the maven
configuration file under the SRC we have the entire Java code as well as the spring configuration
in here so you can always compare your classes that use once you start working on the hands on lectures.
If you have any issues or any errors you can see what's wrong by comparing your code with the code inside
these projects.
And if you want to import them into eclipse goto the eclipse IDE right click goto import click on import
here and type in existing Maven projects you should import them as existing Maven projects.
Next browse to that folder I have it under Documents spring projects Select a particular project
hit open.
I already have that project here that is the reason it's not enabled.
But in your case if you don't have the spring core project in your Eclipse IDE you will see this enable
select it hit finish and that project will be imported into eclipse.
But I don't want you to use the ready made projects.
I want you to code along with me in parallel and only if you have any issues you should be referring to
these completed projects.