This lecture I will walk you through the simple steps that you are going to follow in the next few lectures
to implement the user registration use case.
By then they will cease paying NBC and autumn inaction and doing the first step is to create them even
project in Eclipse and update the bomb dot ex-model with the dependencies.
Secondly will configure the front controller or the dispatcher solve for our MVC application by creating
it.
Bob Daut accessible we are going to reuse several components from earlier projects like Labrada example
and even spring configuration.
Third step is to come up with this bring configuration file with them which will configure the autumn
stuff starting with Hibernate template which needs session factory data source and finally the view
resolver for spring MVC.
So all in one configuration file.
Last but not least we will code and we get to the coding portion.
I'll explain the steps in detail but at the high level it will create the middle class create the data
access layer which will use the hibernate template.
Then a new layer will be introducing a new layer and a set of interface and classes.
So is this layer.
And finally the controller layer or the UI layer so will do all this in the next few lectures.