Do work on the spring NBC and autumn use case which is user registration you need to use that table
in the database.
That is what exactly you are going to create in this lecture download this spring.
MBC autumn Darby XTi from the resource section open.
What if I wrote a text editor grab the contents of it copy it go to my SDL workbench open up a new qwerty
tab.
Paste the contents.
Change this to your database.
Name my database name is my DB.
As you know by now execute that with just the database.
The second statement is to create a table with three fields.
The table name is user he has an ID in name and email.
We are keeping it simple Selecta execute.
That creates a user table go a select statement which you will be using again later on.
Right now there is no there are no records in the user table.