In this lecture he will walk on the very first step which is to create them him project and update the
bomb dot example or to eclipse Filemon you knew Mavin project you had to create it may have an application
next door and select the default option scroll down and go to May an archetype that Python webapp next
with a name call it putting MVC or R M and B C for a model view controller or item for object relational
mapping inish.
And that will create a new project for us.
The very first step is to get rid of this error.
You know why that happens.
It's because of this dependency is already already done it.
When you work on the spring MBC project right click go to properties search for run times click on target
at run times and Apache Tomcat.
OK that will resolve that error.
Next open the Bombarnac someone and let's update it by adding someone figuration from the previous projects.
Go to the spring MBC project open up the palm file click on the last tab about a click to maximize.
You can copy starting from properties all the way till end of burled copy that come back but the new
project start from dependencies.
Go to the end of it and paste what you have copied to the Control shift.
If you format we that may have an compiler plugin as well as we have the spring.
MBC dependency.
We also need the spring autumn dependencies.
So go to the autumn project spring
autumn expanded open the bombard X-amount
lofts tab again and maximize it.
All we need is the spring autumn hibernate core and my squirrel character copied those three dependencies.
The spring quarter and spring context we get it for free when we add the spring.
Bambi MBC.
We have successfully added all the dependencies.
The first one is putting in.
You know why we need it to work on the UI layer.
We need to bring MBC trans pulls all the other dependencies.
It requires spring.
Autumn of course to use Hibernate.
Hibernate template hibernate core has all the hibernate core and a squirrel character.
This is the driver profile file JTB see Driver Josephite right click on the project go to may even do
it.
Update Project hit OK and maven will resolve everything and we don't see errors anymore.
So he have successfully completed the very first step.