The second step is to update the web dot ECOMIL file by adding dispatcher.
So let's go back to Eclipse and that's spring NBC or go to a sarcy mean webapp web.
Enough have been put on the Web got a sample file right now.
It has very few elements in here.
Open up the spring MVC project go to as SEE main webapp Labrinth Labrador sambal.
You are welcome to copy paste everything or you can start typing.
I suggest you do it at least one more time so that you remember what goes into the library.
Select is the first element.
Give it the names of let my fun name is DISPATCHER You can do whatever name you want.
Next is selve left and class.
You can search for the dispatcher select by hitting control shift key or go to disrupt R-TX symbol and
drop this name along with the package name.
Ambac Bastet.
Save it next is the select mapping cell.
Let mapping copy the cell name from here.
And the second element is.
I'll let you waddle pattern one forward slash just like how we have use of the word pattern.
You can also use other water patterns like Slash MBC if you want to but then we'll have to include that
in Alaba requests that we want to go through the dispatcher so late.
So in this Lechter you have successfully finished the second step which is to configure the dispatcher
servlet.