In this lecture area will work on the PERDER an important step which is to create the spring configuration
file and Wajir the hibernate template beans as well as the way you resolve our beans in it.
You have already done these two separately when we were on spring putting autumn and spring.
And we see.
So let's get started by going to eclipse the naming convention we need to follow is the name of ourselves
left in the dark which is.
Dispatcher fun so that dot Exxon-Mobile the dispatcher so will search for a file with that name on the
classpath.
So let's reuse some of our earlier configuration.
Go to the spring.
Autumn all the way to product or best package.
Copy this conflict got Exxon-Mobile come back to our spring NBC autumn go to the web that actually been.
Bastet reichlich rename it to dispatcher hyphen Soldat example this Patcha hyphen.
So let dot Exxon-Mobile hit.
OK open that dispatcher Let need this context confidence can we'll come back to it and give it the right
packages.
Were already aware of all these beans you know configure them and you worked on spitting autumn hibernate
template is what we are going to use inside our doll class when we create it.
We had to of this high but the template and that template depends on session factory and the session
factories the local Sishen factory being from spring.
It needs a data source which is configured up here which takes a class name of the driver that you want
to connect to the database the user name and password.
And also there are couple more properties the hibernate properties where we give with the ballot form
as well in my case this class is responsible for generating the sequel queries and this flag through
here through hibernate choice Google tells hibernate that it will display all the queries that it creates.
Finally we have annotated classes property configured for decision factory is where we configure or
tell hibernate about all over entities are Mardell classes.
We'll come back to this configuration later on and we'll change these back names.
We'll fix them once we create those classes in the next lecture.
We will configure the view resolver.