In this lecture we'll grab the viewer resolver from our spring NBC project and we'll wire up inside
our new dispatch of solar dart.
I'm all for spring NBC Wadham project expand the spring MBC project go to the dispatcher so Legarda
ex-model and grab this bean which is the view resolver been copied come back to the new dispatcher.
So let go all the way to the end.
Bastet control shift the format.
And you know how the internal resource the resolver works.
This is the class from spring which is also the complete view name given due just have you name it.
It is all the complete pop and extension.
So here we can figure out the prefix which is the location.
Insert off using views.
Let's change it to just piece this time just for a difference.
This piece and the extension is still going to be d'arte just be we we're going to leave that alone.
So this if you resolver will append or prefix whatever view we get from the controller with this and
it'll suffix it with Dot.
Just.