In this lecture I will walk you through the simple coding steps that you will be following in the next
few lectures to create our application.
The very first step is to create a moral class called user that represents that database table will
mark this moral class with the hibernate annotations the JPA annotations to make it entity so that Hibernate
can stick to the database and read it back from the database.
Next we'll start courting our players for the application starting with data access layer.
So we just layer and then that controller the data access layer will how that user doll which is an
interface implemented by user impulse.
You already know this pattern you use it in spring JTB Z as of last spring or autumn it uses the hibernate
template to perform the database work using the model class that we create next to the services layer
typically holds the business logic will create a user service and use a service impellor which implements
that interface and it uses the user are dull.
Finally the controller class will use the services provided the methods provided by the user service.
So each layer here depends on our users.
The other layer they have it has a relationship and within the layer they have an easy relationship
has an easy let's get started in the next lecture by creating all the classes and interfaces for these
layers across these layers.
First we'll carry the mordent then in the next few letters we will create all the classes and then we'll
implement the methods.