In this lecture you will create the first class in our application which is the model or the entity
which represents the database table called user that we have three columns ID name and email so we are
going to have three properties in our entity order the spring MBC autumn project started by creating
a SIRC main job.
Right now there is no job for her to carry our score.
So right click on this SHC mean resources say new archosaurs folder click on either search for for it
to select that click Next select mean SIRC mean and direct.
We want a folder called Java finish and this is where all our source code will go.
The very first place will be new class caudate user Bakkies name com dot dot dot spring dot spring MVC
Autum dot our use case which is use up dot NBP.
That is where I want to put all of our entities.
There is only one entity in this use case finish this and it will have three fields but i private end
Id wait in name where it should be private string name and finally private string email serach them
all or the source Jenrette getters and setters.
Select All I want it to be after email it.
OK I can do a lot of effort to format.
Go to Sorsogon generate the two string method.
Ok control shift to format.
We have created the class but we need to mark them with the JP annotations to make it into t so that
Hibernate can map this class to a database row and the fields to database columns at NDB is the very
first annotation and mandatory annotation if you remember from javac start with the stents.
Second the ID should be marked with it.
I'll be back.
Persistence.
These two are compulsory this usually represents a primary key in the database.
Next here we have a name.
Let's check in the database.
We have a name here as well and email is email in the database so we don't need the.
Column attribute because the names here are the same.
They match their database names.
Similarly the table name here matches the class name so we don't have an issue there as well.
But if you want to.
You are welcome to use the at table annotation and within double quotes you can provide the table name
which is used to hit count on one imported from by extort all assistance.
You don't need to format and this should go into the value or the name of the people not a value in
this case.
It should be the name of the table that you've is name.
So in this lecture you have successfully created the model for our application which is user.