In this lecture you will start implementing the interfaces and classes across the layers of our application.
Starting with the user interface in the data access layer will only create the interfaces classes and
Arto out of them.
And in the next few lectures we'll implement the methods across these layers or do Eclipse.
Right click on the source for the new interface.
Start with User B.
All the packets should be user Daut deal finish.
It was that Adal create the implementation for this new class.
Package could be used right now are user Doud got IGMP implementation user.
I am is the class.
Click on Add and they should implement that user be able to select that.
OK.
Finish.
We don't have any metrics to implement this class with that repository annotation from Spring.
Because this is going to do all the database work and it needs some transactional support.
And it depends on if you look at the diagram it depends on hibernate template to do its work.
So let's add that as a dependency hibernate template control space use the one from hibernate 5
but neat template see it make sure that it is from the hibernate file package it controlled one generate
of setters.
OK.
Similarly create the services Slayer class right click new start with the interface user service is
the class package com dot dot user dot service or services finish
and create the implementation for the service new class.
It was a service I am click on and it was a service
that interface hit finish
and we need to market with it so we annotation from spring.
So the Dow was Makara with repository.
This obviously is micro with ex-service and the service.
If you look at that Agonum it depends on the user or Tao to do its work so that user interface here
will be injecting the implementation are automatically splitting will inject the implementation later
on.
It was that or Dow Dow and market with it auto wired annotation similarly copy this on the dollar immobiliser
and we need to markhor hibernate template with it.
Ottaway location I'm back with the service make this private control one agenda getters and setters.
Okay.
Format it.
So we have successfully created two layers.
The Dow and the services.
Let's go to the controller layer which is our UI and the final layer in our application right click
new Plus you know we don't need any interface name is user control.
Package.
Com dot dot it's being autem NBC Autum dot dot CON-TROLL finish in the controller class should be macrobid
it controller annotation I'm spinning.
You said your type annotation again and this depends on the user service.
So they use that in the controller user.
So this is the interface garlics service and market with auto wired annotation and gendered that getters
and setters
formatted controls you have to do that.
So you have completed all the layers creating the interfaces and classes and also why adding the dependencies.