From this lecture we will start creating them methods across these layers starting with the Dow.
Leah the services are the matters in the Data Access Layer are used by the services.
Let's do that.
In this lecture and we'll start working on the controller layer in the next one or two clips what would
they use or Tao.
And had a method called inte introduced in Dejah create.
Text that use the model object user
and they use the registration happens when we want to save the record database.
This is the method that should be invoked.
Now where we use our Dalrymple it control one wherever we see read and implemented amateur's or to create
matter control.
We have already implemented this method in project early and out hibernate template d'arte save and
pass the entity to it.
And it returns a signed statement to a new local variable returns a serializable object which is in
picture type cast to be Carlat result and return that result back all in one single line.
So we have successfully implemented the Create Mathare.
Now go to the services class which is user we sit in or he has a service implement or create them at
their altimeter which unsane Dejah you can call it create or you can call it save or anything you want.
It need not be the same name as the method in their the user user on one import user or on package or
their service impulse control one and an unimplemented methods.
Here we are going to use the Dow.
So insert them at 38 or Daut create pass the user and you can add the write down statement here.
Get rid of this written control.
Delete the record.
So what are the always running these classes are these methods that are running back.
In addition we can house some business logic here.
I will show you some examples later on.
And this meant there can be market with it transactional annotation from spring we haven't been able
annotations in our configuration will do that but we can mark this method with transactional instead
of mocking the method.
We can also have a transactional here but it's always a good practice to have it.
So we just layer because we can how multiple database statements that might be executed from within
here.
And we want all that to be in one single transaction.