In this lecture will implement the controller matters so that our application will be wired and ready
to go and do and go to eclipse go to use the controller.
We're going to get some help from the earlier project which is putting MVC because we have already implemented
the very same methods in the use of controller in that project or do the controller package in spring
MVC open that controller grabbed these two methods we are going to modify one of them copy them come
back to the new controller.
Those methods are shift to format and closed the controller so that will not modify that accidentally.
Maximize delete this model object from the old project control the control one on the user imported
from our new package in the new project.
The very first method in the controller is going to return the registration page to the end user when
he accesses.
There you are.
If we lose the registration page in the water and we'll send him a page called use the range which will
have the DML form.
So copy that use the range from the earlier project as sarcy webapp.
We have been for views use the range dark speak copy that close this project can put the new ones being
NBC Warham or SIRC webapp that Benford.
But this time it's going to be Diest piece because if you open the dispatcher so that we can figure
out the resolver with the prefix Verband of slash GSB.
So right click on have been new for the GSB for the finish.
Paste the DSP that you have copied which is use the range got TSB which has the form and this submit
this gets submitted to the register user and in the controller we have a matter mapped to registered
user or register user which basically immortal attributes being container automatically takes the form
data that comes in puts it into this object because we have marked it with a model attribute annotation
and we also use a model map to send the user data back to the UI.
But this time we are not going to send the end user data only saying that they return value from that
create method.
So get rid of these first two lines.
We had lots of changes to his rage result in a second.
For now for us we are going to call the service dark save the matter on the service.
So whatever he has that information comes in we are taking that and passing it to the service manager
control one.
And this guy returns the end result back big that result and create a string
or create than dot and attribute result and the value will be user created with 80 plus pass the result
back whatever Hibernate is returning us back.
The idea that we are sending a message to you why and instead of using a new UI we're going to send
it back to the same user rage page and we will display this message below the file will do that change
in the way in the next lecture.
In this lecture we have successfully implemented the controller matters to show the initial UI which
has the history of form.
And when the user submits it it comes to this particular matter where we are taking the model saving
it to the database and then setting a result on the model which goes back to the UI using model map.
Inside that we have a message along with the result that comes back from the same operation.