We have used annotations everywhere in our project.
But we haven't enabled them in their dispatcher so servlet dart example to do that.
Go to the dispatcher.
Let go up top right here right after the bean starting element.
You know how to do it using text call and component scan and the base package.
In this case we have our POJO classes spread across the different packages for the different layers.
So we need to pick a base package which could be putting NBC Autum up to that or even user because controller
Dow Dow temple and services they are all sub packages off the user which is already you scarce or right
click on any one of the packages.
Autorefractor rename say that is better so that's fine.
Grab it up to the user handsel
come back to the dispatcher servlet paste that package up to the user and you can close this context
component's can right there.
Contradictive to format.
So this spring that you should scan all the back pages of this particular package.
This package as well as its sub package is.