Before we see our application end to end in this lecture one small change of a dark example opened up
our product someone and up top here you see a dot by DTD which inconsistently causes problems with days.
If we have it here the wrong then the DSP expression of language won't work either we need to upgrade
it to the latest So let version or completely get rid of it.
So I'm going to delete it for now and have the app element that's it.
Ready to run that allegation right click on the index start GSB or on the project as add on.
So it finished to start the.
That will apply the application and launch it in the browser of Eclipse copy that link.
Let's use Chrome or any of your favorite browsers.
Paste the link and we'll go to the index dot GSP.
Go back to eclipse go to use our controller grab the registration page you are-I come back.
Delete this in Nexstar DSP paste registration page that is the right answer.
Registration page that will take us through the registration page with three fields and the form entered
an ID lets say 7 8 9.
Name is parrot and email is best at best dot com hit the submit button when we hit the submit button.
That request goes to the controller and we see an ID coming back with 7 8 9 with a database to ensure
that the data is really saved.
Execute select start from user execute and we do have an ID 7 8 9 user is part and his email is test
that test dot com so the control went to the controller to start with the user controller
and it displayed the user registration page.
Then we have entered the details.
Hit the submit button.
Then the request came with the second method because this is the action in the form.
Spring automatically converts the incoming form data into a model object because we have McBeth using
Mardell attribute.
We have taken that model object past it to the service the service done.
In walks the matter and the document uses hibernate template to save it to the database and it returns
the result back which is the ID which we have passed in that ID comes back as the result goes back to
the controller in the controller.
We are taking the ID setting it into the model map which we are creating and sending the result back
saying user created it id and we are pushing the portal back to the same registration page which is
being displayed here along with the reason.