In this lecture you will implement the methods in the Dow and the services which will load all the users
in the user table and display them on the UI.
We'll start with that here then the services layer and then we'll implement the controller and view
in the next lecture.
Go to the user now add a new method that returns a list of users call it find use this
import less hit Control run imported from Jacquard.
It'll go to the user.
Impulse control one at unimplemented amateur's delayed that to stop the Tom-Kat if it's running otherwise
it's going to keep reloading the context.
Was that a impulse to find the users we remember the operation on the hibernate template hibernate template.
Dark Lord all is the matter and we need to tell it.
What is the A.P. class.
In our case it is user dot plus.
And that will automatically return a list of users assigned to a new local variable.
We can either do that or simply add a written statement here.
Delete this written null and that matter will return a list of users back to the Soviet laya users so
we start Java do the same here.
List of users.
And you can follow this method get users.
It need not be the same name as the Dow.
It's up to us to design our business logic methods control one import the list go to use so we simple
control one are unimplemented amateur's and the return dao not find users that set a single line.
So in this lecture we have successfully implemented the load user's method so that we can get all the
users in the database into a list of users in the dark layer or the data layer.
And so we said earlier in the next few lectures we will implement the controller and the methods.