In this lecture you will implement the controller.
After that we'll use to use a service load the users from the database and send it back to the view.
It will send that list back with The View will create the view in the next lecture.
Go to use a controller copy the very first method which users get by default.
Bastet Lord you can call it the users are get users is the matter also change that you are pattern to
get users
get to use this method we'll call the service Daut get users which returns a list assignable local variable.
And we need a model map so that we can send this list back to the UI.
So in the matter parameter we need to define a border map order so that will go back to the UI into
the model map model dot and attribute the last one the string.
The key will be users and the value will be the users which is the list here.
So we are going to send that list back to the UI and return it to a page call display users which will
create in the next lecture display users.