This lecture you will create the display users start a GSB and use JFT or tags Jervoise and the tag
label inside it to display the list of users to do that.
Before you create the speed there are a couple of steps we need to do to protect someone or three steps
in the product simle we have removed the DTD on the root element earlier.
Let's add the proper root element from the resources section of this lecture.
You can download this.
D.
D a lot.
B XTi.
Once you download it from the resource section the very first step is to grab this root element which
is webapp.
Copy it will back to Bartik someone select this webapp that have an app.
Paste the new element so that we have the root element with the three dot or name off.
So let it be.
Second step is to add the Mabon dependencies.
So grab these two dependencies SPL and standard tag libraries.
I cover a lot more details on tag libraries.
In my case be sublets and database of course but it's this much knowledge is enough to work on it.
You need these dependencies in the palm up open it with the dependency section all the way to the end
based on new dependencies.
Control shift to format and Mebane will pull those dependencies for us.
The very first time now we are ready to create the DSP goto source webapp.
This piece right click new DSP and the name of the file should be display.
Users Dorte GSB
to use the Taggett we need to include the tag Libert data too.
You can copy this last piece from here pasted right next to the very first line which is the page Darick
to.
This is the tag lib namespace and this is the prefix for it.
Now we can start using the bag liberally inside our DML page to display all the users are the result
that comes back to do that.
Use C colon for each.
These are the core tags.
C stands for core and these are the core tags in the SDL which we can use to display the object data
inside the display page without writing job or code Seacole and for each
items is that rebute is equal to within double quotes.
Use the expression language of DSP Dala within our brackets.
The name of the variable inside the user control or whatever we have set into the model.
Go back to the controller we have set it as users so retrieve that list go back to the display use or
start DSP users automatically.
This tag will pull users from the request using request or get a reboot and it will loop through it.
We can assign each user in this list where variable is equal to within double court user.
So this object will carry each user in this list inside the loop.
We can get that data using the expression language I can simply see Colon.
We don't have to do that simply use the expression language dollar symbol within flower brackets.
Use that is the bean thought I'd be.
Similarly we can get name and salary well formatted better Letran name and the last one is e-mail.
Let's check the B names by going to use a dot Java ID name an email in the display.
That's not GSB we are moving through the list of users that comes back in the model and taking the each
user object in the list and displaying their details.
We'll run this program in the next lecture and we'll format it better.