This lecture will test the display users call.
We have just written by accessing the controller from the web browser to do that right click or otherwise
run on server finish.
Once that allocation starts then grabbed the or to crawl onto our favorite browser.
Paste the warm spring autumn slash display get users get users is what we are used you capital in the
controller that that will go to the controller all the way to services down there and it loads our user
data to see the ID the name and that email id.
Let's do a better formatting.
Go back to the days page.
We'll put it inside of his DML table outside the for loop create the table rabbit.
We landed after the each each right here for each object in the list are for each row in the database
we need to create the table row.
Let's create the table row and heading outside here outside the for loop ph for table Hading knows the
hitch IB is the first field.
Copy that.
And our people are hurting bestit couple of times.
Second is name.
Third is e-mail Similarly for each of these here we'll have it Tia closed that table row at that and
B are last year and for each of these fields are they the BE table data and close table data right there.
Similarly for the other two table data open table data.
Close it
close the table data control shift to format.
So we have successfully included a hasty table to add a border if we want to border is equal to 1 save
it go back to the web browser load it again refresh the browser and you see it in a hasty multi-table
if you want to you can insert more cards and you can see that in action as well.