You have successfully created the user and also displayed the list of users on the UI in this lecture
you are going to sort the users that we are displaying on the UI the list we are returning from the
user so is Imbolc can be sought.
But how do implement the compatible interface on our model so that it can be used for sorting.
So go to the user dot Java and implements compatible if you remember from core Java compatible is an
interface that should be implemented and the gender type in this case is use that we want to compare
to use that objects and sort them had control one had and implemented amateur's change this idea to
in Bija so that our life will be a lot more easier in Bija you can change it here.
Its ok to really do the art of boxing Pharez.
But when we implement the Compared to matter it would be a lot easier.
Change this parameter name to user return.
We can say this Daut I want this sorted by ID.
So this dot dot com I can use the compare to method which is available on the wrapper type 2 user dot
ID.
So I am combating and retaining the IDs.
You can also sorted by name and email but for now sort it by the ID start the server have stopped myself.
So lets start it if its up and running for you can restart it.
And if you go to the controller I want to add a few more cards in the database right now I only have
one card in my database.
Lets add a few more so that we can see sorting and action.
So registration page is that you are and we should be using right click on eyes on server finish that
we launched here.
So paste that you are our copy this you or I'll go to Chrome which is much better than the eclipse default
browser.
Paste that link.
Grab that link from Eclipse come back.
Paste it right at the beginning and it should be a registration page at the end and that will take us
to the form which we can submit and create.
Couple more users IDs one name is John John at gmail dot com.
His email addy Jaun at gmail dot com.
Submit and it creates a user with ID one cleared one more to Bob is the name Bob at gmail dot com submit.
Now we have three the cards in the database.
Select and we have three cards.
Let's see how they would come back with a UI and sort of register page.
It should be.
Get users you Capital get users will feature the users and displayed in a table if you see they are
not sorted by AB 789 comes first then one and then to go back to the Soviet mentor or the Soviets this
class which is US-Soviet simple.
And then the get users do their collections Daut sort Corrections is a little class that can start a
lot of collections.
And this collection starts sort of wide type.
So saying this variable hit condoled one beyond our find users should be assigned to a variable then
we should start them.
I'm going to stop my server squad it up so that you can see it clearly.
The word art find users assign it by hitting control one local variable call it users get rid of this
sort of dump collection starts sort users and then return users.
Now stop the server
and 1:06 back up or.
Go back to the web browser refresh this page which is get users
and this time and it fit just that a card.
It should sort them by.
I'd say how successfully implemented that compatible interface on our model of class and you how Sautter
that ecards based on their IDE.