In this lecture, I will walk you through this simple user registration usecase that you will be implementing
in the next few lectures and send that data from the UI to the Controller.
The very first step is to implement a userRegistration.jsp which the enduser will access through
the Controller.
The Controller will send this view back.
The user will then enter the information and submit the form which will once again go to the Controller
at which point the Controller will create an instance of the User class that we create.
We create this User class. The Controller will automatically create an object of this User class when
this form is submitted and it will handover that object, this particular object to the Controller method,
marked with @ModelAttribute annotation.
So we are going to create a Controller with two methods. The first method will simply return this userReg.jsp.
The second method is what we'll mark with @ModelAttribute, the parameter will be marked with @ModelAttribute.
It will retrieve the user information and simply display it on the console and send a response back
to the user.