In this lecture, you will start working on the user registration usecase by creating the user model, that
is User.java and userReg.jsp page. Go to Eclipse, go to the source folder,
right click on it. New -> class and this should go into the dto package.
So com.bharath dot, select the dto package under springmvc. The name of the class is User. Finish. And this
class will have three fields,
id, name and email that are required for his registration, his Id,
usually we generated it in our application.
But for now let the user enter this. Private int id, private String name, private String email, three fields
id, name and email.
As always select them and generate the getters and setters. Source -> Generate getters and setters. Select all,
and I want them after the email.
OK.
Also generate the toString method.
Control+shift+f to format it. And we have the model with the three fields.
Next, we are going to create the useReg.jsp which will have the HTML form from which, using
which the user will submit the user data to the Controller.
Let's get started by creating, to create the userReg, go under views, right click, new -> JSP.
Call it userReg for registration, dot jsp. Maximize, within body we'll have three input types or four,
three text fields, text boxes and one submit button.
So get started by using the HTML form. Action will be,
addUser or call it registerUser.
This will be the mapping that we'll be using in the Controller later on, registerUser.
And method is equal to post.
Within the form first is Id, colon, input type is equal to, text is equal to, we'll come back
to the name in the second. Close it right
there. Copy the whole line and paste it three more times.
Second is name,
third is email.
And finally we don't need a label for it.
It's the submit button. Input type is equal to submit, name is equal to register and put all these
three or four fields inside a pre element that will keep them in an order.
Control+x, we'll end that pre right here. Control+shift+f to format.
So we have successfully created the form.
The names here,
if you remember should exactly match the fields in the model here.
So id, name and email. Id, name and the last field is email. Only then the container will be able to map
these fields into our model
once it creates the user object later on when the request comes in.
So you have successfully created the model and the corresponding JSP page.