In this lecture, you'll work on the next step which is to create a UserController that will return this
user registration dot jsp to the end user
when you hit a URL.
So first he needs to access the form and then he can submit the form.
So we are going to do and handle that portion in the Controller. Go to Eclipse, minimize, right click on the
Controller or a Controller package. Say new -> class, UserController, finish. Mark it with the @Controller annotation
right away before we forget that. @Controller from Spring stereotype.
Next we'll start with one method that returns a ModelAndView. Public ModelAndView from Spring.
showRegistrationPage, a long method name. Within this method we'll create a new
ModelAndView. Hit control+1, assign statement to a new local variable. ModelAndView is fine.
ModelAndView.setViewName.
All we are doing in this method is returning a view.
The very first view the user should see, which is userReg.jsp.
So user, r is capital, reg. And return that ModelAndView object back. Control+d, do the
RequestMapping. @RequestMapping, within brackets, double quotes,
you can use whatever URL you want, say register or registrationPage. So users will access this using
this particular URI.
This method will be run and we'll return a userReg.jsp.