We have successfully completed our usecase and ready to see the application flow end to end. To test
it, go to Servers, right click, restart the Tomcat server so that everything is reloaded and we
are clean.
Once it restarts, you can right click on the application, do a Run as -> run on server. Or if you have a browser
open already,
simply go there and change the URL.
The URL we should be using is registrationPage.
That is where the flow starts.
First we'll access the registrationPage, go to the browser, at the end paste registrationPage after
springmvc, p is capital. Enter, now the request goes to the UserController,
the very first method because that is what is mapped to registrationPage.
It returns a userReg as view. The ViewResolver will append the .jsp and the location and
we see the output which is the form, the userReg.jsp. Enter some details, 123,
the name is John.
Email is john@bob.com.
Now when we hit submit it will again go to the Controller because in the userReg.jsp,
we have mapped it to registerUser. So it will go to the Spring Container first. The Spring will create
a corresponding model object for this form,
because we have used the @ModelAttribute. It will come to this method because the registerUser is
mapped to this method it will create a model object called user. Take
the form fields,
whatever we are submitting from here, create that object. So hit submit and you will see it in action.
It comes to the Controller, goes to that method, gives it the model object after creating it, taking the form
fields, setting the values which we are displaying on the console here.
And after that, it goes back to the same registrationPage because that is what exactly we are doing
in the Controller. Here we are setting the view as userReg. This is where we are displaying the details on the
console.
So in this lecture, you have successfully finished sending the data from the Controller or from the
view to the Controller, from the UI to the controller.