In the previous lecture, you have seen how to send the data from the Controller back to the UI but
when we send the response back,
we were sending it back to the same registrationPage once the registration completes successfully.
Instead of that, let's complete the flow end to end. That is, from the UI to the Controller and from
the Controller to an other new UI.
Go back to the UserController. Instead of sending it to the UserRegistrationPage, we'll send it
to a regResult, r capital, regResult will be our new view which will simply say user registered
successfully and it will display the model which we are going to set into the ModelAndView.
So here into this ModelAndView, stop the Tomcat server. Come back, dot, addObject.
Set the user information again so that we can access it in the next view.
Double click to minimize, create a new view.
Right click on the view and the view name should be regResult. JSP file,
reg, r capital, result, dot jsp.
The title is User Registration Response
or Result. And within the body, say User Registered Successfully.
User details are, you can display them however you want.
I am going to simply use the JSP expression and say request.getAttribute and the key that we
have used in the Controller is user. So use that key and the toString method will be invoked and it should
be displaying the user details. Go to the server, right click, restart or just talk because I have stopped it.
Go back to the browser
within Eclipse or even outside Eclipse. Start the registration,
let's say test is the, or 1234 is the id, test is the name, test@gmail.com is the
email id. Hit the submit button.
This time the registration completes and it goes back to the result page. Instead of going back to the
registrationPage,
now it goes to a new page, the JSP which we have just created. And it displays User Registered Successfully.
User details are and the user object.
So you have completed the flow end to end. You have used both sending data from the UI to the Controller as
well as sending data from the Controller to the UI in one single mini application.