In this and the next lecture, you'll learn the second way of sending data from the UI to the Controller
and accessing it. It is by using the request parameters or the query parameters. We send the data by
appending it at the end of the url using the query string, that is the question mark syntax followed
by data as key and value pairs. Each of these key value pairs is separated by an ampersand symbol.
Once we send that data, we can retrieve it in our Controller by using the @RequestParam annotation
from Spring.
Give it the key and Spring will automatically retrieve the value and it will set it into the Controller's
method parameter.
So we mark our method parameters using this annotation and Spring will do the rest of the work.
DT here stands for data type. It could be integer, double, string, etc.
For example, here I have a id field as a Controller method parameter and I mark it with
@RequestParam("id"), Spring will
do these two for us automatically. It will invoke the HTTP servlet request.getParameter internally, use the
key which we provide here, retrieve the value which by default is String. It will then parse it into the appropriate
type. Here I'm using integer.
So it will use the integer.parseInt and parse it into the appropriate type and set the value into
this parameter. We can then use that parameter inside our Controller method.
If invalid data comes in, for example here I am using integer
but in the URL, if string comes in xyz, abc value comes in,
then Spring will throw a 400 HTTP error code back in the response.
Similarly, if a key is not provided by default when we use the @RequestParam, Spring assumes that that particular
key should be there in the URL.
In this case if id doesn't come in as a query parameter in the URL, Spring will
once again send a 400 response back. So to avoid that we can mark the request parameters for required
is equal to false. Use an additional attribute called required. By default it is true.
So you need to turn it off by using false as value.
And we can also provide default values.
Sometimes we can provide the key in the URL but if the value is not provided then we have a problem
again on primitive types.
That is where we use default values. If no value comes in the URL, Spring will automatically use whatever
value we provide here.
Last but not least, the order doesn't matter.
That is, the order of the URL parameters here,
key values and the order in which we define these parameters on the Controller methods doesn't matter.
What matters is the key that we use here,
and the keys that come in the URL.