In this lecture, you will send the query parameters using the URL
and you will retrieve them on the server side in the Controller using the @RequestParam annotation.
So let's get started by going to Eclipse, create a new Controller. Right click, new -> class, call it
RequestParamsController, finish. Mark it with @Controller annotation from Spring stereotype package.
Create a new method, public,
this method will simply take the URL parameters and it will display them on the Tomcat console. Public
ModelAndView from Spring, showData is the method name. Mark it with @RequestMapping and provide a mapping,
showData, forward slash, showData is the URL that I want to use. And this should return a new
ModelAndView. We'll set the view in a second
although it's not required. To retrieve the URL parameters, we need to use the @RequestParameter or
@RequestParam annotation on the method parameters on the controller. Let's define the method parameters.
Int id is the first one, string name
comma double salary.
We can define whatever data types we want.
Once we have the parameters defined, we used the @RequestParam annotation on each of those parameters.
And within brackets, give it a name.
This name should match the key that we use in the URL, when the query parameters come in from the browser.
Copy that, RequestParam, paste it next to String name as well as double salary.
Change the names to name and sal, instead of using salary,
I'm going to use sal, sal in the query parameters. So this key here should match the key used in the URL.
Once you have mapped it, use a sysout, display the details. Id colon, +id. Copy that line, paste it
a couple of times. Name is the second one, name and finally salary, sal or salary.
That's the variable name, control+shift+f to format.
And let's forward it to some view.
Forward it to userReg.
Doesn't matter.
You can create a new view and forward it.
But our goal is to just retrieve the user query parameters and to display them on the console.
So I am forwarding it to the userReg.jsp To see this in action, right click, restart the server.
While it restarts,
go back to the browser, grab the earlier URL, one of the earlier URLs from the browser.
Open any textpad or any text editor of your choice. Paste that URL, change it from springmvc/registerUser
to showData, d capital, slash
we need to pass three parameters, not slash. It will be a question mark. Id is equal to 123.
And name is equal to John and ampersand symbol,
sal is what I think we have used,
if you go back to the RequestParamsController, sal is what we should use here as well, is equal to
let's say 72.5 per hour maybe.
Copy that URL, come back to Eclipse.
Or you can open it in Chrome as well,
or any other web browser. Paste that here.
Enter and you will see that it goes back to the registrationPage.
That is not what we care. Go go to the Tomcat console
here. Maximize it and you'll see all the three values. Id is 123, name is John and salary is 72.5.
So you have successfully sent data using query parameters and you how retrieved it in the Controller
using @RequestParam annotation. The Spring container has automatically taken the values, used the
appropriate parse methods and it has set those values into the method parameters.