In this lecture, you'll work on the last and key step which is to handle the incoming form data. Within
the Controller we're going to create a new method,
use the @ModelAttribute inside that method and take the object that the container creates on the fly.
So let's get started by going to Eclipse. Create a new method, you can copy this method from here.
Paste it, call it registerUser
and the URL mapping here should be what we have used in the userReg.jsp. Call it registerUser.
Copy that, come back,
use that mapping here.
And this annotation has an other attribute.
So before we use it, assign this to value comma, there is a method attribute, is equal to, use a class
from Spring. RequestMethods is the class which has constants defined. It's a enum right here,
from spring framework, dot post. By default the method is get.
But in this case, this method should handle the HTTP post because in the JSP page that is what we
have used when the form gets submitted. Come back to the Controller.
We need a new ModelAndView. The ViewName, we are going to send it back to the same registration page.
Once the model, we display the model, we'll send it back to the same registration page.
That's fine. Within this registerUser,
we need a parameter which will be annotated with @ModelAttribute from Spring and that param in our
case, we know that it's the user. User user
is the model. Hit control+1,
import user from our own package, not from any other package. @Model, control+space, attribute and
we can give it a name, whatever name we want.
Call it user and the container will create this user object and when we mark a particular parameter
with this annotation, it will inject it into the, or it will assign it to that parameter.
And within the method we can do a sysout, control+space, user. You are simply displaying the user.
So in this lecture, you have successfully implemented a method that handles the user registration.
We are simply displaying the user information that comes in. We have retrieved the object that the container
creates on the fly using the @ModelAttribute. And we are displaying it and then we are returning the
same registrationPage so that it'll go back to the same registrationPage after the, displaying the user
details.