In the previous lecture, you have successfully read and displayed the query parameters. In this lecture you
are going to learn two more attributes that we can use inside the @RequestParam.
Go back to the browser, and this time don't provide the salary details.
Get rid of the last parameter, hit enter, submit the form again and let's see what happens.
It says required double parameter salary. You get a HTTP 400 back because by default Spring
container wants everything that we mark with the @RequestParam annotation. To make them optional,
you can add a new attribute. Before you do that,
you need to assign this sal to a value.
If its two attributes are more than we have to use value is equal to sal
comma, required is equal to, within double quotes,
it's a boolean value.
So required is equal to false. By default
it is true.
Now you're going to see an other exception.
So go back to the browser, hit enter without providing salary. Once Tomcat restarts
let's try that again in the browser and we see a different exception this time.
Scroll down and it says optional double parameter, it is optional,
but salary is not present but cannot be translated into null. Because it's a primitive type,
it cannot be translated to null. Spring tries to assign a null value, it doesn't work.
So go back to the RequestParam's controller and provide a defaultValue.
The last attribute is defaultValue,
v capital is equal to, say 60. 60 is the default salary.
Save it and that should go inside double quotes.
Restart the server
just to make sure our changes are picked. Go back to the browser, hit Enter and this time you don't see any errors.
And if you see the console, id is 123, name is John
and the salary is the default salary. You can provide zero as well if you want to, any default value.
So in this lecture, you have learnt that you should always mark the fields as optional
if you don't want them and you should provide default values for primitive types because a null value
cannot be assigned by the Spring container to the primitive types. You can also try out by passing invalid
values.
For example if you pass in xyz for id you will also see an exception.