As you watch this video lecture, you through your web browser are acting as a RESTful client. And this
website is acting as a RESTful provider by streaming the video back to you.
All that on the HTTP protocol. REST which stands for Representational State Transfer, is a bunch of principles
or architectural guidelines and HTTP allows us to easily implement REST. In this lecture, you will
learn the key principles that make up REST and also how HTTP implements REST. No matter which web
application you take, it will allow the end users to perform the following four operations or any other
application to perform these four operations.
CREATE, READ, UPDATE and DELETE on its resources. From Facebook to Twitter, Gmail to Youtube, you will be
able to perform all these four operations.
That brings us to the very first RESTful principle which is Uniform Interface and Easy access.
HTTP provides a uniform interface to perform the CRUD operations using its HTTP methods.
Starting from POST, to create a resource, GET, to retrieve a resource or read a resource, PUT, to update
the resource and DELETE to delete a resource.
So once we learn these four methods, we can pretty much work with any application, any RESTful application
and create, read, update and delete the resources in it.
These are also known as VERBS,
HTTP VERBS.
Easy access, HTTP provides an easy access, easy and unique way to identify resources through it's
URIs and URLs.
For example, if we are working on an Employee management software, we can identify the employee resource
using /employees. To uniquely identify departments, you'll use /departments.
Now let's see how we can use the combination of the HTTP VERBS and NOUNS. These URIs or
URLs are known as NOUNS because they uniquely identify a resource.
Let's see how the combination of VERBS and NOUNS can be used to perform CRUD operations. To create an
employee,
we'll use the POST method with /employees and we will send in the employee data.
Here the employee name is bharath and his department is IT.
The method is POST and the URI is /employees. The REST provider will receive the request,
create that in the database and send a 201 Created HTTP status code along with the
entity that got created in the database. This resource here,
this URI is called a collection resource, because it is /employees.
It represents all the employees, a collection of employees.
We are adding a new employee to that collection.
If we have an id at the end of a particular employee, then that will become an item resource. For
example, to get the employee back
we'll use a GET method with the employees slash, the unique ID of that particular employee.
So this is known as a item resource.
Here is how the GET method will look like. GET/employees/1 that will get us the employee that
was just created in the database, with a 200 OK
HTTP response. You can also perform a GET on the collection resource, without this ID and that will
get us all the employees in the database back. Next is UPDATE.
We use a PUT method on the collection resource, on the item resource with the unique ID to perform a
HTTP PUT which will update the employee information. Here,
my department is getting updated from IT to psychology, a field of my interest and the response will be a 200 OK,
along with the updated information. Update does a complete update. That is, we need to pass in the
entire resource in the request.
We can do a partial, we can't send in partial fields. If we try to just send in the department in this
case, the name will be set to null.
That is where we use PATCH. The HTTP PATCH method supports partial updates on the item resource, we can
pass in partial information. In this case, I am not passing in the name, just the department and I will
get a response back with the complete updated entity or the patched entity back with a 200 status code.
Finally DELETE,
we use the HTTP DELETE. And that will delete the employee in the database.
The next important principle of REST is that our applications or RESTful providers should support multiple
formats. And HTTP allows us to do it very easily,
we can support XML,
JSON, plain text or any other format and the clients can tell what format they want using the HTTP
MIME types like text/xml, application/json, text/plain, hal/json as you would see
later on when you build the applications. So the key principle, the same application or the RESTful provider should
be able to provide the responses or it should be able to support multiple data formats.
To summarize, you have learnt three key principles of REST and how HTTP implements REST in this lectures,
starting with Single HTTP Interface or a unique interface.
HTTP supports a unique interface to perform CRUD operations using POST, PUT, GET, PATCH, DELETE and other
methods in the HTTP protocol also known as VERBS. We can easily identify and access resources
using the HTTP URLs and URIs.
That is the second principle of REST.
And finally, Multiple representations. REST, says that we should support, or whoever implements REST
should support multiple data formats and that can be easily supported using HTTP MIME types.