Creating RESTful web applications is very easy using Spring because you need not learn a new module.
You will be using the Spring MVC or the Spring WEB module to create a web application. And to create a RESTful
endpoint, we'll create a Controller class and mark it with
@RestController. Instead of simple Controller which you used to mark when you worked on the web applications,
here you'll mark it with @RestController annotation. And to map it to a path, you'll use @RequestMapping
which you are already aware of, from Spring Web.
And once you have the controller in place, this is your RESTful endpoint, and you can define as many
methods as you want in the controller
for your RESTful web service to serve.
And each of these methods will be marked with the appropriate annotation.
Each of these annotations bind your java methods to a incoming HTTP method from the client.
You can use a GET, POST, PUT, DELETE and so on. For each of the HTTP methods, there is a annotation from
Spring that you can use.
So it's that simple.
You'll define a controller, mark it with @RestController annotation, give it a path and then you can define
as many number of methods you want, you can define
paths, relative paths to
your methods and also bind them to the HTTP methods using these annotations.