The second step is to create a RESTful controller class that will act as a endpoint to our RESTful application.
To do that,
go to STS.
Right click on the src/main/java, New -> Class. Call it ProductController and put it in a package called
com.bharath.spring.controllers. Finish. Right now this is just a class. To make it Spring RESTful
controller, you have to mark it with @RestController annotation from springframework.web.
So you have added the maven dependency in the last project which was spring-boot-starter-web.
That is where this annotation resides.
That is the number one step. And then we have to define a root path for our controller.
That is where our clients will be accessing our RESTful services. To do that you'll use @RequestMapping.
Within double quotes, /products. That will be the URI that our clients will use to access this
particular controller and starting the next lecture,
you will define all the CRUD operations starting with getProduct.