In this lecture, you will implement the getProduct method that will return all the products in the database. We'll expose it
out as a RESTful API. To do that,
start with the public Iterable. So this method should return a iterable products.
I will tell you why
an iterable. public Iterable getProducts()
and we have to use the repository interface in here. First import the product, control+1, Import 'Product',
Next, start using productRepository. control+space, take the ProductRepository. Call it repository.
And mark it with
@Autowired annotation so that Spring will automatically inject this dependency for us. Then we can start
using it.
Copy the repository, go into your method, dot, findAll(). The repository has a findAll method that returns
all the products as a Iterable product.
You can convert it into a list, etc if you want to.
But I am returning an Iterable. Spring will automatically convert this into JSON.
That magic happens for us automatically. So return repository.findAll();
So the default data format for spring RESTful web services is JSON, it configures the Jackson adapters and
all that automatically.
The next important piece, mark this method with @GetMapping. Control+space,
@GetMapping, because we want to use the clients, to use the GET method to get all the products.
So you should tell that by using the @GetMapping annotation. So you have successfully implemented it. In the
next lecture, we'll test if this particular endpoint works by using Postman.