Before we launch our application and test it,
one small change is to move this SpringdatajpaApplication which is the starting point of our application,
to a package above it.
That is, I don't want it to be in com.bharath.spring.data, because when we run our application automatically
Spring will
scan this particular package and all its subpackages. So it will not
scan our controllers package because controllers is not a subpackage of com.bharath.spring.data, but it
is a subpackage of com.bharath.spring.
So let's move this to one level above.
Get rid of data because now our project deals with Spring data as well as Spring REST or
Spring web. Delete that, hit control+1, move it to com.bharath.spring.
Now we are good.
It should scan all the subpackages of com.bharath.spring. Launch our application. To do that, you can
right click, say Run As -> Spring Boot App.
Since we have included the web dependency, it will automatically launch our application on the embedded
Tomcat server and it starts on localhost8080.
And since we haven't mapped any web application route context, it will be localhost8080.
We can access our application at that URL. So launch Postman, our REST client. By default it will be
a GET method.
Start typing in the URL, localhost:8080/products.
That's the URL to access all the products.
Hit Send.
Click on that button and we get the one and only product we have in our database.
You have multiple products, as you can see it is JSON array.
So you have successfully implemented and tested a RESTful application, just the GET part so far.
We will be implementing and testing the rest of the methods in the next few lectures.