In this lecture you will implement a product creation, the CREATE method by using the PostMapping. To do that,
start with a new method, public create() is the method. It takes a Product product and it returns the
created product.
And within the method, we'll be using repository.
Rename this repository. I have spelled it wrong. If you have spelled it right,
you are awesome. Right click and I want to Refactor -> Rename it correctly. It's not respository, it should be
repository.
For some reason it couldn't rename it. So I changed it to repository.save, is the method
we want and pass it the incoming product in the request that the client will send and return it back.
So whatever is saved to the database, we are returning it back. And here, this product, this request parameter
should be marked with @RequestBody, that tells spring that this parameter is being expected from
the RequestBody in the post body. Control+1, import RequestBody from Spring. And the next and the last
important piece, mark this method with the @PostMapping this time.
So for creation, we use a HTTP POST method.
So we are telling that this particular method is being binded to the HTTP POST method,
and in the incoming POST request we'll get the product details as JSON. Spring will automatically
convert that into this object.
And we are taking that object and saving it into the database. In the next lecture, we'll test
this POST method.