In this lecture, we'll test our POST method. To do that,
stop the server.
It's already running, bring the app down and re-run it,
because we have made the code changes to implement CREATE. Once that's up,
go back to Postman. Click this plus button to open up a new tab. Go back to the previous tab,
grab the URL,
come back to the new tab, paste it.
Change this HTTP method from GET to POST. From the dropdown you can see all the HTTP methods here.
Click on Body, because we need to pass in the JSON in the POST request body, and select this raw.
Change the content type from text to application/json.
Go back to the previous tab and copy the contents of just the product.
No need of copying the square brackets, just from the starting flower bracket to the end up the brace.
Copy it, comeback.
Paste the contents.
Change the id to 2, name to IPhone and it's awesome,
atleast for me. And the price is $800.
So we are creating a new product with a new ID and everything. Click on Send and that should create
a product and in response we get that product back and the status is 200 OK.
To verify it, you can always go to your database.
And select * from product, and you should see two products.