In this lecture, you will implement the UPDATE method of the product for the RESTful API. So go to STS. And it's very simple
because you can copy the CREATE method, paste it and change this mapping to @
instead of PostMapping,
it should be PutMapping.
You are going to use or our clients are going to use the PUT method. Change the method name to UPDATE. These
method names could be anything, the important piece is you are using the appropriate or the correct mappings
and bindings and the request and responses.
So the request will still be the entire product and we'll still be invoking repository.save. This save
method internally,
it knows whether a particular product is already there.
If it's there it will update that information instead of creating it by looking at the ID field in the
request and it returns that product back. Stop the application, start it again.
While it starts, go to Postman, open up a new tab. Change the method to PUT. Grab the URL by going
to the previous tab. Come back, paste it. Go to Body, go to raw, change this to json.
You could have used the previous tab, but I just want you to go through this exercise if you are new to Postman.
And we are updating an id or a product with id 2. Change the price from 800 to 900.
Send it and we get a 200 OK response. The id is still 2.
And the price has changed to 900.
You can go to the database and execute a select and the price has changed to 900.