In this lecture, we'll implement a finder method to get a single product.
So you have already implemented a method that returns as all the products.
If you go to the very first tab and click on the Send button, now it returns both the products in the
database.
But if you want a product by it's ID, to find the product by its ID, we'll implement that particular finder
method. Go to STS,
and go all the way to the end of your controller.
Let me add some spaces so that you can see it clearly. public Product,
I wanted it to return a product and it is getProduct.
It takes a long id and it returns repository.findOne. The findOne method takes a id and it
returns just a single product.
Mark this with @GetMapping.
But the difference here, along with the GetMapping, in the GetMapping,
we need to pass in the id in the URL. So forward slash, to pass in a path parameter,
open up the flower bracket,
this is like a placeholder. Whatever URL parameter comes in, that will go into this. Or we
are telling Spring that it should be binded to this. And then, to inject the value from the URL into our
method parameter,
mark this method parameter with @PathVariable. @PathVariable annotation from Spring, and within brackets
you can tell it that it should be mapped to this particular id. So automatically the value in the URL will be taken
by Spring and it will be injected into this id and then it will be used in the findOne method.
Let's stop and start the server and test it out.
Go to Postman, open a new tab grab the URL from the previous one.
Paste it.
The method is
Get, slash
1. Simply pass in the id. Send and we get the product 1, with the id 1 back. Change the id to 2
and you will get a product for which the id is 2.
So you have implemented a finder method which takes an id in the URL as a path variable
or as a path parameter and it returns that particular product back.