Spring Boot provides various starter projects that help us easily start building different types
of Spring projects.
For example, we can use the spring-boot-starter dependency, we can add this project as a Maven
dependency, and automatically it will bring all the jar files that are required to build a standalone
Spring application.
Similarly, if we want to develop a web MVC application we'll add a dependency in our pom.xml called
spring-boot-starter-web.
So they all start with spring-boot-starter-web and at the end we add the type of project we want to create.
Similarly if we want to use JPA for Java persistence using Hibernate or whatever ORM, you would include
spring-boot-starter-data-jpa and all the other jars which are required to do JPA will be automatically
pulled for you.
Last but not least, if you want to use Spring Data REST, you will use that particular starter project.
So internally, it uses a concept called Bill of Materials from Maven.
Inside each of these starter projects, there will be a file which tells Maven what all dependent jars should
be filled should be pulled from the Maven repository.
It's no magic.
So inside each of these, they have information about what all jars are required to perform or to create
a certain type of project,
and those are pulled. When you create a project later on, I will show you how we add just the spring-boot-starter
and it will pull all the dependencies that are required to create a standalone Spring application.
You can also google for Spring Boot starter projects, Spring Boot starter projects and you can explore
the various starter projects that are available. You can click on one of the links. Let me click on the very first
one, spring-boot-starters. And you'll see a list of starter projects. Let me search for web or -web.
There is one for Web services.
There is a starter project for web, websockets, etc.
So depending on the type of project you are creating, you will include that particular dependency in your
Maven pom.xml. But Spring Boot provides you different ways to create Spring Boot projects
and you might not even add these entries manually.
The IDEs or the Spring Boot initialiser which I will talk about in the next lecture, will automatically
add these to your Maven pom.xml.