So how does Spring Boot magic work? It's no magic.
Spring does not generate any code on the fly, nor does it use any XML configuration.
It is all programmatic configuration which you have done in a section earlier on. Instead of we creating a configuration,
Java configuration, for web.xml or dispatcher servlet or configuring hibernate etc; Spring already has all
those configuration classes in their jar files. The people at Spring have already created them,
and they will be enabled based on certain conditions.
So to understand that, you already know about the Starter POMs. When you add a Starter POM, it doesn't do
any magic, Spring Boot magic.
They simply bring in all the jars that are required for a certain type of projects, for standalone, for web,
for REST, etc;
But once you have these jars, these jars inside them have something called Spring.factories,
under META-INF.
These are already added by
the Spring developers
and these decide what should be enabled and what should be disabled,
what programatic configuration should be enabled at runtime and what should be disabled. So everything,
all the configuration is inside Java classes provided by Spring marked with @Configuration
but conditionally. There is an annotation called
@Condition. If you open up the spring source code and see how the configuration or the Spring Boot works,
the classes they use. For example, for a substitution of web.xml they will have a Java configuration
which would be marked with @Configuration and also @Condition. Only if it is a web project, then enable that
particular configuration.
Similarly, for HibernateJpaAutoConfiguration, only if
there are certain hibernate related classes on the classpath, only then will Spring Boot enable the
hibernate support or this particular HibernateJpaAutoConfiguration.
So that is the magic behind the scenes.
How Spring Boot works, it will look for META-INF/spring.factories which will have a list of
configuration files and it will enable those configurations based on what it finds on the classpath.