In this lecture, you will learn how easy it is to create a spring boot project using the Spring initializer
web interface. To do that, launch your web browser.
Unlike earlier where we created our projects from Eclipse, this time we are going to do it using your
web browser and search for spring boot initializr.
There is no 'e'. It is initializr. They have removed e,
just to be cool.
Click on the very first link Spring initializr and it takes you to their web page where you can create a
spring boot Maven project. Generate a maven project.
We also have a Gradle project option, but we are not going to do that.
We are going to create a maven project with Java.
Other options are available here,
Groovy, Kotlin. And spring boot, you can select a version. I'm going to stick to 1.5.4 which
is stable.
The group id, the maven group id, com.bharath.spring.boot.
You can give whatever unique group id you want to. And the artifact id is the project name. Springboot will be
my project name. And the dependencies,
it allows you to search for dependencies. If I search for web,
if you add this you will have the spring MVC support to your project.
For now I'm going to leave it alone. When we create Spring web projects later on, we'll be using this part.
And when you click on the Generate Project, it will generate a Maven project for you with all the pom.xml, source folders, etc;
It will zip the contents and it will download it into your Downloads folder.
So click on Generate Project and as you can see it has created a springboot.zip. Go to your downloads folder.
For me on Mac,
it is Show in Finder.
That will take me to the downloads folder.
I have the springboot.zip. Unzip the contents of it and you will find Maven project with the source
folder, pom.xml and two other files. In the next lecture,
we'll import this Maven project into Eclipse and will explore the contents of it.