In this lecture, you will import the standalone Spring Boot project that you have generated in the last
lecture into Eclipse and we'll walk through the contents of it. Go to eclipse, to the Spring workspace. Right
click, click on import and search for or type in existing Maven projects.
Select this option from under Maven, Next.
Browse, browse to the downloads folder under which I have my springboot project. You can copy it
to your workspace and you can import it from there if you want to. Open, and the pom.xml, select it,
Finish.
And the spring boot project now has been imported to Eclipse with all the folders.
Get rid of these two files.
We never use them.
They are command line files to run our project from the command line. Right click, delete those two, hit OK.
The important file here is the pom.xml which is the Maven configuration file. Go to the last
tab, pom.xml.
By now you are familiar with the maven coordinates.
These are what you entered on the webpage in the last lecture.
The project name, which is the artifact id.
It has a parent project. By default,
when you create a spring boot, all of them will have a parent project which is the Spring project,
so that we can refer to it and get the dependencies from that project.
The properties, it has the java version.
If you scroll down the important section
here is the dependency section where you see Spring-boot-starter.
So for different types of projects there are different starters available.
In our case we are creating a standalone project, so we have spring-boot-starter.
Similarly we have spring-boot-starter-test for unit testing support.
Finally you see the build section which has the spring-boot-maven-plugin. This plugin allows us to run our
project as a jar file.
It knows how to run a Spring Boot application.
If you see here there are no versions mentioned inside the dependencies. It is because we get the versions
from the parent. So the parent project has all the version information.
If you see here, 1.5.4.RELEASE and the dependency management section in the parent
will have all that information.
So that is the pom.xml. Go under src/main/java,
we have a class called SpringbootApplication. Open that up. Its marked with @SpringBootApplication annotation
which is equivalent to
@Configuration, @ContextComponentScan which you have learnt earlier as well as EnableAutoConfiguration.
So it's equivalent to all these annotations from Spring.
So internally when you mark a class with @SpringBootApplication, all these are or all these come for free
from Spring. Spring will automatically consider this class as a configuration class.
It will also do the context component scan as well as enable automatically configuring your spring beans.
So this is the starting point for your Spring Boot application. It has a main method within which we
use SpringApplication,
is a class from Spring Boot, dot run.
It will start running our spring Boot application and it gives our class to it as the configuration.
So right click, do a Run As -> Java Application and you will see that it starts Spring boot and it runs our
application successfully.
Let me do it one more time.
Right click, Run As -> Java Application, there we go.
It loads
the Spring context and at the end of it, it shuts it down.
So, so far we haven't created any beans, we haven't configured anything but you have learnt about the
pom.xml and all the important dependencies in there
and the spring boot application project. And you have learnt that the SpringBootApplication annotation is
equivalent to @Configuration,
@EnableAutoConfiguration as well as @ContextComponentScan.