In this lecture, you will start working on a tiny little use case which is to create a DAO class and a service
class and inject the DAO into the service using Spring Boot so that we can see a standalone application
running end to end.
I'm going to explain the entire flow once again once you complete this use case.
So let's get started by creating a DAO class, the Data Access Layer class.
We're not going to put any database logic into it. Right click on this package here, say New -> Class.
Call it DAO and put it in a package called .dao which is a subpackage of Spring Boot. Finish. Dao will
have one single method, public void create(){
Use a sysout. Within double quotes, Created.
It simply displays a string.
Next, right click, create a new service. New -> Class, Service.
This service will use the services provided by the Dao.
We are going to autowire the Dao into the service using constructor injection.
This needs the dao to function. Dao dao;
Service(). I am using constructor injection here so that we can atleast see some text being printed whenever
these beans are created. @Autowired and this constructor takes a Dao dao.
this.dao = dao;
Save it.
Hit control+1 to import the dao because it's in a different package and all the errors are gone. Add a method
public void save(){ and this method calls the dao.create().
That's all the service does.
So you have successfully created the Dao. You need to mark this with @Component and the same for @Service
You can either mark it with @Service or @Component annotations from Spring.
And that's it.
So you have created a service and a Dao. In the next lecture,
we'll wire these two and come up with a test class.