In this lecture, we are going to test our application end to end. We are not going to create a Java class
with a main method or use the SpringbootApplication class with the main method, but we will be much
more professional and close to real time and use this src/test/java
SpringbootApplicationTests.java class. So this class got generated when you created your spring boot
project.
This is a test class to test our Spring application.
It is like a JUnit class.
It is a JUnit class except for it uses the SpringRunner instead of the default JUnit runner.
And also it is marked with @SpringBootTest annotation.
This annotation tells the spring test or spring boot to go look for the main configuration class which
is marked with @SpringbootApplication and use that class to start up the spring application or
the spring application context.
So whenever you create test, at least one class your parent class for all the tests should be marked
with this annotation and that tells Spring that it should use any class which is marked with
@SpringbootApplication to start up the spring application context. Before we run this,
let's put something in the service class constructor. Let's add a sysout so that we can see what is
happening.
"Service Bean created", you can also check the log but this will be easy for us to search.
Go back to the test.
By default the test method does not do anything.
But it says context loaded.
So if the test successfully finishes, that means that our spring context has successfully loaded and
it has created all the beans.
So right click, do a Run As -> JUnit test and that test passes.
Everything is green, if you go to the JUnit window it is green.
That means all our tests have passed.
Double click to minimize. Maximize the console and you see a lot happening here.
The Spring container is loaded. Search for service or just search for created and you will see
Service Bean Created.
This is coming from the constructor of our bean.
So spring starts up. This test when it runs, it goes looks for SpringbootApplication or any class
that is marked with @SpringbootApplication, it invokes the main method which is starting the spring
context which in turn scans through the packages,
all the packages within which this class is, the Spring boot were application is and all the sub packages.
You could have put this service in a service package.
But that's okay. Let's move it later.
So it scans through all the packages and subpackages for beans.
Then it figures out that the service needs a Dao.
It creates the Dao bean, injects it into service.
That's exactly what has happened so far.
In the next lecture, we will wire the application context into our test class and we'll use it inside
the test method and use the beans that we have created.