In this lecture, we will use the Service bean inside our test class and see if it got wired properly. Before
we do that, let's move this service to a new subpackage. Create a new package under springboot, dot
service.
That's where our service belongs.
Move the service there.
OK.
In the test class, I can rename this contextLoads to testService,
and to get the beans we need to autowire our ApplicationContext context;
mark it with @Autowired. In most of the realtime applications we'll be developing web applications
and we rarely have to do this.
We use Spring MVC mock test etc; which I'll show you when we do the web development piece using Spring Boot.
Inside the test service, context.getBean(arg0), pass in the class name which is Service.class. Hit control+1,
and import the service class from our own package. Control+1, assign statement to a new local variable.
Call it service. service dot, the only method we have in there is save. Invoke that method and that's all
we need to do.
You can assert for multiple things, but in this case we just want to see the output.
So right click, Run As -> JUnit test.
And that finishes successfully. As you know if we go here,
it's all green. And if you go to the console you should be able to see this text called Created.
So copy that, go to the console.
Contro+f, paste that and search for, this is Service Bean Created.
But you search again and you see this text here which says Created which is coming from the Dao.
So all our beans are successfully wired and we see the proper output. In the next lecture,
I'll explain the flow once again end to end, what exactly is happening,
how are the beans getting wired and how the Springboot application is starting and executing.