Now that you have learnt all the important concepts of Spring boot and also saw a standalone Spring
Boot application working end to end, I will summarize all the concepts while walking you through the
flow of our application.
You have started by creating a Spring Boot project by going to the Spring initialiser website. Once that created
the project, which is the Maven project, you have imported it into Eclipse and the very starting point is the
pom.xml.
If you open it, you have seen it has the starter dependencies. Spring Boot gives us Starter dependencies
or jars or the starter poms, which when used will pull all the additional dependencies for us. Instead
of us including all the dependencies
in our Maven project's pom.xml,
we include the starter poms and automatically Maven will pull the other dependencies. If you see, there
are tons of jars here under Maven dependencies,
but we didn't include all of them in our Maven. They are transitively pulled because these projects in turn tell
Maven that we need all these jars. When you are building a web application,
you will use a starter for web and that will bring a few other additional jars that are required to
build a Spring web application.
You have then looked at the Spring application or SpringbootApplication project or SpringbootApplication Java class
that got generated.
It is market with
@SpringbootApplication, telling the Spring container that this is the starting point of your Spring application.
It has a main method which will be run by the container which inturn uses this particular class as
a configuration.
So this is the starting point of your Spring Boot application. Every Spring Boot application will have
a class that is marked with
@SpringbootApplication. You have then worked on a tiny little use case which is to create two beans, a Dao
with a create method and service with a save method.
The service uses the Dao and we have then went to the test class which also got generated.
It uses the SpringRunner which is a JUnit runner for Spring.
This class is marked with SpringBootTest and it has a test method. Inside the test method,
you have retrieved the ApplicationContext by autowiring it. And you got the service bean and invoked the
save method. When this test is run,
since you have marked this test with @SpringBootTest,
it knows that it should look for a class
in your application marked with SpringbootApplication and use that class
to run your application.
So that is what happened. And when this class is run, the Spring containers scans through all the the,
this package as well as all subpackages for the Spring components.
That is how this annotation is created by Spring guys. And it has scanned through, it find these beans.
it wires them. And then in the test we invoke the save method.
We didn't do any assertions but we simply invoked it and it worked.
So to summarize, you have successfully created, learnt all the concepts of Spring Boot and you've seen it in
action.