Out of the four different ways to create a Spring Boot project, you have already learnt how to do it
using the Spring initializer website and then import that project into your IDE.
In this lecture, you will download an other powerful IDE that allows you to create a Spring Boot project
right from the IDE
instead of using or going to the Spring initializer website.
It is Spring Tool Suite. This IDE is built over Eclipse.
It internally uses Eclipse.
So it will be exactly same as Eclipse. For Eclipse users,
it's nothing new.
But in addition, it has a lot of support for Spring projects.
You can also use intelliJ. If you are already using intelliJ,
you can create Spring Boot projects right from your IDE. To install Spring Boot, launch your web browser,
open a new tab and search for spring tool suite. spring tool suite, select that and you will go to the
spring tool suite search results. Click on the very first link, and download the version for your particular
machine. That will be a zip file. Once you download it, unzip the contents and you will see something
like this.
For Mac, you will see STS.app. For Windows it will be an exe and you will be all set to create
projects from your IDE. In the next lecture,
I will show you how to create a project using Spring Tool Suite.