In this lecture, I will show you how to create a Spring Boot project by using the STS which is
Spring Tool Suite. Doubleclick on the Spring Tool Suite icon. That will launch the Spring Tool Suite for you.
Choose a workspace.
It is very similar to Eclipse because it uses Eclipse.
You can select a folder on your machine, click on Launch. And that will take you to the STS homepage
or the workspace once it launches up. And as you can see it is very similar to Eclipse.
Go to the file menu, say New -> Spring Starter Project. You see that option only in STS, not the regular
Eclipse.
So click on Spring Starter Project. And you can change these Maven coordinates if you want to. I'm going
to leave them as it is. But as you can see it uses the Spring initialiser website to create
a project.
The name is demo, that's fine.
The package is com.example.demo.
Click on next, and here what you have earlier seen as an option for search on the spring initialiser
website is available for you right here.
If you are creating different types of projects, you can select one of these options like the web and
those starter dependencies will be included in the pom.xml.
We'll do that later
when we create web projects. For now, simply hit the Finish button. That will create a standalone Spring Boot project
for you called demo.
Expand it and you will see the very similar structure which you have seen when you created this project
using the Spring initialiser earlier. Open up the pom,
and it should be similar to the pom which you have already seen. Go to the last tab, pom.xml, maximize it
and you will see the starter projects for spring-boot-starter and spring-boot-starter-test.
And at this point you know what to do with this.
You are welcome to create the dao and service again, but that's not required.
It has the DemoApplication which is marked with SpringbootApplication with a main method that is
the starting point.
Then it also has a DemoApplicationTests,
marked with the SpringRunner and the SpringBootTest annotations.