In this lecture, you will create a project in eclipse that you are going to use in the next few lectures,
to implement dependency injection. To do that
go to the eclipse IDE
Once you have eclipse up and running go to the file menu say new maven project leave the defaults as is
on the first screen,
Click next.
here you select the default which is maven archetype QuickStart this archetype that we use
to create standalone Java projects.
Next group Id give a unique ID this is like a package name for the maven repository this is where all of our
products are kept com dot bharath dot
spring is my group ID maven will create folders with the following names and it will put our
project under it. The artifact ID which is the project id is going to be spring core finish and automatically,
eclipse will create a maven project with all the folder structure SRC main java is where all the source
code will go
SRC test Java is where all the test code will go.
In our case, we'll be putting a lot of things under SRC main Java the pom dot XML is the heart of
any maven project.
It has all the configuration if you open it and click on the last tab here which says pom dot xml
maximize it.It has the project coordinates which we gave the group ID artifact ID version
exectra the packaging is Jar because it is a standalone Java project.
And by default it includes the JUnit dependency so maven will pull all the dependencies that are required
by our project instead of us going and downloading the jar files including them in our Eclipse project
adding them to our classpath maven does all that for us to change all these dependencies and to include
dependencies.
You should download the following file instead of searching on the Internet and downloading these dependencies
or copying these dependencies.
You can simply download this pom dot txt file from the resource section of this lecture.
Once you download it copy the whole thing control A control-C
go back to eclipse select from Properties all the way
till dependencies and paste it so we have included two dependencies here
the spring core and spring context that is require these two are required to do dependency injection
as we will see in the next few lectures.
We are going to use classes and interfaces from these two jar files and the version is the latest version
four point three point six, the five dot O is out there but four point three point six is being used in
most of the projects still.
So here I am defining a property for the version and I am using that property here so that if you want
to switch the version in the future.
The spring version would not change it everywhere in the pom dot xml
We can change it in one single place save it.
We also need to put the JUnit dependency back because we have a test here.
We can either delete this test right click related because we are not going to write any JUnit tests
will be coding everything under the SRC package or SRC main Java any time we change the pom
dot xml
You see this error here it is because you'll have to right click on the project and go to Maven do a update
project click OK and now.
Our project will be rebuilt and maven will automatically pull all the dependencies.
Go to maven dependencies expand it and you see spring core spring context and also all the transitive dependencies
that these two depend on are pulled
by maven.We have only defined spring core and spring context here.
But maven has automatically figured out what these two need in order to work.
And it has pulled those dependencies as well.
If we do not use maven then we'll have to download all these jars
And then copy them add them to the classpath
we don't have all that as till now.
So in this lecture you have created the spring core maven project and updated the pom dot xml
for a couple of things one is the dependencies, two
There is also a plugin here.
The compiler plugin we want to use one point eight version of java by default it would pick up 1.5 or
1.6 instead of that we are pointing it to one point eight.