Now that we have the maven project in Eclipse we are going to do dependency injection in three simple
steps.
The very first step is to create the POJO class that is the java bean to do that,
go to eclipse right click on this package here create a new class call it employee this employee
will how to fields in it maximize by double clicking private int ID and id for the employee and a private
int name of the employee.
We are going to, it will be a string name.
They're going to inject these two using spring control one create getter and setter methods for this.
Again control one on the name create get and setter for that name as well.
do a control shift F to format it.
And we have the bean ready.
That is the employee bean. In the next lecture, will come up with this spring configuration where will
define our Bean and inject these dependencies.
We can get rid off this app dot java or we are not going to use it right click delete.