The second step is to tell our spring container about our POJO class and their dependencies it needs.
We do that using a XML configuration file.
You can grab this xml configuration file using a bare bones xml,
It does not have any Bean's defined in it.
It has the beans element which is the root element and the all the name spaces that we need from which
we'll be using the elements inside this bean's element.
So we can grab this from the resources section of this lecture.
Once you have it downloaded you can simply copy the spring config dot xml into your Eclipse project
or copy the contents of it go to eclipse right click on the source.
Main Java say new go to other type in xml, xml file select that next filename should be
config dot xml, it can be anything
I'm naming it as config dot xml
Finish do control a and paste the contents what you would have copied from the downloaded file maximize it and
will start configuring our pojo
The element that we use here is the bean element.
We define a bean element for each object we want to instantiate the bean element has an attribute called
name which is a unique name for it.
Let's call it EMP in our program we'll be using this name to refer to this bean when you write a test
class next in the next lecture you'll be using this name to get the bean class.
We need to get the complete qualified class name.
Go to the employee.
Copy the package come back to config dot xml or paste the package dot employee.
That's the class and within the bean element to do dependency injection we have two Properties which we need
to inject ID which is an int and name which is a string.
To do that will use the property element which is the sub element of bean property.
Name is equal to within double quotes.
We need to give the exact name of the property which is ID close it right there and value is a sub element
within that you can specify the value.
Let's say that ID is 20 copy it paste it.
The second field is name and it's of type string.
I'm using my name.
You are welcome to use your name in the in here.
Inside the value do a control shift F to format.
So we have successfully created a bean or asking spring to create this employee bean and inject these
2 values into the properties ID and name the next lecture will write a test class which will pull this bean
out of this configuration file and we can check out dependency injection.