The last step is to create a test class and see the spring container as well as dependency injection
in action.
Go to eclipse right click on the package new class call it test with a main method finish.
delete that to do. The very first statement is to create a spring container.
We are going to use the classpath,
hit controlspace xml application context.
This is going to search for xml configuration file on the classpath call it ctx is equal to GNU
classpath application context there are overloaded constructor.
There is one that takes a configuration file name or configuration file name is config dot xml
So give that file name config dot xml
And that file is on the classpath because it is under the SRC main Java.
If you put it inside a package then you need to give the complete qualified package name with forward
slashes instead of dots.
you need to give forward slashes because that is how the folders will be created for these packages.
But since it is directly under project or directly under source folder,
I'm using the config dot xml directly, once we have the spring container to get the bean
we do CTX dot get bean.
That's the method which takes a bean name.
or bean name in the config dot xml use EMP.
So we need to use the exact name it is case sensitive and assign it hit control one at the start of the
line assign statement to a new local variable.
Call it EMP by default it returns an object.
We need to change it to employee hit control one add cast to employee.
We do know that it is Employee object.
So we are typecasting it do a sisout
EMP dot get the id
within double coats plus employee id colon space do another sisout
within another sisout double coats employee name colon space plus EMP dot get name so we are getting the bean using
the spring.
And then we are checking if the properties are being injected by spring into that bean lets run this
test right click run as java application and that will kick off the spring container.
It creates an instance of the bean that is specified in the configuration file.
It injects these two properties as values into that bean and we are able to access them and display the
values which are 20 and bharath.