When we have injected the primitive types you have learned that we can use the value element value as
element inside the property to do it.
The second variation of value is instead of using it as an element.
We can also use that as an attribute on the property itself.
So get rid of this value from here and right on the property element we have a value attribute to which
we can assign the value and then we don't need this closing tab we can close it right here.
at the end.
Similarly the second one as well.
Value is equal to bharath.
We need the bean get rid of the property and the value, this is called property value as attribute.
And the earlier one is called value as element run the test again.
Right click run as java application and the output still remains the same.
The dependency injection still works.