You have used value as element and value as attribute.
An other way to initialize or inject values or inject dependencies is to use the P schema.
It's a very easy and popular way to do that.
You need the P namespace which is right here and the prefix for it is P.
and this is its namespace. Once we have it,
We can use the P colon and we need to specify the property which we want to initialize instead of
defining the property element we use P colon ID on this particular class class object.
I want to initialize the ID to within double coats 20 similarly P colon the second one is
name that is the property P colon name is equal to within double coats bharath
and then we don't need any of these.
and this bean element can also end right here.
Its a convenient and easy.
So this is called the P namespace or P schema way of doing it.
Let's run our test one more time and see if it still works.
And the output still remains the same.
So we have finally learnt all the three ways of injecting values using value as element value as attribute
and then the P schema way of doing things.