So far you have learned and work on injecting primitive types as dependencies.In the next few lectures,
you will learn how to inject collection types which are the second type supported by spring.
There are four types of collections list, set, map and properties. The list type is represented using
XML element called list.
Once we use the list spring we'll create a list for us and then it will put whatever values
we provide using the value element into that list, if we want to add a null value then we use the element
called Null.
Once you learn how to use list and inject it into a bean through  setter injection it will be very easy
to use set because a set is represented using a set element and everything else is similar to how you use a
list you assign values to the set using the value elements. Set does not allow duplicates whereas list
allows duplicate
that's the only difference, next is map.
A map is represented using a map element in the xml configuration and it takes a key value pair
entries.
Many entries can be added to a map this key and value can be attributes on the entry element or there
can be child elements of the entry element as well.
We will work on all those combinations in the next few like just the final collection is the property.
A property element is represented by props it can have multiple properties inside it to represent
a single property.
We use the prop element with a key attribute and the value will go inside the body of that element.
In this case, I have the languages just as properties key is USA and the language spoken in US is English.
To summarize.
Spring supports four types of collections.
And we can inject them using the list element in the XML
The set element the map which has a child element called entry.
And finally for properties we use props the child element of it is prop will add multiple properties using
multiple Prop elements.