This and the next few lectures you are going to create a list and inject it into a Java class using
spring.
We'll work on a use case which is very simple you will create a hospital POJO class which will have to
fields the name of the hospital which is a spring and then the list of departments in that hospital
which is a list of strings will accomplish it in three steps which you already know, you'll first create
a spring bean which is a plane Java object the hospital class will then create the spring configuration
file.
Finally we'll create a test class and see the dependency injection of list.
Go to eclipse.
Let's get started let's do the first step of creating the spring bean right click new class call it
Hospital lets change the package to dot list finish the hospital class will have private string name of
the hospital private list of strings which are the departments the names of departments save it hit
control one import Java dot util dot list control one generate or create getter and setters for this.
We can also do all the getter and setters at once.
For now just use this control one shortcut
control shift F to format.
So you have successfully completed the first step will do the configuration file and the test class in
the next few lectures.