In this lecture you will learn how to use the list xml element in the configuration file to inject the list
into a java object.To do that,
go to eclipse will create a new configuration file.
We can also add a bean in the config dot xml but just to show you how to put a config inside a package
and use it.
Let's create another configuration file.
Copy this paste it on this package just to avoid confusion
Right click on it rename by going to rename or hit F2 change it to list config dot xml
hit OK get rid of this bean
dont touch the config dot xml close it open the list config dot xml maximize.
Delete this
bean here and let's start from scratch.
Declare a new bean the name of it will be hospital.
Class is equal to the entire package name so go to the class grab the package name.
Come back to the conflict paste it
copy it again come back paste it dot hospital.
That is the instance we want spring to create close it and within the bean element we are going to
do a setter injection.
The property injection of these two values for the name
Go here
Property name is equal to name.
Inside it you can give a value you are welcome to use either the value as attribute or value as element.
I'm going to use value as element but the name the hospital name is going to be global hospitals.
You can list your favorite hospital here
save it.
The second property going to define it as a List property name is departments copy it comeback
paste it
The department is not of a value
It's going to be a list.
This is where we lose the list element
from spring namespace and within the list we can have multiple values.
Again you can use value as a list of value as a tag or value as an element value as an element or value
as an attribute.
Let's put three values into this ,list the various departments.
I'm going to keep it simple front office inpatient outpatient
You can list more if you want to and that's it.
So we have successfully configured the hospital bean and we are injecting two fields into it or two
dependencies into it using the setter injection or the property injection and for the list inside the
property we have used the element called list.