The last step is to create a test class and see the dependency injection in action.
To do that go to eclipse right click on the package say new class test
with a main method this class will look exactly same as the earlier test.
But I want you to type so that you will remember the API better after some time you can start copying
and pasting the code classpath XML application context that is what we want to create so new
class path xml application context which takes a location of the file control one assign statement
to a new local variable call it context on the left hand side instead of classpath application context.
You can simply use the parent interface which is application context.
hit control one import that to provide the file location this time will have to provide the entire package
because we have put the config under the package.
So go to hospital grab this package from here.
Package name come back to the test paste it and change the dots to forward slashes because there are
folders.
The packages will have corresponding folders and that is where it should be searched
Slash list config dot xml
Next step is to get the bean bean context Dot get
Bean within double coats the name of the bin which is Hospital take that paste it here.
Control one.
assign statement to a new local variable that will be an object changed to hospital automatically
it will ask for typecasting hit control one add cast so that it will be typecasted to hospital sis out bean
lets rename this bean to hospital give it a meaningful name hospital dot get name
that's the first thing then
sis out you can simply print the list hospital dot get the department's  do a control shift f format it.
In the next lecture will run our test and explain the flow end to end.