This lecture we'll run our test and I will explain what exactly is going on in the background.
So right click on our test class do a run as Java application as soon as we run it
a spring container is created this pink container loads the configuration file from the classpath
under this folder structure it will create the hospital bean because that is what we have declared here.
It will create an instance of it.
It will then inject the name property with a value called Global hospital and it will then create
a list and it will inject that list into the departments. Departments property on the hospital,
that is exactly what we are seeing in the output if I drag this up.
The name of the hospital is global hospital and the list has three elements or three objects inside it
front office inpatient and outpatient.
If you want to check out what type off list, list is an interface.
So we haven't specified whether it should be an array analyst or a linked list.
So let's check out what type of list is being created.
You can know that hospital dot get Department dot get class if you do that you will get to know what
type of list is being created by spring.
So run the program and you will see that its a array list by default,in lecture us later on I will show you
how to customize it if you want to use a linked list.