Before we wrap up the list topic you will learn a couple more things about the list element in the spring
configuration. If you want to configure a empty list without any values
We can do that.
We can get rid of all the values from here.
Save it rerun the test.
Just click on the play button and the result is an empty list.
There is no list that is being displayed anymore.
So let's do that sys out
hospital dot get departments save it rerun and the list is empty.
So you can create a instance of a list by simply defining the list element without any values.
We are controls that bring the elements back.
One other thing you want to learn is if you have only one value inside the list then this list element becomes
optional.
Spring is intelligent enough to create a list and inject this into that list or add this to that list
and then it will automatically inject it into the object.
Let's rerun the test.
Hit the play button.
Here is our list.
It's not a single element but it is a list and it is injecting it into it.
Even though we didn't use the list element inside our configuration do a control Z.
So we have learned two additonal things.
One is if there is only one element in the list then this list element is optional.
And also you can create a empty list by getting rid of these values.