In this lecture you are going to learn how to create set instance and inject it into a class using
spring. you will create a car dealer class which will have a string name the name of the dealer and the
list of models that car dealer sells.
Again you are going to do it in three simple steps create the car dealer POJO or the Spring bean in
the configuration file and then the test class.
Now that you have done a couple of times it's going to be pretty easy and I'm sure you can wrap it up
in a single shot.
So let's go to eclipse.
Start by creating a new class the POJO class.
That's the first step.
Car dealer is the class name com dot bharath dot.
Dot instead of list change to set finish.
This class will have two properties private string name private set of strings the models of the card
or the makes of the vehicle control one import it.
Once you have it imported control one again create getters and setters
hit OK control one create getters and setters.
OK again do a control shift  F
to format.
So we are done with the first step which is the creation of the POJO the next step is to create the
configuration file copy over the configuration file from list paste it inside the set.
Open it right click rename it to set config everything that applies to a list applies to list to set.
So it's very easy to use instead of list change it to a set thats it the list allows duplicates whereas
a set does not allow duplicate.
So here instead of hospital it's going to be car dealer.
That's the object change the package name from list to set and the class name is car dealer the name
of it.
You're welcome to use whatever you want.
I'm going to use Hyderabad that's my hometown Hyderabad dealer.
You are welcome to use your home town or your favorite dealer.
And the different types of vehicles if you go back to the class the second property is the models of
the cars.
You can also have it as makers or companies or branch models Honda BMW
your welcome to add your favorite cars here Hyundai three models.
And that's it.
We have also come up with the configuration file for our car dealer.
the last step is the test copy the test paste it open it instead of hospital the bean that will
come out is the car dealer and also the structure here will change from list to set car dealer.
And the name of the bean is car dealer as well.
Change all that and from hospital Let's rename this get rid of this sys outs change this to car dealer
as well.
Sys out car dealer dot get name and sys out
the space car dealer dot get models a control shift f to format.
Right like run as Java application and we have an error here.
Let's see what's wrong.
Cannot be opened because it does not exist list config is not the file we should change the file name
to set config so the exception was it could not find the file that we have specified on that classpath
So it happens if you give it the wrong name.
So instead of set config have given it as list config, it doesn't exist under the package called
Set a folder called set rerun the test again
and the output is Hyderabad dealer and it lists out the three values that we have added to the set.