As I have already said everything that applies to a list applies to the set in spring.
So we can get rid off set element if there is only one object.
There are multiple values we can do it.
But if there is only one value we can get rid off the set element and
rerun the program
click on the play button, run the test not the config
And you see the Honda coming in so we can always inject the single value without using the set element.
The second important piece is that the set does not allow duplicates although I list two hondas here
it will still work.
It will still inject and everything will be fine.
But rerun the test in the result will only see one single Honda up.
You know this behavior if you have learnt core java set only allows single elements it will not allow
any duplicates or it will ignore duplicates
the last piece.
Let's see what is the default implementation of the set that is being used
Go to the test class in case of list.
It was the array list that spring was using by default to list what it is.
Use the dot
Get class.
You can also use get a class name or get name of the class so that you will not see the class keyword
in the output.
Run the test again and the default set implementation that spring uses is a linked hash set.
I will show you how to change that default later on.