This and the next lecture you will learn how to create and inject a map using spring you are going to
work on a very simple use case.
you will create a customer class which will have the customer ID and a map that holds all the products
the customer has bought.
the key is the product ID and the value which is of type string is the product name.
Let's get started go do eclipse,
right click  new class
Customer is the class name com dot bharath dot
spring core dot map finish should have two fields private int ID is the first field.
private map of integer key which is the product ID and the product name is string and call it products
control one import the map from Java util control one for generating getters and setters
hit ok you are welcome to use other shortcuts as well to generate the getters setters exectra click shortcuts
Do a control shift F to format and also let's generate a two string method to do that
Go to source generate tostring
Will use id and products for two strings so that when we print this object later on instead of calling
the getter methods we can simply directly print the instance of this and the two string will display the
ID and the map control shift  F to format.
So in this we have successfully completed the first step of creating the POJO class and the next lecture
will create the configuration file which is the key piece and also create the test class.