In this lecture you will create the spring configuration which is the second step and also the Test class
and run it.
So let's get started by copying the configuration file config dot xml grab any of the earlier ones paste it
in the map package grab the test from set or list.
paste it open up the test we don't have the car dealer in this case we are going to deal with the customer
objects
so let's update the test first and we'll come back to xml configuration customer on the left
hand side also its customer
and we are going to name the bean inside spring configuration as a customer when we create it save that
and instead of doing or invoking the getter methods we can simply display the customer
So here instead of this it's going to be customer get rid of the second sys out
Now that we have the two string method on the customer class the two string method will be invoked and the
details should be displayed
change this package name here
to spring core slash map slash config dot xml
The next step is to come up with the configuration.
Open the config dot xml maximize the name of the bean is customer class name spring
Spring core.
Dot map dot
customer.
We can use the piece schema for assigning the ID.
We have an ID field on the customer as well so we can leave it as it is.
But it doesn't end there.
We have more slash bean ends there within the bean.
We have the property name is products go to customer and the products is the name of the property.
Come back paste it within the property we'll use map and map is where we define entries entry key
is equal to hundred and value is equal to iPhone.
Let's start with that.
So here we are we have defined a map entry which has both the key as well as value as attributes.
So this is a way where we are defining the key and value as attributes.
There are different ways of defining it.
lets try the second type entry value is equal to or let's start with key, key is equal to within double
quotes 200.
And instead of defining the value as an attribute I'm going to define the value as the element value
is IPad That's the second variation.
The third variation is entry value is equal to
Mac Book Pro
and key
I'm going to define the key element and the value as an attribute this is the third combination.
So these are all different ways of defining the entries.
You are welcome to do all the entries in this format or this format or any format you like but you have
the choice key value is equal to 300 in the last combination of course entry is where we define
both as elements both the key and value as elements key is 400.
Of course I need to define a value I can just define the key as it is key has a sub element called value
control X do a control shift F  to format
save it and the value is MacBook Air
save it.
So we have successfully defined four entries in the map we have used four combinations both key and
value as attributes key as attribute value as element value as attribute key as element.
And then key and value as elements.
Lets run our test and see what happens.
Right click run as Java application load said displays the ID which is 20.
Let me maximize it.
And the values in the map 100 for iPhone 200 for iPad 300 is the key and the value is MacBook Pro
and the last one is MacBook Air.
So you have successfully created a map using spring configuration.
If you go to the config dot xml and also injected it into a Java class.