Now that you know how to inject list set and a map it's going to be very easy to inject properties into a java
class using spring. Will create a class called languages which will have one single field of type
java dot util dot properties which will hold a country and its corresponding national language.
Let's get started by creating a languages class go to eclipse new class
languages.
Or let's call it countries and languages.
com dot bharath dot springcore dot Properties finish create the one field here private properties
from java util country and Langs control one import java dot util dot properties control one again
create getters and setters.
hit OK save it.
Go to source.
generate a two string method generate to string by using countries and Langs that's simply going
to display the properties here.
The second step is to create the configuration file
you can go to the earlier one the map grab the test class as well as the config file paste it on the properties
package open up the config will come back to test and fix it.
Delete everything inside the bean the name of the bean.
Let's call it
countries and Langs a long name and the name of the class.
We need the package name so go back to the class grab the package name up copy it and come back
paste it DOT countries and languages get rid of this P:ID we don't have ID field in this case
and to inject the properties first we need to define the property property name is equal to the name
of the field or the properties country and langs paste  that and within the property since the value
we are injecting or the type of data we are injecting is properties we need to use the spring element
called props and within props we can define multiple Prop values which will take a key which is the key
of the property.
USA
And the value can directly go as a text note here.
English is the language.
Let's add one more entry
India and the national language is Hindi, do a control shift F to format and you have successfully injected
properties by using props into a java class by using spring.
Or at least you have configured now change the test class, class path application context
map will change to properties and we are not going to get a customer will get a countries control space
countries and languages copy that paste it on the left hand side change this to countries and langs
and paste it here.
do a control shift F to format
Right click run as Java application that will load the test container we have an exception.
Let's see what it is it says no such bean
Customer.
So we still have customers somewhere right here.
So if we try to use customer which is not there in the config Dot xml we get that exception.
Let's take a look at the exception one more time.
It says No bean name customer available.
So let's go back to the test and change the bean name to countries and langs rerun the test again and
this time the output is countries and Langs USA English.
India Hindi.