That third and one of the most used Dependency Injection types in real time applications is the reference
types or the object types.
We use it when a class has a HAS-A relationship with another class that is when a class uses an
instance of another class to do its work.
Here I have Class A which depends on Class B to get its  work done.
We start by creating an instance of Class B.
We are asking spring here to create an instance of Class B which is the dependency then we create
the dependent class A when we create it
We use the setter injection or constructor injection for setter injection we use the property element
name is B.
And to inject the bean which we have already created we use the ref element to inject reference types  we
use the ref element
from spring in the spring configuration.
This ref element can be used as an element or it can be used as an attribute on the property element.
And the third way is to use the P schema where we can get rid of this property itself and use the P
schema right on the bean element.
Very similar to how you have done it while injecting primitive types will explore all the three ways
using reference as a element as an attribute and using P schema to inject object types in the next few
lectures.