The use case that you'll be working on to inject reference types is student and his test scores will
create a student class which in turn depends or uses a class called scores which will have all the students
scores in math physics and chemistry.
So let's do the first step go to eclipse you know what the first step is new class
in this case we are going to create two pojos or two spring beans the student and the scores start with
student package com dot bharath dot spring  core dot ref types REF types finish and this student
needs a class called scores private scores
this class doesn't even exist scores
hit control one create class called scores finish
scores will have three fields.
private double maths private double physics and finally  private Double chemistry the scores in chemistry
select
right click go to source
It is also a shortcut for it generate getters and setters.
Select all hit OK.
do a control shift F to format if you want to move these up.
You can hold the alt key select them hold the alt key press the up arrow so that the fields will be
moved to the top control shift F to format go back to student.
Save it.
Hit control 1 we need to generate the getters and setters for the scores as well.
So create get a sense that is it OK.
And we have successfully created both the beans and in  the next lecture will do the spring configuration
and also write the test class.