In this lecture, will wrap up the last two steps which is creation of the spring configuration file to inject
the reference type and the test class.
So grab the configuration from earlier packages config and the test copy it and paste it on ref types
open the conflict let's config the reference types always start with the dependent or dependency bean.
That is in this case student depends on scores.
So will start with creating scores first in the config dot xml
Let's get rid of everything and start from scratch.
Except for the beans element nothing is there in the config dot xml start with bean name is equal
to scores
Class is equal to
scores.
We need to grab the package name.
Go to the class copy it come back paste it dot close it right there and we can use the P schema
to inject the values P colon
First one is maths
That's the field name
let's inject that value is equal to 80 in maths
That's a decent score.
Physics is equal to 90.
And finally P colon chemistry lets say 78.
So we have successfully created the first bean or the first object which is required by student.
Now let's create the student bean bean name is equal to student.
Class is equal to student.
Copy the package name from up here.
And paste it
and inside the bean will use the property.
by doing property injection and the name of the property is
scores if you go to the student the name of the property is scores copy paste and to inject the ref types
we need to use an element called ref
ref Bean is equal to specify what is the bean name.
So here the bean name is scores so we are going to refer to that paste it and that will inject scores
into the scores property of a student.
There is a space here the double quotes are not properly ending
so ref bean is equal to scores.
Go to the test class and make the updates instead of properties.
This will be a ref types.
That's the package name countries and languages should change to student typecast it to student and the bean
we are interested is student although we have two beans in the config dot xml at the end of
it we want to get the student and when we display it should also display the scores.
So let's implement the tostring method in student as well as inside scores go to source point your
cursor to the end of the file go to source generate tostring.
Ok.
Go to scores
Source generate tostring.
OK.
Save it.
Come back to the test class.
Student is the name of the bean its typecasted sysout
Change this name here to student student CONTROL shift F to format right click its time to run and
see reference type injection and it displays the student's course in math physics and chemistry.
So we have successfully configured object types and injected one object or reference into another java
object.