When you injected the reference type you have used the ref as element.
They can also be used as an attribute if you learn how to do that in this lecture and more to use ref
as an attribute
You will start using it inside the property as an attribute there is a ref attribute on that element
is equal to scores
And then we can end that element right here and get rid of these two.
We don't need the end tag this is how we can use ref as attribute instead of element run it
run the test again and the output still remains the same.
The score object is created and it is injected into students.
Now let's learn another way of doing it.
The P schema way you have used P schema to inject primitive types
So for now you're going to learn how to inject the reference type as well.
So right on bean here the student bean use P colon the syntax is variable name hyphen ref.
So the variable name on the student is scores so will have to use variable name which is scores
hyphen
We need to tell that it is a reference type.
We do that using a ref is equal to within double quotes the name of the bean or the reference of the
bean which is scores then we don't need all this get rid of that and we can close the bean tag right
there.
save it rerun the test and the output still remains the same.
So we have successfully learnt all the three ways of injecting reference type that is using a reference
as element using ref as an attribute and also using the P schema to inject reference types.