In this lecture, I will quickly recap what you have learned from the setter injection section. Setter injection
is the process of the spring container using the setter methods on our object to do the dependency injection.
We also learnt the three important steps to do dependency injection using spring they are creating the spring
beans for our application classes which are pojos plain old Java objects.
Second step is to create the spring xml configuration file and provide the spring container the
dependency injection information.
That is how the beans should be created and what dependency should be injected goes into this particular file.
Last but not least get the beans from the spring container and use them
either in our test classes or other application classes .There are three different types of data you
have injected have injected the primitive types using value as element value as attribute and also using P schema
which is a very convenient and easy way to inject dependencies.
The second data type is collections and to inject the various collection types we use the collection
elements in spring list set map and properties are the xml elements that we have used.
Last but not the least objects or reference types can be injected using the ref element inside the bean
element property.
Ref can be used as an element and also as an attribute on the bean.
back.