In this lecture, you will create a Spring
MVC Maven web application.
You are going to use it in the next few lectures to see the Maven Spring MVC end to end.
Get started by going to Eclipse, File menu, new -> Maven project.
We are going to create a Maven web application this time. So click on the next,
don't select the default option which is maven-archetype-quickstart.
This is for standalone projects. But we are creating a web application, so scroll down.
Go to maven-archetype-webapp, maven hyphen archetype hyphen webapp.
Next, Group Id should be com.bharath.spring.
That is what we have been using. And the Artifact Id is springmvc. springmvc for model view controller
Finish. That will create a maven project for us. The very first step
as always is to open up the pom.xml.
There is an error.
I will discuss about it and we'll fix it in a second.
Go to pom, open the springorm pom.
Go to the last tab, the pom.xml, maximize it.
Copy from properties all the way to the build section.
Come back to the springmvc/pom.
There is no properties here, so start from dependencies. Go all the way till end of build. Paste it, do a
control+shift+f to format. We have the compiler plugin. Get rid of all the dependencies and leave
just one, because for Spring MVC all we need is one dependency and Maven will pull all the other dependencies
transitively. I have the spring-core here, change it to spring-webmvc.
It is spring hyphen webmvc and we are using the version 4.3.6. Save it, minimize it.
This error here is because, if you see the error, go to src -> main -> webapp, open the index.jsp which has
the error message. Point at the error,
it says the superclass javax.servlet.http.HttpServlet was not found on the Java Build Path.
So it needs the servlet class which is not there on the class path. We can fix it in two ways.
One, we can add the servlet dependencies to the Maven pom.xml or an other simple way,
right click on the project, go to properties. In here on the top corner, top left,
search for target, Targeted Runtimes. Select it. And on the right side you will see Apache Tomcat which you
would have installed and configured in Eclipse from the software setup section.
If not, please do that.
Once you do that you will see it here.
Select that and hit OK.
And that error will go away.
This is a different error now. You don't see an error on index.jsp anymore because Tomcat has the servlet
dependencies and that error is gone.
This is because we haven't updated our project.
So right click, go do a Maven -> Update Project. Every time we change the pom.xml,
we should update our Maven project. Now it does an updation and all the errors are gone.
The structure of the web application, maven web application is different.
If you notice, we have Java resources which has src/main/resources. It does not have a
src/main/java. We'll create that folder. And under src, if you go here,
it has a webapp under which we have WEB-INF which has the
web.xml which is the deployment descriptor file. And all our JSPs and HTMLs
can either directly go under webapp like this.
Here we have index.jsp.
Or we can also put them under WEB-INF. Let's create a src/main/java folder here so that
we can put our controllers. Right click, say new, not Source Folder, go to Other, seach for folder. Folder,
Next. You should go under src/main.
That is where we want it. And the folder name should be Java, Finish.
This is the structure we need to follow in Maven. Any source code should go under src/main/java.
Any configuration files, we can put them under src/main/resources.
So in this lecture, we have successfully created a Spring
MVC Maven web application and also updated the dependencies and got rid of any errors that we had.