Starting this lecture, you will create your Spring MVC application in five simple steps.
Number one, configure the dispatcher servlet in the web.xml, create a spring configuration file
under the WEB-INF folder. Number three, configure the view resolver.
You know what a view resolver is. It appends a prefix and suffix to the view we return from the controller.
Create the controller class is the fourth step.
And also we'll configure it.
And finally we'll create the folder structure and the JSP page under WEB-INF.
So let's get started by configuring the dispatch servlet.
Go to Eclipse. Spring MVC is our project. Open the web.xml. This is where we'll configure over dispatcher
servlet.
Change the name to Hello spring
MVC. That's the display name of this application.
Configure the servlet, servlet
is the element that we want to use. Servlet name is the first one, let's call it
dispatcher.
The second element should be servlet-class.
We know that it is called dispatcher servlet, but we don't know the package name.
You know what to do.
Control+shift+t, search for DispatcherServlet and you'll find it under spring framework.
Select it, grab the class name all the way from the package name, copy, come back to the web.xml,
paste it.
Remove any unwanted lines.
We have configured this servlet name and its class.
Now we need to configure the mapping for it. servlet-mapping
is the element. It has elements two child elements,
servlet-name again.
Dispatcher, the same name
what we have used here. And a url-pattern. We can use whatever pattern we want.
I'm going to use a forward slash meaning, all the requests that come from the browser to our web application,
any request should go to the dispatcher-servlet. We can also use something like .html or .do etc;
But I'm going to use a forward slash. So in this lecture you have successfully configured the dispatcher
servlet from spring MVC in the web.xml.