The second step is to create a Spring configuration file.
And there is a convention that we need to follow
when we do that, because we are developing a Spring MVC web application and not a standalone application.
We'll put it under the WEB-INF.
So go grab any of the configuration files from the springjdbc or even springorm. Go to src/main/java,
test, copy the config.xml, come back, paste it directly under WEB-INF. Right click and rename
this. There is a convention we need to follow. The name of this file should be, the name of the servlet, our
servlet name if you see it
above, in the web.xml is
dispatcher.
So dispatcher-servlet.xml. By default the dispatcher-servlet will search for a configuration
file with the following name.
That is, the servlet name hyphen servlet.xml. There is a way to override it which I'll show
you in lectures later on. But for now always remember that the name of the configuration file should
have the servlet name hyphen
servlet.xml. Click OK.
Open the dispatcher-servlet.xml. Maximize.
Get rid of everything inside the beans element. And in the next lecture we'll configure the view resolver
inside the dispatcher-servlet.xml.