The third step is to configure the view resolver in the Spring configuration file.
It is a Java class. We'll configure it as a bean and it's going to resolve the prefix which is the location
and the suffix which is the extension for us, for our view. So go to Eclipse.
Go to the dispatcher-servlet.xml and start creating a new bean. Bean
class is equal to, it's called the InternalResourceViewResolver. So do a control+shift+t,
InternalResourceViewResolver, select this last one from Spring Framework.
Open it up, go all the way up, copy the package name, come back to the dispatcher-servlet. Paste it, dot
go back, grab the class name.
Come back, paste it and we have the complete class name.
Name is equal to, call it whatever you want,
viewResolver.
Close it and within the bean tag we need to set a couple of properties.
The first one is prefix and the second property is suffix.
So use the property element, name is equal to prefix. The location will go into the prefix. Within the
property provide a value. And the value, we are going to put our JSP pages under WEB hyphen, its forward slash
WEB hyphen INF, forward slash VIEWS.
We can call it whatever we want, but I'm going to put it under a folder called views under WEB-INF. Control+shift+f
to format. The second property is the extension. Property name is equal to suffix, using which
we'll provide a value.
And this will be .jsp.
You can use any extension. In this application the
extension is going to be .jsp. So the view resolver will use this particular path as the suffix for whatever
view we'll return from the controller and it will append this at the end of the view.