The fourth step is to create the controller class which is the key class in our application, which takes
the request and sends a response back. Go to Eclipse,
src/main/java, right click, create a new class. Call it HelloController and change the package name to
com.bharath.spring.springmvc, HelloController is the name of the class, finish it.
To make it a controller, we need to mark it with the @Controller annotation. Every controller should
be marked with this annotation.
It is from the stereotype package which tells the Spring Framework that it can create a bean of this
type and it is a controller bean. That is, it can process the incoming HTTP requests. Add a method public.
It should return a ModelAndView. As you have learnt, ModelAndView. Control+space, import it from the
Spring framework, web.servlet.ModelAndView. The method name can be anything.
Hello is the method and it should return
new ModelAndView. Select that, hit control+1, extract to a local variable.
ModelAndView is the name of it.
We are not going to touch the model portion in this lecture, we'll not be setting any data. We'll only
set a view onto this ModelAndView variable or object. ModelAndView.setViewName which takes
a string. Within double quotes,
we need to pass in the view name which is hello.
We haven't created this view yet.
The hello.jsp, but we are going to pass it. And in the next lecture
we'll create the JSP page.
The beauty is, there is no location,
there is no suffix, the extension here that we have already configured with the view resolver in the
dispatcher-servlet.xml.
We need to mark this method with @RequestMapping because we need to tell Spring when this method
should be invoked, for which url-pattern.
So RequestMapping, within brackets, within double quotes, forward slash
hello. That's the url pattern I want to use. From the browser we should use this url pattern.
That is when Spring will invoke this particular method.
Now we haven't enabled annotations. So go to the dispatcher-servlet.xml which is our configuration file.
You know how to enable them.
Context colon, control+space component-scan.
This will both enable the annotations as well as we need to provide the base package which is this particular
package here.
Right click.
I want to rename this package, I'm not happy with the package name. So refactor -> rename.
We should have .controller at the end, dot controller because all these are controller classes.
Right click, refractor -> rename.
Just grab that name, cancel or
you can go to the Controller class.
Expand this, go to the controller, grab the package name from here.
Go back to the dispatcher-servlet and paste that package name. Close the element right there.
So you have successfully created a controller and you've also told Spring that it should scan the following
package for the controllers, for the beans that it can create.
And in this case it is a controller bean.