The last and final step is to create the location or the required folder structure and the view under
it, which is the hello.jsp
in our case. Go to Eclipse. Under the WEB-INF,
if you open the dispatcher-servlet.xml, we have configured the folder to be WEB-INF/views.
So right click on WEB-INF, create a new folder called views, finish.
Right click on the views, say new, JSP file. And the name of this should be
hello, hello.jsp, Finish.
Maximize, title is Hello.
And within the body, we'll add a bold tag or h1 so that we can see bigger text, h1 for heading.
Welcome to spring MVC or you can say Hello from Spring MVC, save it. And that's it.
So you have successfully finished the final step which is to create the views folder under WEB-INF and
a page called hello.jsp which is our view page.