We are all set to see it in action. Before we do that, in the dispatcher-servlet.xml,
I forgot to add a forward slash at the end of views. So add a forward slash so that when the view
resolver tries to resolve the view, it will use the following path,
slash hello.jsp. if you don't add this forward slash we'll get an error. So add it. right click on the application,
go to Run as -> Run on server.
This will deploy the application on the Tomcat server which we have configured in the software setup.
It is stopped right now.
It will automatically start it and deploy
the Spring MVC application on the server. By default,
you will see Hello world, because it opens up the index.jsp.
But that is not we are interested in.
So go to the eclipse browser. You can grab this link and you can open this in Chrome web browser as
well and you can also configure Eclipse to directly open it in Chrome.
At the end, the url should be Spring MVC which is the application name. Localhost is the server name,
8080 is the port number of Tomcat, slash,
hello.
That is the url which we have configured in the controller.
If you go here,
hello. Let's use that, Enter. And Spring runs and you see Hello from Spring
MVC. This is coming from our hello.jsp page.
So from the browser the request goes to our web application. In the web.xml
we have configurde the dispatcher-servlet to handle everything that comes to our web application.
We have used a forward slash. Thr dispatcher-servlet will take the request and it will dispatch it to the
hello controller.
Here, this guy and this method because we have matched the url pattern to this particular method. And this
returns a model and view in which we have configured the view to be hello.
The controller will then invoke the InternalViewResolver and it will give it hello. The view resolver
will append.
If you look at the dispatcher-servlet, it will append a prefix, this path and this extension and return
it to the controller.
The controller will take the JSP and execute it and send the response back to the web browser.