In this lecture, you will learn an advanced Springcore concept called Bean externalization or reading
properties from a file and injecting it into a bean. In realtime applications, we often have some properties
or key value pairs such as the db name, the port number of the server, usernames, passwords etc; which we
do not hardcode in our application code and use a properties file instead.
If we have to change these values, the values for these keys, we need not change it everywhere in the
code.
Simply we go to this one global property file and change the value right there.
And it can be reused without recompiling our application or code. In spring applications,
we use the property place holder configuration to link these property files with our xml configuration
in three steps.
The first step,
we create the property file ofcourse.
The second step is to link this property file in our XML configuration and then we use that property
file and inject the values in this property file into our application, or we inject these properties
as dependencies to our beans.
In this lecture, you will create the property file and in the next lecture you will link it and test it.
Go to Eclipse, right click, create -> New, go to other. Type in file. Select file, because we are going to create
a property file. Call it database.properties, Finish. We'll move it under a package in a second.
Right click, new, create a test class. com.bharath.springcore.propertyplaceholder
is the package name, finish. Move this property file into that new package called propertyplaceholder.
Open it, add some properties to it.
This will have a dbServer is equal to, let's say a bharathserver.
You can give a IP address if you want to.
dbPort=3306. Let's keep all camel case. dbServer, S capital, dbPort, P capital, dbUser, U capital, test.
dbPass is equal to test as well.
Save it.
So you have successfully created the dot property file. Both the keys and values
here are string type. And if we have duplicates, for example, if I add another dbPass here, always the
latest will be taken.
So the last one will be used. If you want to comment out something, you use hash. That means comment, in
a property file and that property will not be read.
Comments are useful to give information.
For example, you can say #The default port etc;
Or if you have multiple configurations, if you have along with dbServer configuration if you have a
web service configuration here, you can say #web service configuration. That is the use of comments. And
these db properties here or any properties are case sensitive, the keys here are case sensitive. dbUser
is not the same as dbuser.
So you've got to be careful with the case as well.
In the next lecture, we'll link up these properties in our XML configuration and we'll inject them into
our bean. Uncomment everything
and you can delete this line, we'll have four properties.