In the previous lecture we have created a properties file.
In this lecture, you'll create a POJO class and the configuration to link up this property file and
inject one of these properties into our POJO.
Let's get started. Right click on the propertyplaceholder package, New -> Class, call it MyDAO.
Let's assume that this is a class that does the database work and it needs that information in the properties
file.
At a single property called private String dbServer;
Let's use constructor injection, because you have just learnt how to do that and this constructor
takes one argument, string dbServer
which we are going to inject from the property file. this.dbServer = dbServer;
Generate a toString method. Go to source, generate toString, save it.
The next step is to come up with the configuration file.
Grab any configuration file of your choice from any packages.
I'm getting it from constructorinjection,
Ambiguity, paste it on the new package.
Open it.
Delete the bean. And let's create the bean file from scratch.
bean name="MyDAO"
get the package name,
paste it before the DAO.
name is equal to myDAO. Close it there and within the bean tag, we need to use constructor argument.
const and then the control+space will give you constructor-arg.
Only one value is required and that value we want to read from the property file.
We don't want to hardcode it here.
That is where Spring's propertyplaceholder comes in. It is from the Spring's context namespace
which you have already used.
You have used context namespace to enable annotations earlier on.
Now you'll use one more element from that namespace. context: hit control+space and we'll see all
the options, property-placeholder. property-placeholder.
That is the one you need to use. And the attribute, location. We need to provide the location of the property
file that will load up the property file and we can use those properties in our configuration file or
inject them into our beans. The location is database.properties and copy the complete package name
from here, because on the classpath we need to provide the package path as well.
Change all the dots to forward slashes and get the name correct, database.properties. And here bean
name and this should be class, not the name. The first attribute is class and the second attribute is
name.
Now to read a property from here, inside the value element in between those elements,
use dollar. That is how we read it. And within flower brackets our braces,
the name of the property which is dbServer.
In the database.properties dbServer is the name of the property.
So use that.
Save it.
So using the dollar symbol and within braces, if we put a property name automatically that will be
read from the property file which we have configured using context:property-placeholder. Go to the
test class, let's create the test and run it. main, control+space, Enter. Control+shift+f to format.
ApplicationContext context = new ClassPathXmlApplicationContext("config.xml");
config.xml need to provide the path, paste the package, we have already copied it earlier.
Forward slashes, dots get replaced with forward slashes.
Save it. context.getbean("myDAO") within double quotes name of the bean is myDAO. In the configuration file the name
is myDAO, DAO capital.
myDAO is what we want it to assign to. Call it dao.
Typecast it, myDAO within brackets, System.out.println(dao); do a control+shift+f to format. So we have successfully
used the properties in the config file and also created a test class.
Let's run it and see it in action.
Run as -> Java application and it prints the dbServer name. So spring container loads the property file, links it up.
In the XML, we can read the property and it injects it using constructor injection into our DAO.