In the previous lectures, you have learnt how to read and inject properties into our beans.
In this lecture, you will see what happens if we use a property that does not exist in the properties
file.
Or we can also demonstrate it by using case insensitiveness.
That is, go to your test,
or go to the configuration and let's try to read dbserver. This property does not exist.
Let's see what happens by running the test.
And the exception is, if you scroll up it says invalid
bean definition, could not resolve a placeholder 'dbserver' in string value dbserver.
So that's what Spring throws, a bean definition store exception. It could not find that particular property
or particular bean in the configuration or in the store.