Just like how Spring made it easy for us to use JDBC by providing a Spring JDBC template.
It also makes it easy to use ORM tools like Hibernate by providing HibernateTemplate.
It hides all the boiler plate coding like creating a hibernate session etc; and we can simply use
the HibernateTemplate and execute operations against a database such as save, update, delete, get which
returns one record, loadAll which returns multiple records as a list of objects.
Everything, all these methods here deal with objects. They take objects, save them into the database
table as a row,
they retrieve data, return a single row as an object or multiple rows as list of objects. All that is done behind
the scenes.
We simply use the HibernateTemplate and start invoking the methods on them and hibernate internally
will generate the necessary SQL statements and execute them. Any application that uses HibernateTemplatehibernate template
will have the following design.
Usually, for example if we are dealing with a entity or table called product, we'll create a Java bean called
product, we'll mark it with all the annotations or the mapping information against the database table will
be provided.
And then we create the product Dao which will have all our database code. This is the interface. We implement
it.
And this DaoImpl will depend on HibernateTemplate. The HibernateTemplate in turn uses the SessionFactory
bean which is an interface. This SessionFactory takes care of establishing the connection and all
that. It is a, it provides the hibernates session at the end.
We need not worry about it. We simply give the
SessionFactory bean to the HibernateTemplate and the rest of it will be taken care by the HibernateTemplate.
An implementation of SessionFactory is LocalSessionFactoryBean from Spring. We'll be implementing
or we'll be using this particular bean in our application. And also the SessionFactory needs a DataSource and
a few more things which I will explain in the next slide.
We also will configure a TransactionManager.
We need transactions when we do write operations against a database to ensure that either all of them fall
in one transaction, either all of them execute or they dont.
The LocalSessionFactoryBean takes three arguments or it depends on three other beans,
the DataSource which you already know, you have used it while working on Spring JDBC.
hibernateProperties, we need to provide a couple of properties which I will show you in the next slide.
And finally a list of annotatedClasses. We need to tell the local SessionFactory bean which all classes
in our application map to the database tables.
You will see all that in action in the next few lectures. A couple of hibernate properties that we provide
in the key value format or hibernate.dialect. The hibernate.dialect is a class that generates the
SQL from the objects we provide for a particular operation. If it is save, it'll generate insert, if
it is update, it'll generate a update etc;
So this class is responsible for generating SQL for a particular database.
Hibernate provides dialect classes for all the popular databases.
Here is one for MySQL.
Similarly for Oracle there will be a different dialect. The second property is hibernate.show_sql.
By default hibernate will not display all the SQL statements it generates on the fly.
This property will tell the dialect that it should display all the SQL statements that it is generating
on the console.
So in this lecture, you have learnt how spring provides ORM support. It makes our job to use ORM
tools like Hibernate easy by providing templates.
We use the HibernateTemplate which inturn depends on SessionFactory bean. SessionFactory bean needs a
datasource,
a couple of hibernate properties and a list of annotatedClasses which are entities. In our case it
will be the product entity,
just one. And here are a couple of properties, the dialect which generates the SQL for a particular
database and property called show_sql which tells hibernate that it should display the SQL statements
on the console.