When we use ORM tools like Hibernate the only piece of information we as developers need to provide is the
mapping information, mapping between the fields in our classes and the database table.
We can do it using XML or annotations. Annotations is the most popular way and that is what we're
going to use in this particular course.
There are four JPA annotations, Java Persistance API annotations that we as developers should know, @Entity,
@Table, @Id and @Column.
Let's take a look at an example.
First we create an entity.
It is a simple class.
It is a simple java bean like Employee
in this case. And we create all the fields in it, id firstName and lastName. And then we start marking
it with annotations, starting with the @Entity annotation.
And the primary field or the primary key field or the unique field in our application or in our entity,
for example in this case the id uniquely identifes an employee and it should be mapped to the id field
in the database which should be the primary key. We mark it with the @Id annotation.
This tells hibernate that this particular field is the primary key field.
These two annotations @Entity and @Id are mandatory for every entity that we create. The next two, the @Table
is optional as well as the @Column annotation is optional.
We use these only if the database table name is different from the class name, we can use the @Table
annotation and provide that name here.
For example, in this case the class name is Employee but the table name is not employee but it is emp.
That is why I am using @Table annotation and through the name attribute I'm providing the table name.
So all this information at runtime,
all these annotations will be processed by hibernate and it knows which entity should be mapped to which
table and which column or which field
in the Java object should be mapped to which column in the database.
You can also use the @Column, it's optional. And we use it if the fields here, the field names here are
different from the column names and also the @Column has few other attributes as well.
To summarize, you can use the four annotations to map our Java classes to the database tables.
They are @Entity,@Table, @Id and @Column. The @Entity and @Id are mandatory. @Id is used to mark the primary
key column and we use the @Table and @Column optionally if we want to map fields and classes if
the names are different from the database.