In this lecture, you'll create a database table which you will be using throughout the Spring ORM usecase. To
do that, download the springorm.txt file from the resources section of this lecture.
Open it in your favourite text editor once downloaded. Do a Control+a, copy it, Control+c, go to MySQL workbench.
Open a File -> New Query Tab, paste the contents there.
The very first line is to switch the database or go to a particular database.
Use mydb, mydb is my database. In your case if you have a different name please switch it to that and
then use this command. Execute it. That will change the database to mydb.
The second command creates the product table.
There are four fields, id is an integer, name is varchar(20),
description of the product varchar(100), price is a decimal. Here 8 is the total number of digits that
can be stored in price and 3 is the number of digits that can go after the decimal point. Select
that, execute.
That creates the product table.
Execute the select statement or query.
Right now there are no columns or there is no data in the product table.