In this lecture, you will work on the very first step which is to create the Maven Spring ORM project
in Eclipse.
To do that, go to the File menu, say New -> Maven project. Click on the next button.
Leave the default option as it is,
which is maven-archetype-quickstart for standalone projects, click Next.
The Group id is fine, com.bharath.spring.
That is what we have been using. The Artifact Id or the project name should be
springorm, all lowercase, springorm for object relational mapping. Finish. And we have our maven project.
Click on the, double click on the pom.xml, open it. This is the Maven configuration file.
Click on the last tab, go to the previous project which is springjdbc. Open its pom.xml.
Go to the last tab, double click to maximize. Grab everything from properties all the way till end
of build section, just before the project ends.
Copy it.
Come back to the new pom.
Delete everything from properties all the way till dependencies and paste whatever you've copied. Do control+shift+f.
And you know what's next.
We have to update the dependencies, you're going to delete some dependencies or one dependency which is
the spring-jdbc because we are going to use spring-orm, we don't need spring-jdbc. We need the
spring-core dependencies to do dependency injection and we need the mysql JDBC driver in my case.
If you are using Oracle that would be a different driver.
And we need two additional maven dependencies, Spring ORM
is the first one and Hibernate Core is the next one.
This is the ORM implementation, hibernate that we are going to use. Go go back to Eclipse.
Copy one of the spring dependencies, paste it right next to the spring-context dependency. Do a
control+shift+f to format. And change this context to spring-orm.
That is all that is required.
This is the Maven dependency to grab spring-orm. The next one is Hibernate Core. To get that dependency,
go to your web browser,
open up Google and search for hibernate core maven dependency. Click on the first link.
I am currently using 5.2.5.
You are welcome to try out the latest that is out there, but I'm going to grab 5.2.5
because I have been using it and there were no issues with it.
Scroll down, click on this text area and it will be copied to the clipboard.
Go back to Eclipse, right after all the spring dependencies and before the sql-connector paste
our new dependency. It could go anywhere.
Just having a logical order in here. Delete this link. Control+shift+f to format. If you want to add a property
for this version you can do that here.
But since we have only one dependency we are not using this version multiple times.
I'm going to leave it as it is.
Now we'll see some errors.
You know what to do. Get rid of the tests. Go to the src/test/java,
right click on the package.
Delete it. You have done it quite a few times by now.
And once we update the pom.xml, right click on the project, go to maven and update project. That
will fix everything for Maven.
It will pull the dependencies and all the errors are gone.
So you have successfully created the Spring ORM project and updated the dependencies and also you have
the compiler plugin in place which tells maven that it should use Java 1.8.