In this lecture, you'll create the very first class in our application which is the product entity. The product
will represent the database table which is product.
It has four columns, id, name, description and price.
So let's go back to Eclipse. Close all the poms, right click, close all. Go to the src/main/java, expand the
package, get rid of App.java, delete it. Right click on the package, say New -> class, Product.
This is our entity.
Entity represents a database table,
springorm dot, the package name should be entities or entity. entity the package name.
You can also use model, model or entity they are both synonyms. Finish.
Double click to maximize, we need to add four properties here.
Private int id, private int or private string name, of the product.
Private string description.
I'm going to use desc just to show you that the property names need not be same as the database column
names in the database.
It is description, but I am using it as desc. You can map it to the database column.
You've already seen that in theory. Private string, the last one,
it's not a string.
It's going to be a double, value.
Sorry, the price. You can select them all, go to a src or source, generate the mutator methods which are setter
and getter methods. Select them all. And here,
instead of first member change it to After 'price'. Hit
Ok, do a control+shift+f to format.
We have created a java bean. It's not an entity yet. To make it an entity we need to mark it with the
appropriate JPA annotations.
Let's start with the very first one if you remember, @Entity.
That makes this class an entity. Hit control+1 and import entity from javax.persistence, not from
hibernate, it should be from javax.persistence.Entity.
The next mandatory annotation is on the id field,
you should use a @id. Control+space,
id from javax.persistence.
These two are mandatory and the rest of the optional ones, table, @Table, this class should map
to a database table. javax.persistence is the package. Within brackets,
name is equal to product.
This is not mandatory unless your table name is different from the class name.
That is when we use this @Table. But it will be much more clear if we use this annotation,
doesn't hurt. And the next set of annotations are @Column, the last annotation is
@Column from javax.persistence again.
Inside this we can use name is equal to name, copy that, paste it above id, also paste it for description
and price.
Change the names, name is equal to id. For a description column name is not desc, it should be description,
description, that is what it is in the database.
And finally, the last one is price.
Now our Java bean has turned into an entity. In this lecture, you've successfully created our product entity.