The next step is to create the ProductDao interface and the ProductDaoImpl class that implements
that interface and will use the HibernateTemplate class.
So go to Eclipse.
Right click on this package here, say New -> Interface.
Always go to interfaces.
The package name should be springorm dot, product is our domain, dao.
And the name of the class should be Product, d capital, Finish.
We'll start with one method called create and we'll add the rest of the methods later on. The create
method
can return an integer. Integer create, it should take a product entity and create a row in the database. Product product,
that's our method, control+1, import product.
It's under springorm. Let's change the package of product as well.
Instead of springorm, we'll say springorm.product.entity. Control+1, more the Product.java
to the new package. So we'll have product, is our business model or it's the domain. Under it we have
entity, same in dao product, then the dao. Delete this import, hit control+1 and reimport product
from the right package. Save it. Right click, New -> Class, ProductDaoImpl and put it in a package called
product.dao.impl. This is how we do it in real time.
Click on add, search for ProductDao. Select that interface and our class should implement that interface, Finish.
And Eclipse will add the method for us.
Hit control+d to relate that TODO. Maximize.
And this class uses uses the HibernateTemplate. HibernateTemplate and the package should be,
always use the spring HibernateTemplate,
the latest version. Change the import to 5.
So there are multiple versions of HibernateTemplate available in the jars that we have added to
Maven dependencies.
So make sure that you are using the latest.
The package should be, or the import should say hibernate5.
HibernateTemplate, call it HibernateTemplate.
That's it.
And in the next lecture, we'll start wiring our beans.
So we'll add SessionFactory, LocalSessionFactory, the HibernateTemplate and then we'll inject into the
ProductDao.
And then we'll use the HibernateTemplate inside the create method.