In this lecture, you'll create the Spring configuration file and configure the very first bean which
is the DataSource bean. Go to Eclipse, double click to minimize, grab the configuration from the previous
project, go to Spring JDBC, src/main/java. Go to the test folder under Employee.
That is where we have created our config. Copy that config, close that, come back.
Right click on this package, say New -> Package. We'll create a subpackage called test. springorm dot product
dot test, finish. Paste the configuration.
Maximize it or expand it. Open the config.xml. Get rid of everything except for the DataSource. Leave the
DriverManagerDataSource as it is because we are going to need that bean. Delete this context:component-scan
and JdbcTemplate. We'll add whatever we need later on. And remove all the spaces. And you have successfully
created the configuration and also configured the DriverManagerDataSource. In the next few lectures
we'll create all the other beans or we'll configure all the other beans.