In this lecture, you'll configure the LocalSessionFactoryBean which is an implementation of the
SessionFactory and which does most of the work.
This is the biggest portion in our configuration file.
So let's get started. This LocalSessionFactoryBean needs three properties or three dependencies, the
DataSource, HibernateProperties, a property called HibernateProperties which are key value pairs or
properties.
And finally, a list of entity classes.
Let's get started by going to Eclipse, the configuration file.
Create a new bean, class is equal to, within double quotes,
its the LocalSessionFactoryBean.
We know the class name but we don't know the package.
So do a control+shift+t, search for LocalSessionFactoryBean
and you will find that. Grab the one which has the package as hibernate5. Don't use 4 or 3.
We are using the latest, select that. Grab the entire qualified class name which has the package name,
copy it.
Go back to the config, paste it within double quotes.
Make sure you don't have any spaces. Name is equal to, call it sessionFactory.
Close it right there.
And the very first property is the DataSource. Let's use p-schema. P colon, data, s capital, source
is equal to, within double quotes,
grab the dataSource name from here and paste it.
We already have the dataSource bean. It has two more properties.
Let's set them. Property, the first one name is equal to hibernateProperties, p capital.
It's hibernateProperties.
Close that. And within the property element we need to configure key value pairs.
Props is the element because it is of type properties. The first prop, key is,
you know this,
hiberate dot dialect. This is the dialect class that generates the SQL queries from our entities
or for our entities.
Since I am using MySQL database, we need to search for MySQL dialect. Do a control+shift+t, search
for Mysqldialect.
If you are using Oracle, you will search for Oracledialect.
Select that from hibernate. Copy the entire package name starting from here.
Package, grab that, go back to config.xml,
paste it in between the prop tag for value.
Create another property, the second and the last property that we'll be configuring. Prop key is equal
to, within double quotes,
hibernate.show_sql. This is a boolean property, by default it is false.
It should be prop, not prope. Make it true. This tells hibernate that when it generates the queries, when
this dialect generates the queries,
those queries should also be displayed on the console.
You have successfully configured both the properties.
The last property that we need to set on the SessionFactory, the name is annotatedClasses,
c capital. And its list of strings.
Use the list element and we need to pass in the class names which are our entities. Within the list,
we can use value. Go to the product entity, grab the package name up to entity, come back to the config.xml,
paste it, dot, p capital, product.
This property tells hibernate what all are our entities and it will grab them and it knows how to interpret
these annotations inside that entity.
So in this lecture, you have successfully configured the SessionFactory, the LocalSessionFactory from
Spring which implements the SessionFactory interface from hibernate.
You have injected the dataSource which is the first dependency.
You have also provided the hibernateProperties,
the two key properties, hibernate.dialect which generates the SQL queries and also a property called
hibernate.show_sql which prints the, which tells hibernate that it should print the SQL queries
on the console.
And finally, a list of annotated classes, in our case we only have one entity.