In this lecture, you'll configure the key classes which is the HibernateTemplate.
And then we'll inject it into the ProductDao.
Let's get started by going to Eclipse, create a new bean. Let me scroll it up.
Start with the bean element.
Class is equal to HibernateTemplate,
we'll get to that in a second.
Give it a name is equal, hibernateTemplate. Close that bean tag right there. In the class,
we don't, we know the class name. Do a control+shift+t, search for HibernateTemplate.
Again, select the one from hibernate5 package.
Open it up, grab the class name and the package. Come back to config.xml.
Paste the class name. hibernateTemplate takes a SessionFactory,
it depends on the SessionFactory.
We can use the p-schema to inject that. In the bean tag
use p:sessionFactory-ref, it's an object type or reference type.
Use ref.
Copy this name from here.
Paste it right there and close the bean tag right there.
Remove any extra double quotes
if you have them and close that tag right there. Get rid of this bean tag. Do a control+shift+f to format and
we have configured the sessionFactory successfully. Let's autowire this hibernateTemplate, that should
be hibernateTemplate, into our dao class.
Go do ProductDaoImpl and you know how to autowire.
First let's use the @Component
annotation from Spring.
Next use the @Autowired annotation from Spring. Go to config.xml.
Scroll up all the way up right here.
Context colon component-scan, provide the base package to do that.
Go to ProductDaoImpl, grab the package name up to Impl, come back to config.xml, paste
that package name and you can close that element right there.
If you remember, this context:component-scan also enables annotations and it also scans for the classes
which are components, which objects can be created.
So in this lecture, you have successfully configured the hibernateTemplate and you have also injected
it into the ProductDaoImpl.