In this lecture, I will briefly introduce you to transaction management in general and how to do it using
Spring.
When we develop Java EE applications or any application for that matter,
they will execute multiple update statements, that is insert, update, delete against a database and there
could be a business scenario where we want either all of them to succeed or none of them should succeed.
That is where transaction management comes in to do autonomous work.
All the work should be done or none of it should be done. And we do it using commit and rollback.
A simple example is a money transfer. When we transfer money from one bank account to another, we debit it
from the sender and credit it to the receiver.
These two should happen within a single transaction.
If the debit happens and if something goes wrong with the credit everything should be rolled back.
Otherwise the sender will not be happy.
That is where we use transactions.
Spring makes it very easy to do transaction management by providing a TransactionManager for every
template or for JDBC it provides a TransactionManager, for hibernate
it provides a TransactionManager, etc;
So when we are using Hibernate, we'll use the HibernateTransactionManager, we'll configure this bean
in the XML and then we'll use the annotation support that is provided by Spring.
We add this single line once we get the transaction namespace to the XML configuration and Spring will
know that we are going to use annotations to configure transactions.
Once we do these two, the last step is to mark our methods, our Java methods which need transaction with the @Transactional
annotation.
Its that simple.
So create a bean called HibernateTransactionManager and add this annotation, for annotations support,
for transactions.
Once we have these two in our Java classes, you use the @Transactional annotation on any method that you want
a transaction. Spring will then wrap that method around a transaction.
Everything that happens in that method will happen within a single transaction.
And in an exception arises,
Spring will automatically roll back the whole thing. If no exception,
then everything will be committed.