In this lecture, you'll configure one of the last beans which is the TransactionManager. This is an interface
and the implementation of it is HibernateTransactionManager.
So go to Eclipse, to the configuration. At the end,
we are going to add a new bean. Start the bean tag, class is equal to HibernateTransactionManager but
we need the package name. Do a control+shift+t,
search for HibernateTransactionManager and grab the one from hibernate5 package, everything should
be from hibernate5.
Select that, copy the package name and the class name. Come back to config.xml, paste it in between
the double quotes, get rid of any spaces at the beginning or at the end. It should be HibernateTransactionManager
from hibernate5. Name is equal to transactionManager, the only dependency the transactionManager
has is the SessionFactory.
So it works around the SessionFactory, it creates a transaction around a hibernate session. So inject it, p colon
sessionFactory, f capital, is a property name, hyphen ref.
It is of object type.
Within double quotes, grab the name from here, paste it, close the bean tag.
Do a control+shift+f to format. We have successfully configured the transactionManager. Spring will create this.
But to use the transactionManager to create a transaction,
we need to add a few more elements here.
You need to introduce a new namespace.
So copy this c-schema namespace.
Enter, paste it. Change this c to tx for transaction.
We are adding a new namespace for transaction, tx. And at the end,
we also need to add the schema for that namespace.
So copy the last two entries, the context, enter, paste them. Change context to tx. For this namespace
which we have defined here,
the schema file can be found at the following locations. So change, wherever you see context change it to
tx. Schema slash, not context, tx.
That's it.
So you have successfully configured the transactionManager and also got the namespaces .
We can use transactions in our application,
Spring transactions either through XML or annotations. To use the XML or annotated way
of doing it,
you should use tx:annotation-driven. That's it. That tells Spring that we are going to use annotations to
do transactions.
You will use the transactions later on.
You'll use the annotations in the next few lectures.
To summarize, you've configured the transactionManager, added the namespaces so that we can enable
transaction management and also youve given a schema file for it.