We have configured all our beans successfully and we are ready to implement the create method and use
the hibernateTemplate. Before we do that,
a couple of small typos that we need to fix.
If we have got them right
that's great.
When I configure the sessionFactory and used the p-schema,
I haven't used hyphen ref. So p:dataSource-ref is the first one. And the property should
be annotatedClasses, not annotateClasses.
It is all the annotated entities, so add a d if you have missed it like me. That's it, go to the ProductDaoImpl,
and start implementing the create method.
It's going to be very easy.
You will use the hibernateTemplate.save is the method and pass it an entity. Pass it
the product that is being passed to this method and this method returns an object, hit control+1,
assign statement to a new local variable.
It's a serializable object.
Let's use integer. We know that
when the save method returns, it returns an integer. Hit control+1, add a cast to integer. Call it result
and return that result. Do a control+shift+f to format.
And also we need to use transactions because this method is going to write to the database, it's using an insert.
So to use transactions you simply use it @Transactional annotation on your methods, @Transactional from
Spring Framework that tells Spring that this method should be wrapped around a transaction and we have
already configured the transactionManager and annotations for transaction in the configuration file.
So in this lecture, you have successfully implemented the create method.
One last step to go, we'll create the test class and run it.