In this lecture, we are going to create a test class that uses our ProductDaoImpl
and saves a product record to the database. Let's see that in action.
If you are lazy you can copy over the test from the previous project.
I'm going to create it. Right click, new class called test with a main method.
Finish. Do a control+d to delete that.
Start with ApplicationContext, control+space from Spring.
That's the interface.
Context is equal to new ClassPathXmlApplicationContext.
Pass it
the configuration file, config.xml, semi-colon, grab the package name, and you know what to do.
Convert all the dots to forward slashes.
One last one. We have the context, that is access to the Spring container, context.getBean, within
double quotes we need to pass in the bean name.
But if you remember, when we use annotations by default Spring will create a bean with the same name
as the class name.
And if you don't want that, within brackets, within double quotes give it a name, call it productDao.
If not spring will create a camel case name with productDaoImpl.
Either you use it or give it a name here.
I'm going to use the productDao.
Go back to test, within double quotes paste that name, hit control+1, assign statement to a
new local variable.
Change it to productDao, hit control+1, import it. Another control+1, add cast.
So you know that control+1 is my favorite key
while using Eclipse. Call this productDao. productDao dot,
create is the method, create a new product. Hit control+space,
import the product.
That is the bean we need to pass. Select that, control+1, extract to local variable called product.
Set the values on it.
Product dot setId, the very first one is id, let's say 1 is the value. Product dot setName, within
double quotes,
Iphone. Product dot set description, desc, within double quotes
its awesome.
And finally product dot setPrice, let's say 700 bucks.
Save it. Do a control+shift+f to format. Go to the database and check if you have any records.
Execute the select query on the product table.
Run it.
There are no records right now.
Come back to the test.
Right click, run as java application.
Hit Ok to save it.
And look at the console and you will see that Hibernate generates a insert query automatically, we didn't
write this insert query.
Now let's go to the database and check if it has inserted the right values.
There we go.
1 is the id, Iphone,
It's awesome and the price is 700 bucks.
So you have successfully executed your very first Hibernate and Spring program.