In the previous lecture, you have successfully created a database product record using the hibernateTemplate.
In this lecture you will learn how to update the product information, how to update the product price.
We'll update it from 700 bucks to $800.
Let's do that by going to Eclipse. Go to the productDao, the interface and add a new method, void update
product. It takes the product entity and it updates whatever information we provide in the product entity.
Go to ProductDaoImpl, click n wherever it says error, hit control+1, add unimplemented methods. Hit control+d to delete
the TODO block. And to implement the update,
it's one single line. hibernateTemplate.update is the method and we pass it the entity which
is the product that comes in as the parameter. And that's it. That will do the magic for us.
But we need to mark this method with @Transactional because it is also a update method. Mark it
with @Transactional. Go to the test.java to test our update method, comment out the create portion, wherever
we are invoking the create method. Change some data here.
Let's update the price to 800 dollars.
And invoke productDao.update and pass in the product. Since it has the unique id here, hibernate
knows how to update the record using this as the condition. Let's run the test.
Let me maximize that. And it generates the update product set description name and price where it uses the id in
the where clause because we have marked the id field,
if you remember, as the primary key. If you go to Product.java, the id field is marked with the
@Id. So it automatically uses it in the where clause.
Let's go to database and see if that record got updated.
Execute the select and the price has changed to 800 dollars.
So you have successfully used the hibernateTemplate.update and updated the record.