In this lecture you will implement the delete method in the ProductDao and delete a particular record from
the database. Go to the ProductDao, void delete is the method.
And all we need to give it is a product entity.
And it should have a
Id inside it. It need not have the other information.
All that is required is the id field. Go to the ProductDaoImpl, control+1, add unimplemented methods.
Go all the way to the end, control+d to delete that. Use the hibernateTemplate.delete and pass it the entity
which is product. Do a control+shift+f to format. Mark it with @Transactional, don't forget to do that. Go to
the test
and comment out the update. Do a ProductDao.delete and pass in the product.
We have only one product record in the database.
Let's go to the database, do a select operation to make sure that we have a record.
We do. So come back, run the test.
See what statement is being generated.
So it does a select first internally and then it does a delete.
So it's fetches the record and then it deletes it internally.
So let's go to the database, do a select operation and there are no records.
So you have also successfully deleted the record.