In this lecture, you will learn how to read a database record using hibernateTemplate. To do that,
let's put a couple of records in the database.
Execute a couple of insert statements. Insert into product values, within brackets provide the values
1 comma the name is Iphone comma,
description is Good, comma,
the price is 800 dollars.
Execute that. We have one record, copy that. Or simply change it.
It's up to you. Id 2, MacBook.
It's also good.
The price is 1400 dollars. Select that, execute it and we have one more record. Go back to Eclipse, start implementing
the read method. Go to ProductDao. This method should return a product back and call it find. Given
a int product, int id of the product,
it should return the product entity back.
That is the method. Go to ProductDaoImpl, control+1, add unimplemented methods. All the way down
to implement the find method, delete the TODO. hibernateTemplate.get is the method.
It takes two things, the class type, we need to tell it what type of entity should be returned.
In our case it is product.class and also the Id field which is the id here.
Hit control+1, assign statement to a new local variable and it will return a product because we are
telling that the entity that comes back is of product type. We are using generics here.
Copy the product, instead of returning null return that product back.
It's that easy.
Use the get method, tell it what type of entity is going to come back and pass the unique id and hibernate will
automatically create a select statement, get the data back, put it into a product entity and return that
product entity to us. Go to test, comment out everything, use a block comment.
Get rid of these comments here.
Comment everything upto this portion here.
ProductDao, take out this single line comment as well,
dot, we need this ProductDao. Only comment out from product all the way down.
productDao.find is the method. Pass in the id which is 1 and that should return, hit control+1,
assign statement to a new local variable, a product. Sysout, display the product. Control+shift+f to format.
Right click, run as Java application.
And we get a product object back. Our entity class does not implement the toString  method. Go to Product,
go to source, generate toString. Hit
OK. Do a Control+shift+f to format. Rerun the test and this time we should see the details as well.
Hibernate executes the select query,
we get the data back, it converts it into an object and gives us back. The id is 1, name is Iphone,
description is good and price is 800 dollars.