In the previous lecture, you have successfully implemented the find method which returns a single record
from the database as an object.
In this lecture, you will learn how to read multiple records. That is,
we should get a list of products. Let's implement that method, list of products is what it should
return in the ProductDao.
Call it findAll, everything in the database, no parameters to it. Control+1, import the list from
java.util. Go to the ProductDaoImpl all the way up, control+1 on the error,
add the implemented methods which is the findAll method.
Delete the TODO. hibernateTemplate.loadAll is the method.
It takes the entity type.
We need to tell it what type of records are going to come back.
It's Product.class generics
again. We are telling that it should return a list of product types. Control+1, assign statement to
a new local variable and it returns a list of products. And return that products back. Control+shift+f to format,
its products.
Go to the test.
Comment out this find method.
productDao.findAll is the method.
Hit control+1, assign statement to a new local variable.
It returns a list of products back.
Display those products.
Run the test.
And we have two products. Here is product 1, the first record and here is the second record.
So you should use the get method when you are loading a single record and you should use the
hibernateTemplate.loadAll to load all the records in database table.