In this lecture, I will summarize what you have learnt from the Spring
ORM section. ORM stands for Object Relational Mapping and tools like Hibernate, ORM tools or frameworks
like Hibernate will map our Java objects to database or relational database rows.
They will also generate the SQL that is required to insert,  delete, update and query these rows
from the database.
They will automatically convert our objects into the data in the table rows and vice versa. When the data
comes back,
Hibernate will automatically convert the row into an object. Spring simplifies using Hibernate by providing
an integration with Hibernate.
It gives us a HibernateTemplate class.
We configure this class which depends on SessionFactory. SessionFactory needs dataSource, hibernateProperties.
Datasource, you know that it takes care of creating the database connection. hibernateProperties,
there are a couple of important properties which you have configured. They are dialect.
It is a class, these are key value pairs. Using dialect property we specify a class for SQL,
MySQL it is different, for Oracle it is different. So for each database,
the dialect class is responsible for generating the SQL commands.
The second property is show_sql which is a boolean property.
By default it is false.
It tells hibernate that it should log all the queries that it generates on the console so that we can
see what's going on against the database.
The value you should be using is true to enable it.
Finally annotatedClasses.
These are the entities which is very first step. When we start using Hibernate we first create entities
which are Java classes, which map to a database table.
We do that using annotations from JPA, Java Persistence API. We mark our classes with annotations such
as @Entity, @Table,
@Column, @Id, etc; Once we have the hibernateTemplate bean,
we can perform the database crud operations using the methods on it such as save, update, delete, get to get
a single object, and loadAll to get a list of objects which are list of rows in the database. While we
use these methods, we'll not be passing any SQL, we'll be using objects instead. ORM tools like Hibernate
will do the conversion for us and generate the queries.