To work on the hibernate use case or the ORM use case we are going to reuse the table from the Spring
JDBC.
It's kind of a migration project where we are migrating from Spring JDBC to ORM or using
Hibernate.
So we'll reuse the passenger table that's already there in the database. Copy over the Passenger class from
the earlier project so that you can make it an entity. You'll do that using the @Entity annotation
and the @Id annotations which are mandatory. And optionally,
you can use the @Table and Column annotations.
Once you make the Passenger a model object or an entity, you will then configure the SessionFactory and the
hibernateTemplate
in the spring configuration. The dataSource, you can ofcourse you need to configure the dataSource
which will be used by the SessionFactory and hibernateTemplate. And once you have it, create a test
class and perform the crud operations using save, update, delete, get which will get one single record
and loadAll which loads all the passengers in the database table.