So far you have used xml configuration to create objects and to do dependency injection. In
this,
and the next few lectures you will learn how to use the stereotype annotations from Spring to create
objects and to inject them. We'll do it in two simple steps.
First, we'll mark our classes with the @Component stereotype annotation from Spring.
The stereotype annotations are used to create objects. This is equivalent to using the bean tag in the
XML.
Once we do that, the second step is to use one single XML element in the configuration file called
context:component-scan. Using this element, we tell the Spring container which all packages it needs
to scan for classes marked with this component annotation.
Here, we use the base-package attribute and we are telling the Spring container that it should
scan a package called com.bharath and all its subpackages for classes marked with @Component. Whatever
package we give here,
Spring container will also search that package as well as it's subpackages
for classes marked with the @Component annotation. For example, here,
I have all these packages the parent and the subpackages. com has one, three, four, two, five, six as the packages and all
these packages have classes.
So if I use com.one as the base package, then the Spring container will scan this package
com which has a class A, then it will scan one for class B and also one subpackage which are three and
four and it'll find classes C and D as well.
If I use com.two.five.F then it will only scan the five package.
It doesn't have any subpackages, so it will only find F, class F.
And if I use com as the base package, then it will scan all the subpackages. So it will find A, B, C,
D, E, F, G.
That is how the scanning works.
The container by default,
when we mark a class with @Component annotation, it will create an object like this.
That is, it will use the class name for the object reference name and it uses camel case to name it, to
name the reference variable. So when we read the object in our test or anywhere in our application, we
should use the camel case to retrieve that object from Spring.
Last but not least, we can use the @Component annotation,
ofcourse only on the classes that we create.
We cannot use it on the inbuilt classes like string etc; are third party classes because that code is
already compiled.
We don't have access to the source code.
So to summarize, we use the @Component scan to mark our classes and then we define a configuration
in the Spring configuration, through which we tell the Spring container which all classes it needs to
scan and create objects for. In the next few lectures,
you will see these in action.