In this lecture you will create an object in two simple steps. That is, you are going to create an instructor
class, mark it with the @Component annotation and then create the configuration which will have the context:
component-scan element.
And ofcourse finally you will create a test class to see it all in action. Go to Eclipse, right click,
create a new class called Instructor or Teacher.
com.bharath.springcoreadvanced.stereotype.annotations. Finish. The instructor will
have an int id to start with, the String name.
Let's start with those two fields. Control+1, create getter and setters. Control+1 for the name, create getters and
setters as well.
Hit Ok. Control+shift+f to format. Source,
generate the toString method.
OK and we have the toString method. The second step is to create the configuration file. Grab the earlier
configuration, paste it. Open it. Get rid of everything in the configuration.
We need only one single element, that is the beauty of using stereotype annotations. From the context
namespace, it is not annotation-config, it is context:component-scan. We can close it right here.
We don't need an ending element. And for the attribute base-package, we should provide the package
the Spring container needs to scan for the classes marked with @Component annotation.
We haven't marked our instructor with the @Component annotation.
Let's do that. @Compo, control+space from org.springframework.stereotype. This is the package,
org.springframework.stereotype.Component is the annotation.
Once we do that, grab this package name and put it in the configuration file.
We can also use subpackages even if you say com.bharath.springcoreadvanced, Spring container will
scan the sub packages of it as well.
But let's be very specific and give the complete package.
Remove any spaces and that's it. The last step is to create a test.
This particular element here also internally enables the annotation config. So it also enables all the
annotations and then it also scans this package.
We need not use the context:annotation-config anymore.
You are welcome to use it, but it is not required.
Copy the test.
That is the last step.
Paste it. Open the test. We've got to change the package names as well as the objects.
The object is Instructor.
Copy it, paste it on the left side.
Call it instructor, and display the instructor. The bean name if you remember, by default,
if you go back to the theory portion, Spring will create an object with this name, the same name as the
class,
but in camel case. So instructor will be the name of the bean. Grab the package name from here.
stereotype.annotations.
Copy that, get rid of standalone and collections or whichever package you have and change it to
stereotype/annotations/config.xml. And that's it. Right click, run the java application and
you will see the instructor object.
Ofcourse it has the default values, we are not injecting any values.
I will show you how to inject values later on.
To summarize, in this lecture you have created an object or a class called Instructor. You have marked
it with @Component annotation which tells the Spring container that an object of this class can be
created or should be created. And the second step was in a configuration file, you've told Spring which packages
it needs to scan for the classes to create objects for using the context:component-scan.