The Spring container when we use the @Component annotation by default uses the class name to name the object
reference as well, but it uses camel case.
That is the reason in our test class, when we read the bean from the container, we have used instructor.
I small,
i is small, instructor. But we can change it, and we can use whatever name we want.
Go back to the instructor class. On the component annotation,
we can provide value within double quotes and this will be the bean name. Instead of instructor,
am giving inst.
Now if you go to test class, right click, run it, we should get an exception. It should say bean not found.
Maximize the console.
It says NoSuchBeanDefinitionException: No bean named instructor is available, because once we start
using a value on the component annotation, the Spring container will create a bean with that name. In
our test class,
now we should use inst instead of instructor. Save it, rerun the test. And now it creates an object.
So to name a particular bean while using the @Component annotation, you should use it on the component
annotation, within double quotes, you need to provide a value.