You have already learnt and used the various scopes that Spring offers. That is singleton, prototype
request, session and globalsession.
You have used the first two types through XML configuration.
You will learn request and session when you work on Spring MVC web applications. And globalsession
applies for portlet applications. In this lecture, you will learn how to configure the scopes using
annotation instead of XML configuration.
Go to Eclipse. By default,
if we do not use any scope
can you tell me what the Spring container uses as scope? Yes,
you are right.
It uses singleton scope. That is, it creates only one object no matter how many times we retrieve it
in our application.
So go to the test class, copy these two lines here.
Let's create one more object. Let's ask
Spring container to give us one more object. Name it instructor2. Let's display the hashCode values. instructor
dot hashCode within sysout, instructor2.hashCode(). Save it, run the test. And the output
is, we have the same hashCode for both the objects. That is, Spring is creating only one object no matter
how many times we are reading it.
Now let's configure the scope by going to the Instructor.java. Right next to the @Component annotation
if we use the scope always with @Component annotation, we can't use it on its own.
We use it with other stereotype annotations. @Scope, within brackets, double quotes, prototype. Control+1,
import it from org.springframework.context.annotation. Control+shift+f to format.
Go back to the test.
Right click, ran as Java application. And this time you will see that both the hashCodes are different.
That is the spring container
is creating different objects every time we ask it for an object of that type.