In the previous few lectures, you have learnt how to create objects in Spring using annotations instead
of XML configuration.
You have successfully used the @Component and @Scope annotations.
But when we ran our tests, go to the test, get rid of this hashCode.
I want to display the object and see the values inside it. Remove both the hashCodes for instructor and instructor2.
Run the test again.
And it injects the default values, because we are not providing any values in the XML configuration
or through annotations.
You already know how to provide values to a bean through XML configuration using the value
tag.
But here, we are using component annotation.
Everything here is being done through annotations.
So in this lecture, you will learn about the @Value annotation which can be used to inject values. For
primitive types, we use @Value and provide the value within double quotes. This is an integer. For a string,
this is how we provide the value, within double quotes again. For collection types,
we do it in two steps.
We first create a collection in the XML configuration using the util schema.
You know how to do that.
We assign it a id, it could be a list, set, map etc.;
Once we have an Id, we use the value annotation in our class, in our Spring pojo class and we use
something called spring expression language. You we learn more about this in lectures later on.
For now you need to use a
Pound or a hash symbol. Within flower bracket,
you need to give the id which you have used when you created that collection.
So we use, or we refer to the collection we create in the XML configuration in the value tag, using this
syntax of hash, then flower brackets and then the Id or the reference. Finally, for injecting object types.
So if one class depends on another class, then we can do it simply using autowiring.
You are going to see all these in action in this and the next few lectures. Let's start with primitive
types.
Go to instructor.
We have two types here, Id
and then the name. Let's assign them a value.
@Value is the annotation, within brackets within double quotes,
we can provide the value. Say 10, save it.
Hit control+1, import it from org.springframework.beans.factory.annotation is the package.
Use @Value again. Assign a value, name of the instructor is Bharath Thippireddy, that's me.
Do a control+shift+f to format. Run the test again. And this time we should see the values,
right here.
And these annotations override any values we assign using assignment.
For example, here if I assign a value let's say 15 and the name is John instead of Bharath. Save it, run
the test again. The values you see are those being provided through annotations and not those being assigned.
So the annotations always override the values we assign.
So in this lecture, you have successfully learnt that you can use the @Value annotation when we inject
or when we use annotations to create spring objects to assign values. In the next few lectures,
you will also learn how to assign collection types and object types.