In this lecture, you will learn how to inject a collection type using the @Value annotation.
You will do it in two simple steps. We are going to add a list to this instructor pojo.
And two steps are, first you will create an object or create the collection in the XML configuration
using the util schema.
And then you'll use the @Value annotation on the list in the pojo
with the spring expression language to inject it. Let's get  started. Go to instructor, and this
instructor will have a private list of strings which will tell what all topics he is going to teach or
he teaches. Control+1, import list from Java util. The first step is going to the configuration file.
Use the util:list. For using this,
you need to have the util schema here
and the namespace defined. You know how to do that from previous lectures on util schema or standalone collections.
On the util:list the very first attribute is list-class, the class that we want to use.
Let's say java.util.LinkedList.
Second is the id, the important piece. Call it topics. And within the list we can use the value element
and provide the values.
These are the topics that I teach on Udemy. There are several others,
but these are some of them. Java web services, Core Java.
Let's add one more value,
XSLT. Save it. Go back to the instructor. The second step is to use the @Value annotation. Within brackets
this time we're going to use the spring expression language and the syntax. Within brackets, within double
quotes, use the pound symbol or the hash. Start flower brackets or braces within which you'll provide
the name of that collection bean in the config, which is topics, the id, the reference, the object reference. Save it.
Delete the toString method, regenerate it so that it will also use the collection in the toString. Go to source, generate
toString.
Hit OK.
It will also display the list this time.
Go to the test.
Right click, run as java application and in the output,
this time you are going to see the injected list as well.
So you have successfully injected a collection type as well as primitive types. In the next lecture,
you will learn how to inject the object type using the autowired annotation.