You have injected primitive types.
You have also injected the collection type using annotations. In this lecture,
you are going to use the @Autowired annotation which you already know, to inject the object types or
reference types. Go to Eclipse.
Let's add another object dependency or a class dependency for Instructor.
Instructor has a profile. private Profile profile; import profile from Spring framework. Hit control+1,
there is a profile in spring framework, don't import it. Create a class. Select that option.
Hit Finish. Profile will have two string fields,
we are going to capture private String.
The first field will be the instructor's title and string company,
the company he works for.
Let's keep it simple.
Very simple profile, control+1,
create setters and getters.
OK.
You can also generate getters and setters for both of them at once.
Do control+shift+f
to format. Generate the toString method as well.
Save it. Do a control+shift+f
Add the @Component annotation on this so that we are telling Spring that we want to create an object
of this type. @Component, and assign some values @Value, within double quotes,
title Java Architect and instructor.
That's my title. Company, @Value, within double quotes Vivekananda Consulting. You are welcome to use
different values.
You can use your own profile information here instead of mine.
Save it.
Go back to the instructor. To inject profile,
you simply mark it using @Autowired annotation from Spring Framework.
So we have done it in two steps. The first step was to create a profile and to mark it using the @Component
annotation,
that tells Spring that an object of this class can be created.
We have also assigned values to the fields using the @Value annotation. And in the config.xml,
when we use the @Autowired annotation,
the second thing we do is, we configure this annotation called component-scan and we provide a base package.
Spring is going to scan this package and all it's subpackages.
We are good because the profile also is in the same package.
So it's going to scan this as well. It will instantiate it, inject these values and then it will use this
bean to inject it into our instructor object.
Let's see if all that works. Go to test,
right click, run as Java Application and you will see two instructor instances.
The toString method needs to be changed on the instructor.
That is the reason we are not seeing that object.
So delete the toString, save it. Source,
Generate toString() one more time so that our profile will also be included.
Hit OK and the profile information will be included this time. We already have a toString method on the profile.
Run the test again.
Maximize and there we go.
Now the instructor, along with Id topics, also has a profile object injected.
That is the power of annotations without writing much XML, very little XML. In the configuration
file,
all we have is this context:component-scan and if we are not using collections then we don't even have this.