In this lecture, I will summarize what you have learned from the stereotype annotations section which
is a very important section in Spring core.
You have learnt that instead of using the XML configuration, we can use the @Component annotation
to mark our java classes and Spring will automatically create the object of that particular class. To tell
the Spring container about the packages to scan for these classes marked with @Component annotation in
XML configuration,
we use the context:component-scan and we provide the base package which the Spring container will scan for
the beans marked with this particular annotation.
It will create the objects, does the dependency injection etc; It will scan this package as well as all
its sub packages for the classes.
And when we use stereotype annotation or annotations like @Component, we also use @Scope to
specify the scope of that particular bean which could be singleton, prototype, request, session etc.;
And to provide values or to inject values, we use the @Value annotation. We can inject primitive types and collection
types using the @Value annotation. And to inject the object types or reference types we use the
@Autowired annotation.