In this lecture you will learn what spring is by the end of it if there are two things that I want
you to understand and remember they are spring
is a dependency injection framework, number two
it compilements the existing Java EE standards by making them easier for us the developers to use.
That brings us to dependency injection. When we develop software applications we organize our code across
components in case of Java these components are classes.
Here I have Class A which depends on Class B to get its work done.
So these components typically use each other.Instead of we creating an object of class B in class A we
delegate this responsibility to frameworks like spring. Spring at runtime dynamically create an object
of class B and it will inject it into Class A We as a developers can simply focus on our business logic instead
of worrying about the object creation.This process of moving the control of object creation from the
application code to a external framework
is called inversion of control it is a design pattern.
We are giving away the object creation control from our application code to a external framework
or container like spring.
So where does Dependency Injection apply in case of Java.
EE applications. Any java EE application if you take a look at it, it will be typically organized into
layers UI layers, services layer, data access layer and more.
Each of these layers use the services provided by the layer below.
For example, the UI layer we have order controller which an order service, the order service in turn will
use the services provided by the order DAO.
This is where spring dependency injection will come in spring will automatically create the order DAO
it will inject it into the order service.It will automatically create the order service and inject it into the order controller.
That is where dependency injection comes-in in JavaEE
along with dependancy injection,
the second thing I want you to understand is that spring makes it very easy for us the developers to
use the existing API's and frameworks.
For example, spring provides spring JDBC which you can think off as a wrapper around the JDBC standard
from oracle and as a developer we can execute sequel statement in one single line.
It will take away all the repeated code that is there in JDBC.
Similarly it will make our life very easy by providing spring ORM using spring ORM object relational
mapping
will be able to use ORM tools like hibernate in a very simple manner and in the UI layer it provides
integration with Struts java server faces to develop beautiful faces
again in simple steps.
And also if the community or the people developers at Spring feel that a particular javaEE standard
or a framework is difficult to use for example struts or even JSF then they come up with a parallel
implementation.
One such implementation is the spring MVC.
Using this you can develop the web layer for your web applications you will be learning spring MVC in detail
in lectures later on.
And also spring provide services like security transaction management which we can simply configure and are
ready to use.
To summarize spring is a dependency injection framework when we have classes that depend on each other
will delegate that responsibility to spring.
And it will automatically create those objects then inject them. In a Java application,
these classes are spread across the layers of our application and also spring makes it easy to use existing
standards like JDBC, ORM and UI technologies such as struts JSF etc. and it also provides services
like security transaction management which we can configure in simple steps.