The primitive type dependencies can be injected using constructor injection or setter injection and
using the value tag.
Here I have a class called product which needs or which has a dependency called ID which is of type integer
we are injecting it using the property element that is through setter injection and using the value
tag we are providing a value to it.
The value can be used as an xml element.
It can also be used as an attribute instead of defining a separate element here on the property element.
We can use a attribute called value and assign this value to it. A third and compact way of
assigning or injecting primitive types is using p schema or P namespace with very few lines of xml will
be able to inject values using P schema.
Right on this bean element we use the P schema attributes you we will learn all these three ways and work
on them in the next few lectures.