In this lecture, you will learn how to create a standalone collection and inject it into a POJO or a
Spring bean.
You will create a class called ProductsList and then you will inject a list into it using the standalone
syntax or the util schema. Go to Eclipse,
right click on the source package of springcoreadvanced, new -> class, call it ProductsList.
It will carry a list of product names.
The package is com.bharath.springcoreadvanced.standalone.collections.
Finish. This POJO or Spring bean will have one list of strings, which are the productNames. Control+1,
import the list from Javautil, control+1 on productNames,
create the getters and setters so that we can do setter injection.
Save it. Next step is to create the configuration file which is the most important step.
Grab the config.xml from an other package.
Paste it.
Open it.
Delete everything inside the beans element. The very first step
if you remember, is to add the namespaces that are required to use the util schema. You have already used the C schema
and P schema.
So it's very straight-forward.
Copy one of these lines that say the P schema one, enter, right after the C schema, paste it. Change p to util.
Similarly on the left hand side, the prefix that we are going to use will be util.
So this util prefix points to this namespace and we can use all the elements from that namespace by using
util.
It is like a placeholder for this namespace.
Next, we need to add the schema location as well.
So grab the last two lines, the context and its schema.
Copy them, go to the end before the semicolon, before the double quotes, enter, paste them.
Change everything that says context to util. Util and also spring-context
here should be changed to util.
So you have added the namespaces, the very first time we add it and save it, the schema will be downloaded
from the internet and we can use all the elements from it.
So let's get started, first create the list,
this particular list in a standalone manner. Instead of using the list element we'll use util colon, the
syntax, as you can see here, the util colon, the collection name.
Eclipse will help you out with it.
util colon, and it gives you all the collections you can use. List is what we want to use.
Next is list-class, the collection hyphen class, is equal to within double quotes,
you need to provide the complete qualified name of the collection, java.util.
I want to use Linked list.
I don't want to use arraylist which is by default. An Id, a unique Id so that we can refer to it later
on.
ProductsNames, this can be anything but in ProductsList we have used it as productNames.
That is the reason I am using it. You can also say PN instead of ProductNames and within the list, you
can add multiple values.
Value, let's say Macbook. I am an Apple fan.
You are welcome to add other products as well instead of Apple products.
Iphone, save it. Now we have successfully defined a standalone collection. It is standalone because it
is not inside a bean.
It is on its own. It stands on its own.
This can be used inside another bean. bean, class is equal to ProductsList, grab the package
name. Go to the bean, copy the package name, come back to config.xml, paste it, dot, give it a
name, is equal to productsList, close it. Within the bean tag, lets do property injection using the property
name is equal to productNames.
That is the name of the property right here, productNames.
Within the property tag, you can use ref.
We can also use ref as an attribute.
Let's use ref as element, bean is equal to whatever Id we have given here. We are going to refer
to that collection bean. Delete the extra double quores and close the ref right there. Remove unwanted lines. Save it.
Do a control+shift+f to format.
So you have successfully created a standalone bean and you have also injected it into another bean which
uses it. Next,
grab the test, paste it. Open the test, make the changes. You know by now what changes you need to make. We
need to change this package to standalone.collections. So get rid of autowiring/annotations, paste
standalone.collections, change the dot to forward slash. And this employee should be gone except for the productsList
Same on the left hand side as well.
Grab that, paste it, change the name to pl for productsList and pl. Here, instead of employee, it should
be the name of our bean, which is productsList.
Copy that, paste it in the test. Control+shift+f to format. Right click, run it, run as Java application. It is an exception.
Lets see what it is. It says Invalid property 'productName'. So in our config.xml, instead of productNames
I think I have used productName somewhere. Right here, the property names should be productNames and not
productName. Let's rerun the test.
And this time, it does the injection.
There is no toString method, that is the reason we are seeing the object. Go to productList, generate
the toString by going to source -> generate toString().
Hit OK.
Rerun the test and we see the list of products.
So we have successfully configured a standalone list collection.
You specified that you want a linked list and not an array list and you have injected into another bean.
This can be injected into any number of beans.
It is not local to this particular bean anymore.