In this lecture, you will pass data from the controller to the UI page and display it on the UI.
Let's do that by going to the Controller which is the HelloController. Double click to maximize it.
And right after setting the view you're going to set the data into the model using ModelAndView dot
addObject is the method which takes a key and a value.
The key is string.
Let's set some employee information, employee id, employee name and his salary. Id,
let's start with primitive types and then you will learn how to do with objects. And the id is 123
which is of integer type. ModelAndView, let's set his name. addObject,
select the last one, within double quotes name. And the name is Bharath. ModelAndView, the last one which
is salary.addObject, select the last one again, double quotes, salary. Let's say 10000 bucks. You
can use whatever type of data you want because the second parameter is an object. Do control+shift+f to
format, delete any unwanted lines and that's it.
So along with the view name we are setting the data.
Now go to hello.jsp to process it.
Get rid of this H1,
Hello from spring MVC in the body.
We can display the data in two ways.
The first way is using the JSP syntax, the expressions
or the scriptlets.
Within this you can use object obj is equal to request.getAttribute, pass the key.
So whatever we have set in the controller, this ModelAndView, is available in the request.
So we have to say request.getAttribute("id") and that will return object type.
We can typecast it to an integer, because we know that it's an integer value, integer.
The second is string. So you can typecast it to string, copy this,
this line here, copy it a couple of times or paste it a couple of times. The second parameter is name and
the third parameter is salary.
The second one should be typecasted to string.
The first one is the id. Give them names, name. And the last one is salary.
String, do a control+shift+f to format.
So this is how you retrieve whatever model data you have set into the ModelAndView, that will be available
on the request object and you can retrieve it and display it. To display it,
you can use out.println. Out is the implicit JSP object.
Id, add some text to it.
Id colon, that, copy that line, paste it a couple of times.
Second is name. Display the name. Third is salary, display the salary. Save it, control+shift+f. To run the application
right click, Run as -> run on server, finish.
This will open the index,jsp but we want to access spring MVC. This is the index.jsp slash,
if you remember if you go to the controller, the url which we have mapped is hello.
So copy that, come back to the browser within Eclipse. Paste it at the end, remove any double quotes.
Close it, right click, run as -> run on server. Hit
Ok to finish. At the end add a
hello. Enter.
It runs and the output is the id, the name and the salary. You can use HTML as well if you want
to and format it a little better.
So in this lecture, you have successfully sent the data from the controller by setting it on the
ModelAndView as object by using the addObject method and you have retrieved it in the JSP
using the request implicit object dot getAttribute.