A second way to process the data inside the JSP page is to use the JSP expression language. It has
nothing to do with Spring or Spring MVC but its a convenient method. So let's use it. To use the JSP
expression language,
we use the dollar symbol and within flower brackets, open and close brace, simply use the attribute that
is in the request or session or whichever scope. In this case it is in the request scope.
And automatically the JSPEL will evaluate it.
That is, it will search in the request scope, get the value of it and it will display its value.
Let's put it inside a bold tag, HTML bold tag. Close the bold tag right there.
And this is id colon, copy that line, paste it a couple of times. Do a control+shift+f to format.
The second one is name and the third one is salary, colon add a line break right here. br slash.
So we got Id, name.
Get rid of the extra id here.
Salary, name and then the Id. Save it, go back to the web browser.
But for this to work, there is one thing you need to do. You need to get rid of this doc type HTML
which Eclipse generates. If you have it here,
the EL is not going to be evaluated.
I have seen this issue.
So get rid of this line.
Go back to the web browser to the Hello, refresh.
And we are displaying the details again, but this time it is using the JSP Expression Language which is
very simple, similar to the Spring Expression Language. Dollar symbol, within floor brackets,
the name of the variable which we have set in to the model, id, name and salary. Automatically the Expression
Language, the dollar symbol will evaluate this value.
If we look for this, an attribute with this name in the request scope, get its value and display it to
the end user.