So far you have learnt how to send primitive data from the controller to the UI. In this and the
next lecture, you're going to send object data to the UI using the same addObject method.
So let's get started by creating a new object to hold this data,
the employee information, the id, the name and the salary.
Right click on the java package, new -> class. Call it employee. Instead of controller put it into a package
called dto. Finish, dto for data transfer object. Maximize, private int id, private string name,
private double salary.
Let's make salary double.
Select them all, generate the getters and setters.
I want them, select all, after salary.
Hit OK.
Control+shift+f to format. Go to source, add the toString method as well.
And we have the Employee class which we are going to use inside a new Controller class that we are going
to create. Right click on the controller package, new -> class, call it ObjectController because it's going
to return an object. ObjectController with one single method called public, returns a ModelAndView
just like our earlier method. sendObject, format it.
And it should return a new ModelAndView. Add a return statement so that the errors will go away.
Select this, control+1, Assign statement to a new local variable. Call it ModelAndView, that's fine.
ModelAndView, the very first thing we're going to do is to set a view name. We don't have a view yet. Let's
call that view as object. When we create the JSP page, it'll be object.jsp or let's call it displayObject.jsp.
O is capital, we are following camel case convention. The next important piece is to set the model
data. To do that, ModelAndView.addObject, key value pairs. Call the key employee.
You can call it whatever you want.
You can call it emp if you want to.
And the value is a new Employee.
You are going to send an object back. Select that, new Employee.
Hit control+1, extract to a local variable. Call it employee. Now assign values to it or set the properties
on it. Employee dot setId is 1234, employee dot setName, not the id
again, the name. setName, within double quotes John.
employee dot setSalary, let's say 8000 that's bucks per month.
Do a control+shift+f to format. Add a RequestMapping, RequestMapping, map it to a URL or a URI.
Within double quotes, if you go look at the other controller, the HelloController,
we use a forward slash and then the URI. Let's say readObject. You can give whatever URL you want here
and that's it.
So in this lecture, you have successfully created a DTO, an object called employee with three fields
and you are returning that from the controller to a view called
displayObject. You will create this view in the next lecture.