In this lecture, you'll create the displayObject.jsp which will get the data from the controller and
it will display that data to the end user. Before we do that,
we need to mark this ObjectController with the @Controller annotation from Spring.
We shouldn't forget that.
Go to views, right click, create a new JSP file and the name of it should be displayObject.jsp. Finish.
Let's use a different syntax this time to display the data.
Title is object details. Within the body,
use a JSP expression, less than symbol, percentage, is equal to, request.getAttribute,
within double quotes, employee.
That is what we have used in ObjectController, when we set it into the ModelAndView,
the name is employee and that will be available in the request scope. Control+shift+f to format.
Restart the server because we have been adding several classes. Tomcat automatically loads every time
we add a class or so, but it's always a good practice to restart it.
Go to the browser here where it says hello, instead of hello the URL that we should be using
this time,
if you go to the ObjectController, it is the readObject.
So go back to the browser, readObject, enter. It runs and we see the employee information. The Employee
object comes back, its toString method is being used and the details are displayed.