So far you have worked with primitive types as well as objects types. You have both types of data from the
controller to the view. In this
and the next lecture, you'll learn how to send a list, list of objects. Let's start by creating a Controller.
Copy the ObjectController, paste it on the controller package.
Rename it to ListController, remove the 2 at the end.
Hit OK.
Open the ListController.
Change this from readObject to readList. The method name can be anything.
Change it as well to sendList instead.
The view name will be displayList. From object
everything changes to list. On the ModelAndView, instead of setting one single object,
this time we are going to create a new array list of employees.
Create a new array list of employee. Hit control+1, import array list from java.util.
Control+1, assign statement to a new local variable.
Call it employee. Copy this entire employee creation and setting of data and paste it couple of times,
employee2 and employee3. Change this from, set employee id to 2, John, you can change to Bharath and his salary
is 10000. Change the id to 3.
Bob is the third guy and his salary is 7000 dollars.
And this list is a list of employees.
So add those three employees to this list, employees dot add employee.
That is the first one.
employees.add(employee2) and one more to go. Copy this, paste it, employee 3.
So we have set all the three employees into the list. Now set
that list into the ModelAndView.
Call it employees. Instead of employee,
the key should be, give it a meaningful name,
employees. And this object here should also be employees. Instead of object you are sending an entire list
back to the view. In the next lecture you will create the view and see it all in action.