Before we create the displayList.jsp in this lecture, let's set these values on the right objects.
That is, we have created employee2 and 3.
But I haven't changed the setters here.
It should be employee2.setId
and the name and salary similarly.
Employee3 dot setId, name and salary.
Once we have it, go to the views, right click. By now you know what to do. View -> New -> JSP. Call it
displayList because that is the name we have used in the controller. displayList.jsp, finish.
We need two imports here.
So right on this page directive, go to the end before the percentage, greater than symbol, use an import attribute
is equal to, within double quotes,
we need the Employee object.
So go to the Employee.java, grab the package name all the way till dto, come back.
Paste it, dot employee. We are going to use employee and also a java.util.list.
So all the imports should be comma separated within the import, within the double quotes. Go to the body use the
scriptlets, less than symbol, percentage, percentage greater than symbol. Within that request.getAttribute.
And the key is employees.
That is what we have set on the ModelAndView in the ListController, employees.
That is how we can retrieve it. Come back and this will return a list of employees.
We know that.
So we can typecast it into that employees, is equal to, within brackets, list of, within angular brackets,
Employee. By default,
this returns an object type.
We need to typecast it to whatever type. In this case it is list of employees. Use a for-each loop. For
each employee, employee e colon, employees, open the floor bracket, end it, out.println. Use the
out implicit object, e.getId.
Similarly you can copy this, paste it. e.getName, that's enough, two fields, id and name. Do a control+
shift+f to format.
So we have successfully retrieved the employees from the request by invoking the getAttribute,
looping through it and displaying the id and name.
You can right click on the application, say run as -> run on server. That will restart the server. Hit finish.
It asks for restart.
Hit OK.
And the URL that we should be using, if you go to the ListController, it should be
readList.
So go back to the browser, at the end type in read, l capital, list.
Enter.
And that will display the employee id
and the name for all three employees.