In this lecture, I will briefly introduce you to JPA and Spring Data JPA.
JPA stands for Java Persistence API.
It is a standard from Oracle to do object relational mapping, that is to store our objects into the database
and convert the database rows into objects and deal with them in our object oriented applications.
The providers or the implementations of this standard are Hibernate,
EclipseLink, OpenJPA and more.
We as developers learn the JPA API and these providers, they look at the JPA specification and
do the implementation for us.
So beneath the covers, we'll be using one of these implementations,
Hibernate being the most popular. The JPA standard provides EntityManagerFactory and entityManager, two
key interfaces which we use throughout our application or at least in the Data Access Layer to perform
create, update, read and delete against the database.
We deal with objects in these methods, internally
these providers will do the SQL for us. They will convert the objects into relational world and back to
objects which you would have seen in the hibernate section in the Spring course.
So we repeat these operations across applications, that is every time we create a Java EE application and
we create a Data Access layer, we create a repository class or a Data Access layer class, the DAO class
and we implement these four methods. That is where Spring Data comes in, Spring Data JPA comes
in. And it asks us to get rid of all that boilerplate coding. Without writing all that boilerplate coding
in our application, we can perform all the CRUD operations and many more that you'll see in the future.
For example, if you have a database table called Product and you created a entity, JPA entity. Mark it
with all the annotations and it's called Product. Now to perform CRUD operations on this entity,
you simply create an interface called ProductRepository and that interface will extend an interface
from Spring called CRUDRepository. That is all you need to do.
You need not implement any boilerplate code, any methods inside this.
This is an interface. You simply extend an other interface from Spring,
and you can perform all the CRUD operations on this interface for this Product.
You'll be seeing all that in action in the next few lectures.
We are going to use Spring BOOT, which inturn will make it easy for us to create a Spring Data.
JPA project and boot it up and see it in action.