The very first step to see Spring Data in action, is to create a project in STS. So go to your STS
IDE, File menu -> New -> Spring Starter Project. Give it a name, call it springdatajpa,
if you want to add, you can add jpa at the end. The service URL is start.spring.io which is okay.
Change the group name to com.bharath.spring.data.
Artifact name is springdatajpa. The package,
somehow it doesn't reflect the group name. So I'm going to copy the group name and paste it here.
Next, we need to choose two things here. So you can search from here.
You can select whatever dependencies you want.
Number one, search for jpa and select this JPA which is under SQL. That dependency is added.
Next, search for mysql, because we are going to connect to the MySQL database,
we need that Jar dependency. Finish. So the project is created. If you open the pom.xml, go
to the last tab. It would list all the starter dependencies for us.
Scroll down. It has spring-boot-starter-data-jpa, mysql-connector-java which is the JDBC driver and
some test jars or one single test jar.
Go to Maven dependencies and you will see a ton of other jars which Maven pulls through these
jars. So these dependencies here, transitively depend on these. So
Maven transitively pulls all the jars that it needs to get the work done. Starting the next lecture,
you will create an entity, you'll create a repository and we'll then see how easy it is to do the CRUD
operations against a database by coming up with a test.