We'll be creating an entity, a JPA entity in this lecture. For that we are going to use the Product table in
our database. Go to MySQL workbench. This is the same table which you would have used when you learnt hibernate
using Hibernate through Spring in earlier lectures. use mydb. If you do a select right now, I have cleaned up my Product
table, there are no records in the Product table.
It has four columns, id, name, description and price.
I'm going to create an entity from scratch.
You can copy the entity which you might have earlier from the hibernate lectures if you want to. Right click
on the package, say New -> Class, Product.
This entity, JPA entity represents the database table. Put it in a package called data.entities.
Finish.
It has or it needs four properties.
private Long id; private String name; private String description;
Let's see if that's exactly the name.
Yes, it is description and finally private Double price;
Generate getters and setters for these. Select them all, go to Source -> Generate Getters and Setters.
Select All. Hit OK.
As of now, it is still just a bean. Grab the properties, put them in the right position. Control+x, take them
all the way up, paste them. Control+Shift+f to format. To make this an entity,
you know what to do. Mark this class with @Entity annotation from JPA. Once it loads all the dependencies,
it's trying to figure out. javax.persistence,
that's the entity annotation and this with
@Id. Those are the only two annotations
we need. So we have successfully created an entity in this lecture. In the next one, you will create a Spring
repository, a repository interface that will extend an interface from Spring.