In this lecture, you will learn how easy it is to create a Product repository interface which can perform
all the CRUD operations for us on the fly at runtime. Thanks to Spring data
JPA. So right click on src/main/java -> New. You will create an interface, call it ProductRepo.
You can call it whatever you want.
Usually this is a naming convention, you either call it ProductRepo or ProductRepository. And package
com.bharath.spring.data.repos. Click on Add.
It needs to extend an interface from Spring. And search for CrudRepository.
Select this interface which allows us to perform CRUD operations on the fly.
Hit OK.
Finish.
And the CrudRepository is a genetic repository, which can take a class. In this case,
it is Product.
So if we have multiple entities in our application, we'll be creating multiple repositories, one for each
entity. And we'll be passing in the type of that entity here and the type of Id. In this case, the
Id on product is of type long.
So we are passing that information here.
Control+1, import Product, because it is in a different package. That's it. Starting the next lecture,
we can write our test and perform CRUD operations.