In this lecture, you will configure a datasource for our application without writing a single line of XML
or java code. That's right! Spring boot allows us to pass in all that information through application.properties file.
So go to src/main/resources,
open the application.properties and start adding four properties. spring.datasource and
STS will help you out and
fill it in, datasource.name is the first property, is equal to, give it a unique name.
Let's call it simply mydatabase.
You can give any name. spring.datasource.url is the second parameter and you know what that
URL is.
jdbc:mysql://localhost:3306/mydb
The next two properties are spring.datasource.username=root
in my case. Even in your case I think it is root. datasource,
one last property, dot password is equal to test
in my case. That could be different in your case.
So you have successfully configured a datasource in application.properties. When our application starts up
Spring will read this file.
Let me take an extra '=' right there.