In this lecture, you'll create a product record in the database by creating a test. To do that, go to
src/test/java.
Open up the test class that got generated. The very first step here is to inject the ApplicationContext.
ApplicationContext context; hit control+1,
import it from Spring. Add Auto wiring to it, Autowired. And within this test method, you can rename this test
method.
Right now it only is checking if the contexts are being loaded successfully and all the Spring beans
are wired.
That is why it is named contextLoads.
Change it to saveProduct.
context.getBean() and pass in the class name, which in this case is ProductRepository.
So we are getting an instance of the ProductRepository bean. Control+1, assign that to a new local variable.
Call it repository. And you can start using repository.save.
repository, let me get that spelling right,
dot, save.
And we can pass it a bunch of products or a single product. new Product. I will assign values to it in
a second. Take that or first import it. Hit control+1, import Product. Select that, control+1, extract to a
local variable. Call it Product. Set some properties on it, product.setId().
In this case we are not auto incrementing or we are not using any generating strategy for the Id field
in the database or in our application.
So we need to provide the Id, 1L.
It is a long field. product.setName("Mac");
product.setDescription("awesome") and product.setPrice(1200).
Save it.
Let's see what the problem is. It's a double,
so you need to have a d at the end.
Save it.
Let's run our test.
Right click, Run As -> JUnit Test.
Let's see if it passes without any issues.
That loads the Spring context or Spring Boot application is up and running and we see a green. If you go
to the progress bar,
or if you go to the JUnit Test, if you right click on this small thing here,
Test completed successfully.
Let's go to the database or go to the JUnit here.
If you click on this, it is green.
So this whole thing executed successfully. Go to the database, execute this select statement one more time
and you will see this record.
So to explain you the flow, the Spring Boot application starts up. It scans through all the repositories and entities.
First of all it scans through the classpath and it knows that we have Spring Data and MySQL jars. So it'll use them.
It will create all the database connections and all that on the fly, using the database properties that
we have provided or the data source that we have provided here.
So it figures out all that on the fly.
It creates an implementation of this ProductRepository on the fly for us.
When we invoke the methods on this ProductRepository, which inturn are coming from this CrudRepository
which is an interface, it automatically executes the appropriate SQL statements for us through hibernate.
So all that magic is happening behind the scenes making our job as a developer easier and we can focus on our business
logic instead of worrying about performing the CRUD operations which we pretty much do in every application.
In the next few lectures,
you will see the other operations on a repository in action.