The second of the CRUD operations is to read a record. We can easily do that using a repository. repository dot,
I can't get the repository spelling right.
repository.findOne() there are multiple find methods. You can findAll if there are multiple
products in the database.
For now, I'm going to try findOne and pass it a
unique Id, which is 1L. You can extract that out as a constant and reuse it in both these places. And assign
this, hit control+1, assign this to a new local variable.
Control+1, assign this statement to a new local variable, result. And you can do a sysout.
But we don't have a toString method on it.
So I'm going to add a toString method on the Product. Go to Product, go to Source and say
Generate toString() and select all the fields, OK.
Save it. Go back to the test class and run it again.
And let's see the result if it can fetch the product and display the results for us on
the console. It does it, right here if you see, product Id, name, description and price.