In this lecture, I will show you how to use an update operation or how to perform a product update.
So right here we are creating a product, and then we are finding it. Let's do a update product by changing
the result. result.setPrice(),
I am going to change the price of the product to 1500 dollars.
Now, the Mac price has gone up. And to update it, we'll be using the same method, the same save method.
repository.save() and pass it
the result. You can change that name if you want to. And that will save the product or that will update the
product. So automatically, the JPA API, it internally, hibernate implementation will check if that product
already exists
with this Id. If it does, it will update that instead of creating it again. And let's do a find one more
time. So you can copy this piece here or we can do a findAll. repository.findAll(), dot,
I'm going to use some Java 8 features here which is .forEach(). This forEach allows you to write a
lambda expression. If you have taken my Core Java course, you know how to use lambdas. Inside this forEach,
you can say p or product or whatever, dash, arrow mark, flower bracket open,
close the flower bracket.
This is a lambda expression.
So we'll get a list of products back
here or a collection of iterable products back.
I'm doing a forEach on that and I'm passing in a lambda expression which will be executed for each
product.
In this case we have only one product. p.getPrice();
Let's check the price to see if it got updated.
You can do a sysout inside it, system.out.println(p.getPrice()).
Once we see it, see the result, I will explain it one more time for you. So put the whole thing in a
sysout with a semi-colon.
Save it.
So repository.findAll().forEach(p->); display the price of the product.
Right click, do as Run As -> JUnit Test.
That should create a product in the database.
Fetch it and also then update the price. If you see the result here on the console,
it is 1500 now. So you have successfully updated a product as well as used the findAll method which
retrieves all the records in the database.
I will leave the delete and any other methods you will find on the repository, as an assignment.