In the previous lecture, you have learnt how to use the expression language of Spring to inject an integer
value by evaluating a expression.
In this lecture, you will learn how to inject or how to invoke static methods inside the expression. To do that,
we can use an integer negative value here. For example -99.
Save it, run the test.
And ofcourse 99, -99 and will be injected.
To convert this -99 into a positive value. I always want the Id to be positive. To do that,
we can use the static method from Math class. java.lang.math.abs is the method.
But to invoke a static method inside expression, here is the syntax. We should use T. Within the brackets,
the name of the class dot the static method name and any parameters we want to pass.
So it should always start with a T.
Let's use it. Inside the flower brackets,
start with a capital T, within brackets,
we specify the type, the java.lang.math.
We need to give the complete class name dot abs.
Absolute is the method and close the brackets.
-99 is the parameter that we are passing to the static abs method for absolute
inside the class java.lang.math. We use the class name to invoke a static method.
But in case of expression language, we use an additional T. Within the brackets,
the name of the class will go, dot the method name and then the parameters if any.
Let's rerun the test and this time you will see a 99 and not -99.
So in this lecture, you have successfully learnt the syntax for invoking a static method inside an expression
starting with T, the class name within brackets, dot the method name and then the parameters.