In this lecture, you will learn how to create objects inside the expression as well as how to access
the variables that are inside an object.
So get rid of this value here inside the flower brackets, pound within flower brackets to create an object
of type integer.
We can use the new integer and pass it a value to the constructor.
Within brackets, let's say 88.
Save it, run our test and the value will be 88.
So it's very straightforward.
We use the new operator and then the constructor to invoke the constructor and create an object.
If you want to access a variable or a static variable, we do it in a similar fashion of how you have
access the static method.
For example, the java.lang.integer has a min underscore value and max underscore value inside it.
So T(java.lang.Integer) within brackets,
dot MIN_VALUE.
This is a constant defined inside java.lang.integer. For example, go to test and at the end you can
say integer or do a sysout.
integer dot,
MAX_VALUE and MIN_VALUE, if you see these two
these are constants that are defined inside the integer.
Hit control+space, you can access them like this because there are constants. Hit Control, hold control and
click on it and you can go to the class.
It is a public static final integer field.
And it gives the minimum value that a, or a maximum value that an integer can hold.
Similarly we have a MIN_VALUE which tells the minimum value that a integer data type can
hold.
Do a control+d, get rid of it. Go back to our instructor class.
So here we are assigning the minimum value a integer can hold to this Id field.
It's a static and final field and we are using a T, within brackets the class name and then dot,
access that value.
Let's run the test,
see what that value is. We can't remember that value because it's a huge value.
Here you go.
This is the, it's a negative number.
It's the minimum value that any integer field can hold.
We are assigning it to our field here by using a static expression language syntax on the java.lang.integer.