In this lecture, you will learn how to use string types within an expression.
So let's assign some value or inject some value into this name here using expressions. Start
with pound within flower brackets, inside the quotes everything should be inside the double quotes, pound followed
by flower brackets and the string should go into single quotes because we have already used the double
quotes outside here, to assign the value.
So we shouldn't be using double quotes again in the expression, we can use single quotes to do that.
Let's see if this Bharath Thippireddy still gets injected into this name.
Run the test.
And we still see Bharath Thippireddy.
So using expression language you have successfully injected a string. To invoke methods on the string,
you can simply use dot toUpperCase. You don't get any help from the IDE because you're doing it inside
double quotes. So you need to know the method names to invoke.
You can go to test. You can invoke a method on new String().toUpperCase, it's camel case.
So just to confirm that we are using the right method toUpperCase. Come back to Instructor and use
it. Save it, run the test again and everything
now in the name is uppercase. We can also create a string using the new operator.
Get rid of this within flower brackets.
We can use new, but we have to use the, give the complete class name, java.lang.String(), within
brackets double quotes, sorry, single quotes. We can't use double quotes in expression language. Bharath Thippireddy,
because we are using double quotes outside. So the compiler will be confused.
Save it. Run the test again and we are back to Bharath Thippireddy.
So in this lecture, you have learnt how to use expressions with string values, you have used the new operator.
You have used the string directly within single quotes, as well as you have seen that you can invoke methods
on the string type.