Last primitive type that we'll cover using expressions is the Boolean type.
Let's add another field on this
Instructor which says whether he's active or not. private boolean active;
This flag tells
if the instructor is active or not. Use the @Value annotation, within brackets, to assign a boolean value
let's use an expression. Start with pound, within flower brackets, 2+4>5.
A simple boolean expression.
This could be any expression, you could use objects or whatever but the value at the end should
evaluate to boolean in this case.
In earlier cases, the value should evaluate to string, int and so on. So we have come up with a boolean expression.
Let's see the value of active.
We need to change or regenerate our toString method. Delete the toString. Go to source, generate
toString one more time so that the active will be included.
OK. Save it, run the test. Scroll right or maximize this console and then scroll right to see the boolean
value.
Or maybe scroll left, id, name and active right here, and it says true. You can use whatever boolean
expression you want.
You can also use ternary operator here. 2+4 is greater than,
let's get a false this time, 8 question mark,
false:true.
This expression here will evaluate to false. Ofcourse 2+4 is not greater than 8. So it will
return a true, it won't return a false.
So let's change this order.
True and on the right hand side,
let's have false.
Save it, rerun the test.
This time we have a false for active.
So in this lecture, you have successfully learnt how to use boolean expressions as well.
This could be any expression, it need not be numbers.
You can invoke methods or objects or whatever you want to do. But at the end it should return a boolean value.